Where is everyone?
[★Picnic day★]
[(Con) GOING SEVENTEEN One Heart Picnic (Grats)]
Oh, Mr. Woo!
-Thank you for all of this
-Yes, yes, yes
-We didn't know you were already here
-Let's go all out today
[Event organizer]
-We didn't know you were already here
-After you arrived last...
-Let's have fun today
-Mr. Woo
-I heard you prepared everything today
-Yes, yes
-Have you been well?
Yes, yes
[Haven't seen each other
since the company dinner]
-We meet again, huh?
-Yes, yes
[Tipsy papa]
How have you been? How have you been?
Oh, hey
-Oh, DK
-How have you been? How have you been?
-Oh, JOSHUA
-Oh, hey
I'm loving this
So bustling
[Has always been like this]
Hey, wait, wait
Hold up
Hold up, what?
[First steps of business English]
-Who's missing?
-Hold up, what? What? Hold up
Who's missing?
THE 8 is not here
[Advanced class]
[LOL]
-Anyway...
-Oh, sir
-How have you been?
-Aren't you the CEO?
[Multiple universes intersecting]
-Yes, yes, it's been so long
-Sir
I heard you company went under...
[Failed to obtain SEVENTEEN content]
I heard you quit
I left but Mr. Woo is holding
down the fort so well
[I am free]
-Yes
-Only the CEO resigned
[Department head and CEO]
But why is a picnic called a picnic?
-I was thinking about that too, you know?
-You pick someone to...!
Boo
[Late]
That's why it's a picnic
That's why
[THE 8 is here]
Now, let's get going
Yes, Mr. Woo!
[Let's go]
Where are we going?
I got it all sorted out
[Has all the answers]
I'm so excited, Mr. Woo
-Be quiet and just follow me
-Mr. Woo!
[Means "Me too"]
Deputy section chief DK has prepared an
acrostic poem with "Department head Yoo"
-What? Deputy section chief?
-You got a promotion?
Yes, yes, I have
Why are we going with "Yoo"
if he's Mr. Woo?
One, two, three, Woo!
[Doesn't like "You"]
One days when you feel like eating udon
-One, two, three
-Department
Join the department head
Oh? One, two, three
[In danger]
Head!
And walk around teasing each other
[Wants to be serious] [Joking around]
[Suddenly curious about what's outside]
The weather's nice today
[Signaling where to splice the video]
-Yes, it is
-Be sure to wear your seatbelts!
[So helpful to the editing team]
-Yes!
-Oh, we must wear seatbelts
-Did something happen?
-You need a seatbelt on your mouth...
I think I do
[Click] [For his own safety]
But, you know
if you've stepped down
why are you speaking to us so informally?
Even though I've resigned, we're still...
[Hoping they're still close]
-You know... Right? You know
-Why do you keep speaking informally?
Have you been promoted?
[Never-ending informal speech]
I'm the deputy department head now
Oh, you are?
We really value hierarchy in our company
so please use a formal tone
OK, I understand
[Hierarchy X Public and private O]
You guys...
Are we doing something
as soon as we arrive?
I've got it all planned out!
So, you don't know
[Is just being tight-lipped]
If you don't know, just be
honest and say that
-I've got it all planned out
so just follow me
-Alright
Earlier, JOSHUA said
he helped plan everything
-You?
-Tell them
[Pro tip: If things go well, it's thanks
to me, if they don't, it's your fault]
-I helped prepare
-So, you did everything
-I did
-Because he's an employee
[Employee] [That's why he's been quiet]
-This is our first picnic, right?
-Yes, it is
Well, then
Acrostic poem with "Picnic"
[It never ends]
One, two, three, pic!
Me?
[Realization]
[Extra work]
-You're in charge of acrostic poems
-I have a belt on...
-I'm in charge of acrostic poems?
-Yes
Pic!
Hey, you!
[Informal tone has spread]
One, two, three, ni-!
You're so
One, two, three, -c!
Uh...
OK, make sure your seatbelts are fastened!
[Snore] [Suddenly carsick]
-Yes!
-The weather is so nice
[Peace]
It was fine up till "You're so"
DINO, have you been promoted?
[Enjoying the weather]
What do you think my position is now?
[Surprise! Quiz]
From the way you speak
you sound like the CEO
-Your outfit screams CEO
-Let's hear it
[What do you think?]
Deputy section chief?
-I'm a section chief
-Oh, I see
Mr. Lee
-Mr. Lee!
-Oh, yes, yes
Hey, Mr. Lee!
-Yes, yes
-What's your position?
I'm just an employee
[In a lower hierarchy]
What are you doing?
-What?
-It's free time, free time
How dare you, in this equal society?!
[Respect, plz]
Are you sure you're a section chief?
[Deja vu]
Why don't we all say our titles?
Yes, yes
-From our newest employee
-OK, OK
JOSHUA
I'm JOSHUA, an employee
A round of applause for JOSHUA!
[It's a picnic, not orientation]
-Thank you
-Round of applause!
As expected of our CEO
Let's start from here and go in order
For me... In our company...
I oversee our overseas operations
[Added details]
-The international development team
-In the international development team
I'm the team leader
[Was a regular employee a year ago]
Oh, the team leader
Team leader JUN
[Nice company where everyone's promoted]
The team leader
You're running the company well
You even have an international team now
[Already existed]
Of course
[Summary of why the CEO stepped down]
OK, VERNON
Yes, I'm the doenjang in the
international development team
-You're the what?
-The doenjang
[Thought he misheard]
[The thing about jokes: If they
have to ask again, it's a bad one]
What?
-Doenjang?
-Oh, he's the doenjang
[Suspicions confirmed]
Oh, the doenjang of the
international development team
[Brings the flavor]
That joke was a travesty
[Such a nice summary]
HOSHI, HOSHI
[Saved the moment]
Thank you, thank you
What's going on? That was good?
Mr. Kwon saved it
Next, say something
OK
Oh
As you know
I'm section chief Lee
Oh, Mr. Lee
What team are you on?
[Drop the joke]
For me...
[LOL]
"For me"...
I'm in the marketing team
-You do marketing
-You're in marketing?
[Not marketing team] [A lot has happened]
No matter how good
a company's product is
-Things won't work out
without good marketing
-We were a marketing, ad company
So he has the most important job
[That's why he's the section chief]
We're a marketing company?
[Confusing GOING COMPANY]
-I'm in the promotional team
-Promotions
The team leader
Oh, there are a lot of team leaders here
He's my subordinate
Marketing and promotions
[The thing about jokes 2:
First come, first serve]
He's the team leader of a smaller group
[a.k.a snake's head]
Yes, yes, yes...
That document...
You didn't pass on that
approved document I gave you?
Well...
I just paid for it with your card
[Dipped into personal funds]
-Oh, really?
-Good, good
[Great thinking from the head]
OK
-Yes, start from that side
-Oh, for me...
-You're title ends with
"Jang," right? "Boo Jang"
-Yes...
I'm Mrs. Jwa's Yangnyeomgejang
[Mmm]
[LOL]
He laughed, he laughed
[So nice] [Saved so many today]
-As long as one person laughed
-No, it was funny, it was funny
So full...
A very full yangnyeomgejang
[Not fully coated in sauce→]
Oh, yangnyeomgejang
-Yangnyeomgejang
Mr. Woo's...
son
[Name: Woo Tipsy]
What? A son?
[Secretive birth]
-You're Mr. Woo's son?
-Why did you bring your son?
-Your Mr. Woo's son?
-How could you bring your son?
[Family company] [Nepotism]
Is this nepotism?
I didn't know I had a son like you
[Forcibly made independent]
OK, Mr. Woo's son, what's your name?
Woo Minghao, Woo Minghao
[Name for international business]
[LOL] [Seatbelt off]
-Woo Minghao
-Woo Minghao?
[Makes mouths big and bright]
-Woo Minghao
-Yes, Woo Minghao
[Minghao Papa]
Woo Minghao, and next
I'm team leader Jeon
Team leader, team leader Jeon
Team leader Jeon
[If he leaves, he'll be
the former team leader Jeon]
-What team?
-What division are you in?
Criminal Investigation, second division
Team leader of criminal investigation
What kind of company is this?
-Because crime can happen at any time
-That's right
[Company that respects differences]
Yes, and the last one
Hello, I'm an employee, Mr. Kwon!
Wow!
Mr. Kwon, you're so full of energy today
I haven't been assigned yet
-You haven't?
-No
[Forced to be an all-rounder]
It hasn't been decided yet
what team you're going to
-No
-Then!
What about a scribe?
Scribe Kwon?
Scribe Kwon!
[His future was already predetermined]
-I like that
-Scribe Kwon is good
[His future was already predetermined]
Are we playing foot volleyball?
[Excursion-Foot volleyball=0]
Of course, it's a picnic
I've wanted to ask
The highlight of any trip
is the barbecue or
dinner at the end, right?
It's all been prepared
-I'm sure that Mr. Woo prepared everything
-Really?
[Elbow point]
Mr. Woo prepared 15 bottles
of soju just for you, Mr. Lee
Really?
Prepare to die tonight and follow me
Will you also be having a drink, Mr. Woo?
I'll have 10 bottles
Wow, 10 bottles
[Didn't specify size of bottles]
Get ready to get really drunk
[Always ready to go]
Be sure to pick a spot
on the ground to sleep on
No one sleeps in a bed tonight!
[One with nature on this picnic]
This is an overnight trip?
[Bye bye, weekend]
We'll make it one
Do you think our company
has no money or something?
No money and no something either
[Absolutely nothing]
What you just said was nonsense
No money or something
[Thus began a moment of complete silence]
[Sip] [A sip of silence]
The weather is nice
We need pauses like this
to get good facial expressions
[Yummy]
Since we're off to a good start...
Shut it!
[Hard agree]
[Knew this would happen]
Go on, Mr. Lee
What was it? What were you saying?
[Happy]
I don't want you to shut it, keep going
I want him to be quiet
[Check the seatbelt]
What was his role again?
Yangnyeomgejang
Yangnyeomgejang?
[Getting rice instead of a salary]
I don't know what to say about that
[Untouchable]
-It's kind of like kkakdugi
-Nice, tasty
[Department: Delicious taste]
I'm Jwa Gejang
-Tasty
-"Tasty"
Anything is possible
You're mother's sauce...
Jwa Gaehwa's son, Jwa Gejang
-I can't say anything, I can't touch that
-Yes, nice
The foliage isn't that vibrant
[Filmed in late October]
The leaves are probably about to fall?
Right?
I think the leaves are done changing
colors and are getting ready to fall
♪ I was going to go ♪
♪ Before the sun set ♪
[Karaoke singer 1] [Karaoke singer 2]
♪ To that place you and I were ♪
[What tomorrow will probably be like]
♪ Now, you must ♪
[No interest X]
♪ go on a journey ♪
[Haven't had a single drink]
♪ My precious friend ♪
♪ I was going to go ♪
[Get home safely]
♪ Before the sun set ♪
Wait, something's weird
[LOL]
Something's weird
[Innocent]
♪ I'll always be here ♪
[Confused homebody]
That was fun, singing
the chorus with verse lyrics
That's not right? That's not right?
It's not
♪ I was going to go ♪
♪ Before the sun set ♪
[Realized how to always be here]
You really didn't know?
-I didn't, I didn't, I didn't
-What? You really didn't know?
I thought you were trying to be funny
♪ I tried to go before the sun set ♪
You really...
[Not hurt anywhere]
You really wanted to go home
[LOL]
You really wanted to go
home before the sun set
He was sending a message
No, no, I love this company picnic!
[How everyone feels about
work-related weekend events]
I love when it's a two-day event
-How about we sing a song?
-Hit it!
The perfect song for traveling!
[Hit his hand]
♪ Let's go on a trip! ♪
♪ Babara barabaram ♪
♪ With a happy heart ♪
[Excited on the inside]
But
I heard that Mr. Woo's son is here
-Yeah
-In that case
[Loves his son]
-Let's hear a song from the youth!
-Yes!
[Baby] [Old man (1999) looks for the youth]
-Let's hear it, young guy
-You really know how to play, don't you?
Yes, yes
[Fresh-faced youth]
Mr. Woo, how old is your son?
My son...
is around five years old?
Yes, around five
[Getting him socialized early]
Then, a children's song would be perfect
-OK, OK
-Children's song
-A Chinese children's song
-Three bears...
-Or something like "Baby Shark"
-Do you know "Baby Shark"?
-Five-year-olds love "Baby Shark"
-Yes, yes
Sing "Three Bears"
[Most-recent song for him]
♪ There are three bears, there is one ♪
There's one? Nice, nice
[Two ran away]
There's one?
Is it the papa, mama, or baby bear?
-Just sing it, whatever lyrics you want
-Go on, go on
Five, six, seven, eight
-♪ There's one bear ♪
-Nice, nice!
-It's fine, it's fine
-Let's all clap along
♪ There are three bears ♪
[They all came back home]
-♪ There are three bears ♪
-Yes, yes!
-Who are they?
-♪ Papa bear ♪
♪ Papa bear, mama bear ♪
-Baby bear
-♪ Baby bear ♪
-♪ Papa bear is ♪
-What is papa bear like?
[Like a family gathering]
♪ Nice ♪
♪ We like him ♪
♪ Mama bear is ♪
♪ Pretty ♪
♪ She's pretty ♪
-♪ Baby bear is ♪
-Five syllables
♪ Really smart ♪
[Hoping for that]
[Got the right number of syllables]
-♪ Yes, yes ♪
-And?
♪ Well done ♪
Well done!
[Well done!]
[Bear family has been thoroughly cooked]
You must have played music for him often
He said mama bear is pretty
-Great job!
-So cute, so cute
[Pride of the family]
The baby really lifted the mood
Yes, he did
Want some money?
[Time to pay the talent]
[Teaching him that
nothing in life is free]
[LOL]
Just two, OK?
Mr. Woo, he's giving your kid pocket money
Good, good, good
[Actually going to him]
-Two is enough, right?
-Yes, yes
[Confirm]
[Didn't say what color they were]
Wow... Wow...
[Earning a living]
-You're acting like such an old man
-So cute
I heard we're having a meeting today
Have you prepared for it?
We're holding a meeting?
-A meeting at a picnic?
-What...
[Direct translation] [A true picnic]
As the CEO, I think that going to a picnic
and holding a meeting when
we're so happy could result in
[Would be fun.]
-a lot of positive ideas
-OK, boomer
[Direct]
Mr. Woo, you didn't prepare for this?
[Already has]
-I've prepared everything, just follow me
-You prepared for this?
[Definitely a J]
OK, OK
Can we share ideas right now?
[Refuses to wait]
-Yes, yes
-Let's share some ideas?
Because he's still new to the company
-He's quick on his feet?
-He's full of energy
-He's proactive
-Nice, nice
I used to be like that
[Don't Lie]
Mr. Kwon, do you have any ideas?
Well... Just to give you the big picture
2023!
[Such a big picture]
-He's trying to do something
-He's going to say something weird
Because it's 2023!
We should do some weird content
23 content?
[Helping]
-Yes, 23 content
-Oooh
Like "23 content (Weird content)"
-23 content
-That's a good idea
-We go to see a dentist
-All of us together?
And the ones who need it...
-Get scaling done, so good
-All together?
[Interested]
Oh... bad teeth...
Say MINGYU has three rotten teeth
-Yes, yes
-Let everyone know
[Confused]
We'll have to bring out the x-rays too
Yes, everything
That's what will make it funny
[Honest show]
The one with the most rotten teeth wins
Yes
[Bad teeth] [True to the content concept]
So, we can't brush our teeth till then...
We shouldn't brush our teeth
so we can be funny?
[That's the kind of content we can expect]
Listen up, listen up
It's the age of NFTs, right?
It's the age of NFTs
[Intelligent]
What's our team name?
-SVT, right?
-Yes
To keep up with the age of NFTs, SEVENTEEN
will go to 〇KT
[Amazing rhyming going on]
and get a brand deal with them
[But with a dash of capitalism]
Do you feel like you
aren't doing enough ads?
-You keep going after more brand deals?
-Why...!
[Desire for money grows]
Because it's the age of NFTs
-We should meet FT ISLAND
-Oooh!
-Oooh
-And do a collab with them
[Failed to make a profit]
SEVENTEEN, N FT
Oooh SEVENTEEN N FT
Oooh
What song comes to mind
when you think of FT ISLAND?
♪ You're a bad girl ♪
[I'm not done talking yet]
♪ Yeah ♪
[First event] [Picnic celebratory stage]
-♪ You're a bad girl ♪
-All of a sudden!
[Busting into his eardrums]
Such a bad girl
[Such a loud voice, you wonder
why he isn't more famous]
It shocked me
[LOL]
-There's also "Love Sick"
-Yes, so sick
Please sing "Love Sick" for us
♪ The crime of ♪
Loving...
[Difference between a
singer and yangnyeomgejang]
How about we get some rest?
[Clean CUT]
-OK
-Yes, yes
-We'll talk at the meeting later
-We've gotten enough
[Agreeing]
I heard you've prepared an acrostic poem?
[LOL...]
Save me
[LOL]
He's your subordinate...
-Hey, Mr. Lee
-Do an acrostics poem
[Flipped hierarchy]
And I'm acting all subordinate
to my subordinate
-♪ I was going to go ♪
-♪ Before the sun set ♪
♪ So you, tired from
walking, could see me ♪
-Wow, it's a soccer field
-There's a soccer field
[Arrived at their destination]
We've arrived!
Is it finally starting?
[13-minute prologue]
What are we doing first when we get out?
-I'll explain once we're off the buss
-Wow, Mr. Woo, you did a lot, didn't you?
You've chosen a great spot
♪ A drone floating in the sky ♪
[Knew they'd sing it]
Since we've all arrived safely
a around of applause!
[★Let's get started★]
Nice!
What should we do now?
It would be boring to
head straight inside, right?
-Yes, yes
-And so?
A treasure hunt!
-A treasure hunt!
-Wow
-We're doing a treasure hunt?
-Wow!
[Very refreshing]
So we can move around
instead of resting
We've hidden various treasures
[Someone else did]
-Oh ho
-There are a lot of hidden treasures
Are they amazing treasures?
Some of them are!
[Doesn't know what the prizes are]
-We can expect great things?
-Yes
Yes, you can
[Also has high expectation]
I'm excited!
[Can't hide his emotions]
-I worked hard to prepare for this
-Nice, nice
But a treasure hunt where you just...
find the treasures and
collect your prizes is boring
-Yes, yes
-Yes
You can figure out what
prizes others have found
and you can steal from each other
[Another peaceful day for SEVENTEEN]
We can't use physical force
so we have a simple way to steal prizes
Say you know what prize
this person has found
-If you know?
-If you know
-Then, you get to steal it
-OK
You're not allowed to use physical force
Even if you don't know exactly
I think you got... an MP3 player??
And if that's the right answer?
You can steal it
[Can guess]
People still use MP3 players?
MP3?
[A must back in the day]
MP3...
Are you looking down on i〇ver?
[i〇ver's name comes from "Internet river"]
i〇ver?
[Faint memory]
-Mine was from i〇ver
-Yes
[Now, it's more of an internet ocean]
OK, then should we get started?
Any questions?
No!
Then, let's go!
[Mr. Woo is ready to go]
Let's go!
[Treasure hunt starts]
-Let's go, let's go
-How do we go down?
Where do we go?
-They said it's around a lake
-It's a field
A treasure hunt, Mr. Woo...
[Loving it♥]
I love it, oh, I didn't see you there
[Sucking up to the boss♥]
When did you come up
with this treasure hunt?
-I know as much as you guys do
-Yes, of course
Mr. Woo, how many treasures are there?
-Around 30
-30?
Then, they shouldn't be hard to find?
[Can each get around two prizes]
No, no, this place is so big
It's such a big area
Hey, where's the lake? Is this the lake?
It will definitely be behind the building
How are we going to find these?
But what do the treasures look like?
They showed it to us, you didn't see?
Rather than moving around too much
just casually walking around like this
actually helps you spot things
That's what I think
[Has no energy to run, so relatable]
They say it's usually right
in front of your nose
[The bus they just rode on]
Oh, I found it, I found it
Wait, I'm not usually
good at stuff like this?
What? What? What?
[Found the first treasure]
[Poker face]
[Removes the outer casing]
I should hide and check it out later
[Back and forth]
Hey, deputy department head
[Is the section chief]
Found anything?
We only just got started
Your pockets are pretty full
[LOL...] [Goodness]
We'll see
See you later
Oh
[Treasure]
[DINO finds a treasure]
I found it, found it, found it
I found it
Haa...
[LOL]
There are too many people here, oh no
[Looking for an unboxing spot]
DINO, found anything?
No
[Still taking those acting classes]
[LOL]
"No"
He's acting
[I know everything]
[Fail] [Too bad]
[Didn't say that all
30 treasures are a prize]
I'll find one, no matter what
[Trash]
What's this?
It's not it, is it?
[A different company must have
also done a treasure hunt]
Isn't the foliage so pretty?
Yes, it is
I should take a photo
[Update background photo] [Autumn is here]
Yes!
[MINGYU finds a treasure]
[Suspicious feeling creeps up his spine]
I can't steal it if
I don't know what it is
That's right, and you won't know it
because I don't know what it is either
What does it look like?
-This?
-Show me the outside part
Oh, like this
-Good, good
-It's not that obvious
It will probably be where
we think they'll be
[JUN finds a treasure]
What? What? JUN, what is it?
No, I won't tell you
Show me too, MINGYU
What do they look like?
I threw away the cardboard
I only took what was inside
[Feels like he has a plan]
[VERNON finds a treasure]
Did you find one?
I did
[Honest]
VERNON found one, VERNON found one
-He found one?
-Guys, VERNON found one!
[Looking for fellow hyenas]
-Did you find something?
-I found something
[Quickly arrives]
Let's see
-No
-What does the case look like?
The case? This seems to be the case
-What's inside of it?
-I don't know
[What is with these conversations]
-Have you opened it?
-No, I haven't
Let's open it
-No, no
-I won't steal it, I really won't
No, no
-I swear on everything I have that I won't
-No, no, I don't want to
Let's see what's inside!
[Leading an honest life is tiring]
[JOSHUA finds a treasure]
I found one
-Where are they?
-They said they're in the branches
Hey, DK is hiding something!
[Lion]
-He found one!
-DK is hiding something!
[Time for a hunt]
Turn everyone's attention away
Wow...
DK, do they all look like milk cartons?
[Round and round] [Living like Shin-chan]
-They look like this
-Oh, they look like that?
They're the same color as the trees!
And as I say that
[Live life like JOSHUA]
-You found one, didn't you?
-DINO's found on
-You found one, right?
-I haven't
-Come on
-I really haven't
You came here to check yours, didn't you?
[Deduction from experience]
I just want to find one
-Really?
-I really want to find one
-Have you found one?
-No
No way...
We can't take them by force anyway
So tell me, you found one, right?
I really haven't
-You really haven't?
-No
-They hid so many, how have I found none?
-Right? When there are 30
[Wants to be alone]
I'm sure they're here somewhere
[So nice that he won't leave JOSHUA alone]
-I'm sure they're here
-Definitely
-Hey
-What?
Let's be honest...
[WONWOO finds a treasure]
Wow, that was close
-Wow, really...
-I don't think you saw it at all?
I'm so sad, I was looking at
the tree this whole time
Let's split that
-No, what are you talking about?
-We were here together
[Solomon]
-Move, don't be ridiculous
-Wait, wait
Let's talk it out, let's talk
I won't steal it, I won't
We arrived at this spot at
the exact same time, like fate
[Do you have a minute?]
This is fate, right?
[No, thank you]
Just keep looking
-I'm done, I'm not going to look anymore
-I'll help you
[We're closed]
-That will be my last
if we split it in half
-No, no
Let's just look at it together
There's nothing here, I checked
[Wants all of his attention]
-I just want to see and I won't steal it
-No, no
-I promise, you trust me, right?
-Alright, it's fine
I don't trust you!
-Go away
-But you trust me
[A world full of distrust]
-If I steal it
-Go away
-I promise I won't steal it
-No
-Let's just look at it together
-Really
-No
No, no
I swear on the skies
[Getting dragged into it] [Sky:?]
I swear on the skies!
[Goodbye]
WONWOO!
Go away!
-Seriously
-Hey!
I found one
[Perfect chance]
There, there
I found one
[Even the cameraman was fooled] [Got it]
You're so mean
I'm really going to get upset at you
I'll look at it on my own
Alright, look at it, look at it
He wouldn't look at it that long
if it was nothing
It's a fail, nothing
No way
[Took a long time to read one syllable]
-WONWOO
-It's nothing
That Mr. Woo
[Enjoying a walk thanks to him]
[Breathing in the fresh air thanks to him]
He hid them well
[So well that it took him
this long to find one]
I feel like it's going to be nothing
Why won't it open?
Fail!
[Different font from earlier]
As expected
It will probably be somewhere...
Oh?
I found it
[THE 8 finds a treasure]
[Another different font]
[No two fails are the same]
No one has one
[Many different fonts prepared
to keep them going]
It's kind of funny, isn't it?
Oh...
Seriously?
Seriously...
It's a fail
Wow
[Mr. Woo really prepared so much]
Have you seen this?
[A good marketer = Has no preconceptions]
[Frustrated] [But can't understand ducks]
-No, give it here
-Come on
Argh
DK, why are you being like this?
[Annoying]
Go on, go on
No, not this one
-No, it's really a fail
-The one you just found
The one I just found was a fail
-You found one?
-No, I haven't
-Did you really just find this?
-Yes
Haa...
There's nothing here!
Why are you like this?
[Set up a trap]
How do you even find them?
-JEONGHAN
-Yes?
Did you find anything?
No, I haven't
Come on, you just found one
-No, I haven't...
-Spill the beans
No, seriously
What are you talking about?
You really...
I'm just realizing this now
but I'm really bad at lying
Yes
[Chilling lies]
What have you found?
No, I haven't found anything
-Don't make me laugh
-Seriously
I was walking over here and you
were there
[LOL]
like this
[Kind of like a kid in a sandbox]
"Did you find something?"
"No, I didn't find anything"
What are you talking about?
Why can't I see any?
Why am I so bad at this?
I have no plans to steal yours
Yes
So, let's see what's in there together
-I want to know what the prizes are
-That would defeat the purpose
I just want to see it with you
and congratulate you
[♥Joy multiplies when shared♥]
Who said I'd steal it?
-I won't
-Just congratulate me for finding it
Like, "SEUNGKWAN, congratulations"
I want to see what it is
and celebrate with you
I haven't checked it either
-For example, it could be a tablet PC
-I haven't opened it yet
-Yes
So
A styler
A styler? Wow, that's amazing
Congratulate me
Congratulations on the styler
That's awesome
-Hey, kitty
-A styler sounds great
-Sounds like more than enough
[Is a person]
What did you get?
We should... make it more fun
-A bicycle
-What?
-Come on
You're saying they gave you a bicycle?
-That's what it says
-It's much more expensive than mine
What's yours?
A lock
[Treasure is under lock and key]
Where are you going?
Let me join you
-What is it?
-No
Why?
SEUNGKWAN, why aren't you looking?
He's so cute
Have you found one?
-I'm looking
-MINGYU!
[True treasure]
Yes?
-MINGYU
-Yes?
How many have you found?
I haven't found any
[Nervous sweat]
[LOL]
-Hey
-We won't be able to steal it
Why is everyone lying?
[Just wants half]
-The rumors have spread already
-Hey
Everyone I ask says
"I haven't found any"
[Faith, trust, respect in each other]
-Oooh?
-There's a kitty?
-What?
-He's staying still, he's staying still
Baby, oh my
You were looking at the cat?
Imagine the cat gets up
and there's a treasure there
[Mr. Woo's amazing planning]
Wow...
Here it is
[LOL]
-So pretty
-Should we go?
-Look at his tail
-Is that a good thing?
Yes, it's a good thing
-It means he's happy
-Oh, his tail sticking up means he's happy?
If it looks like this
Like a question mark
Oh, I'm curious about you
Like that?
[Must have been a cat in his past life]
-Oh, yes, kind of
-Is this an exclamation mark?
-An exclamation mark?
-I'm surprised right now?
[Translation! Amazing!]
SEUNGKWAN, how many have you found?
What do you mean, how many?
Even finding one is hard
Every person I've asked said
"I haven't found any"
[Unintentionally all on
the same wavelength]
No one's found one
The game won't end till the sun sets
[Might find the rest at the next picnic]
I hope it's not a fail
[Fail]
[Life never goes the way you want it to]
Oh...
-What is it?
-I found one
Let's look at it together
I'll just congratulate you
I really have no plans to steal it
-Really?
-SEUNGKWAN told me what he has
-Yes
-OK
-Let's see it together
I just want to know what the prizes are
Alright, bye
Hey, but
-I got that too
-Really?
Hey, hey, hey
-I've been thinking about it
-OK
-Yours was a fail, right?
-How did you know?
-I've been thinking about it
-They're all fails?
I think they're all fails
[Toying with them is fun]
-Because mine was a fail too, right?
-OK
I told SEUNGKWAN mine was a bicycle
and he said his is a padlock
[LOL]
It doesn't make sense
To me
[LOL]
To me, he said it was a styler
[Taking back the congratulations]
[LOL]
I got it too
They're all fails
Why is he lying?
But the fonts are a little different
They're all a fail
[Fail-gate is beginning to emerge]
-They're all fails
-Seriously
Mine has these smiling eyes
At least that one's quite polite
You see...
[Here to tell Mr. Woo]
-We've been checking all the found ones
-Yes
And I think the GOING
SEVENTEEN team is playing us
-They're all fails
-Mine too
[LOL]
-Right?
-Yes
I'm starting to get annoyed
How many have you found?
-We won't steal them, what is it?
-I found one
A fail
I haven't found a single one
-Is it really a fail?
-I found one...
What's yours? We really won't steal it
-There's no need for that, it's a fail
-Yes, it's this
-That means they're all fails
-What did you get?
Mine is also a fail?
[Equal Fail-VENTEEN]
-They're all fails
-They're all fails?
-Hey, that means...
-Don't lie
Is yours a fail?
It's bread
Bread?
He got bread
[Believes him]
-Bread?
-Yes
-At least you got something
-Like the bread you eat?
No, it's a fail
What about you?
[Treasure hunt is over]
-It must be over
-We'll figure out soon enough
Wow, really?
How are you supposed to find it
when it's this well-hidden?
[Doctor]
Huh?
[Today is a surprise game of "Don't Lie"
You are the doctor for the day
The treasure hunt ends now for you.]
So annoying
How do you even find them?
-JEONGHAN!
-Yes?
Did you find anything?
No, I haven't