[RUN BTS: BTS vs Zombies]
[We will keep running!]
RUN BTS!
Where are we now?
[Looking around] [A bus?]
Look around. Can't you tell?
We're at...
- The world of fantasy!
- That's right.
- Everland!
- Everland.
[Today's RUN BTS]
[Begins at Everland,
the world of fantasy]
[Sparkling eyes]
- Why are we at Everland?
- Why are we here?
Today's theme of "RUN BTS!" is
"Find BTS' childhood innocence."
- Can we enjoy the rides?
- Are we riding the merry-go-round?
[No way]
I don't think so.
[Quick-witted]
Can't you see what's behind us?
[Looking around]
- A tiger.
- Are we going on the safari?
[Scratch]
Have you ever been to a zoo at night?
[In one voice]
- Nope.
- We can't go in there.
[The zoo is scary at night...]
Right, they don't open at night.
[Night safari for BTS]
But Everland opened it specially for you.
[Clap clap]
BTS has made it!
[For international sunshine rainbow BTS!]
They opened a safari for us at night!
[That's BTS!]
BTS has made it!
- (Sa) Fari.
[Find BTS' childhood innocence!]
[At a night safari opened for BTS]
[BTS will bond with the animals
and find their childhood innocence]
- Wow.
Are we all in one team today?
[Why would we risk our lives at a safari?]
- Sure.
- Risk our lives?
- It's no fun if you're on one team.
- That's true.
[A special mechanism will divide teams]
We prepared a special mechanism
[Spacing out]
that will divide your teams.
Let's go explore the world
of childhood innocence.
[Let's go! Let's go!]
- Let's go on the safari.
- Let's ride the bus.
[Off to find their childhood innocence]
- RUN BTS!
- Let's go!
BTS, to the world of childhood innocence!
[Saying whatever]
Safari at night, so is it a night-fari?
[Tigers are awake at night]
Tigers stay awake at night.
- Tigers.
- Since they're nocturnal.
[Excited to meet animal friends]
The lights seem a bit spooky.
[The lights...]
Right, the lights...
[Excited to meet animal friends]
- The lights are a bit...
- This feels like a bus to the underworld.
[See you there!]
Let's go!
[Like he's being held hostage]
- See you!
- Everland!
[Let's go to find our childhood
innocence with BTS!]
Let's go!
[Night safari just for BTS]
The safari bus has departed.
[So excited]
- Safari!
- Fari! Fari!
The world filled with fantasy, adventures
and mysterious animals.
[Going through the safari entrance gate]
Welcome to the night safari.
[Doubtful]
- Welcome, everyone.
- Night safari?
[Yup... it is...]
That's a thing?
[Hobi is scared of tigers]
This is the area where tigers live.
[Jung Kook is so excited]
- Fantastic Tigers.
- Let's take a closer look
[Where are they?]
to find tigers.
[Rising expectations for the safari]
I hope they won't drop us
in the middle of this place.
[Scared Hobi]
- Why is it so foggy?
- We need to find tigers in the forest.
- Tigers.
- It's hard to find them here.
[I can see one!] [Where?]
- There!
- Where?
Let's find them.
[Joking]
I can't see any.
Guys!
Oh, my.
[The real theme for RUN BTS is...]
Hey! It's a zombie run!
[BTS vs Zombies Special]
[BTS will play 3 games of zombie safari,
secret mission and freeze tag]
[to fight off zombies and get more
free tickets to Everland for ARMY]
[Surprised]
- Guys!
- Oh, my.
- Hey, it's a zombie run!
- We just lost contact
[Surprised]
with our agent Peter who went inside.
[Angry]
I knew something was off!
[Zombies appeared]
[About to cry]
- What's that?
- Please, don't.
[When did we fool you?] [Angry]
They fooled us again!
[Surprised by how real the zombies look]
That's so real!
Peter is getting attacked by zombies.
[Serious] [Hobi's about to cry...]
There must be survivors outside.
I'll go down with Brewster
[Survivors are seen between zombies]
and remove the obstacles.
[Brewster had to go down but...
he runs toward j-hope]
[No! I can't go down! I can't!]
Please, go out with him! Hurry!
[Save Hobi!]
[Anybody but me]
There's no time! Come on!
[In scary movies, those who get off
the bus end up...] [Please say no]
Do I really have to do this?
[So funny]
[In denial]
You can't do this to me.
Seriously...
[Hobi is following directions well]
Please hold this. Let's put this away.
Let's put it there.
[Faster than the zombies]
Zombies!
[Sounds like a broken record...]
Why? What's going on?
[j-hope is running to avoid the zombies]
[Looking around]
Driver! Open the door!
- What's happening?
- What?
[What's this?]
A zombie got him.
[Not yet]
Get out of my way!
[Busy running together]
Hey! Hey! Hey!
[SUGA saw a zombie]
[Chaos]
[Ahhh!]
[Freaking out]
[Lost his shoe]
Your shoe.
- Let's keep going.
- How was it like?
[I lost my shoe]
- Where's my shoe?
- There are zombies outside.
[j-hope showed amazing reactions]
Where's my shoe?
[Dropped his shoe during the chase]
Fortunately, there are
still survivors down there.
[Scared]
- No, there's no one.
- If we pass by here, we can get home safe.
[Sorry? Do I have to get off?]
- Come on. We need to walk from here.
- We have to get off the bus!
[Brewster continues to rush them]
Let's get off! We need to walk!
We need to get off and walk!
[Slowly]
Hurry up! We have no time!
[BTS vs Zombies]
[First game is to decide teams]
[Take off alphabet stickers from
the zombies' clothes. The members with
the same alphabet will team up.]
[Dumbfounded]
[Frightened]
[Boxing?] [1, 2]
[j-hope shows amazing reactions]
[Succeeded taking off the alphabet sticker]
[Zombies are everywhere]
[Having fun]
[Where did you get that...?]
[V and Jung Kook are on one team]
- A?
- A. We're a team.
[Someone help me]
Ahhh!
[Is this the sound of zombies
or SUGA's screams?]
Give me the sticker!
[BTS struggling to get stickers]
[Surprised!]
[Holding his breath and
trying to take off the sticker]
This is driving me crazy.
[These two are busy
running away from zombies]
[Dash]
Whoa!
He got two.
[BTS finally gathered up]
That freaked me out.
[BTS vs Zombies]
[Team A: RM, V, Jung Kook]
[Team B: Jin, SUGA]
[Team C: j-hope, Jimin]
Now you'll get through
the remaining missions with your team.
[Tired]
That was so scary.
I wasn't expecting that.
[BTS looked forward to the safari]
I had no idea. Zombie games?
This is amazing.
[One who was doubtful]
- I was suspicious. - Me, too.
[SUGA's getting mad several times today]
I knew the night safari didn't make sense.
[Stole it from a zombie]
- When did you steal this?
- Didn't you take two stickers?
[Trust us!]
We'll show you the safe way to get out.
[Protesting]
Safe? No way!
- It's not safe at all.
- The zombies must have moved.
[RUN BTS! BTS vs Zombies
The 2nd game]
[Hidden missions and
a secret mission to find free tickets!]
[Along with the team missions]
We hid free tickets for ARMY here.
[Free tickets for ARMY are hidden here]
- They're hidden here?
- Yes.
Why did they hide tickets here?
- The more you find,
the bigger your love for ARMY is.
- To be exact,
- the more we find, the more we can give.
- Right.
- We'll fight for the tickets.
- We can give them to more ARMY.
[BTS vs Zombies]
[In a mysterious lab full of zombies,
each team finds hints and carries out a mission]
[to solve secret missions
and find free tickets for ARMY]
[We won't die]
Fighting! Let's survive.
[Jin & RM get surprised many times]
- Somebody passed by.
- The game's begun.
Somebody passed by.
Why are they doing this to me?
I don't even watch scary movies.
- Jimin! Come with us.
- Yes?
Don't go alone.
[Holding tight] [Hurried]
- Let's hold hands.
- Taehyung, come here.
[Worried] [Smiling]
Someone's there.
How can we go through?
Where should we go?
[A tablet with a map to help them]
- Not this one?
- This way?
We found one.
[It was not a free ticket]
- Nope.
- I knew it. It's empty.
[Playing tricks]
Let's put it in there to fool others.
[Found the first free ticket]
Found one.
[Team A is confused with the starting point]
Is that the starting point?
- We entered that way.
- I think there's a box.
V, let's go!
[Stopped] [Stopped together]
[Stare]
There it is.
[Bark!]
That's it?
[Smiling]
Thank you.
Let's go.
Where should we go?
[Pushing each other to go first]
Don't hide behind me. I'm scared too.
Look! A zombie!
[The zombie did nothing]
I know you're there.
[What did I do...?] [Scared]
Please don't!
Hey, my heart is weak.
- How can we go through there?
- Come with me.
[Persuading the other members]
What's wrong?
There's a zombie in front.
Let's pass by it together.
[It's nothing]
- Why are they doing this to us?
- Seriously.
[So scared]
Jimin, let's go somewhere else.
[Pretending to be fine]
He's a foreigner.
[Different from what he thinks]
He's a foreigner. You can step out now.
[Worldwide handsome boy trying to
negotiate with the foreign zombies]
Hello, hello. Come in.
[Ahhh!]
[Hey, foreign zombie]
Do you have a ticket?
No?
Don't do that.
[SUGA keeps asking why this is happening to him]
[Jin can't move a step]
Why would they do this to me?
[Can Team B successfully solve the mission?]
Please, don't do that.
[Peep]
[Looking around]
Come on!
[Tap-dancing]
[Don't worry, Hobi. I won't hurt you]
They're not Korean.
[Hey, bring it on]
[Busy getting surprised continuously]
[Meanwhile, in Team A] [The fearless
youngest members and the polite leader]
First...
Hang on. Someone's there.
I think she's very tall.
Excuse me.
[Suddenly rushes over]
- Sorry.
- Excuse us for a minute.
[Sorry for intruding on
your time of solitude]
Sorry.
Thank you.
[Polite Team A saying thank you]
See you later.
- Sorry.
- Bye.
[Not scared]
Give me that.
[Team A calmly got 2 free tickets]
[Meanwhile, they're still here...]
Come on out. Or please go away.
[They take a different route]
I don't want to go there.
Here it is!
[Frightened out of their wits]
Go away.
They're very fast.
[Looking around]
- Where's Yoongi?
- Ack!
[SUGA's here]
You scared me! Don't do that!
Yoongi, where are you?
[SUGA's here, crawling on the floor]
Yoongi!
- Yoongi!
- Here!
[Mimicking a zombie]
Where?
[Team C found the room with their mission]
- C.
- C?
- We're Team C.
- Right.
[Is this the right way?]
[Ahhh!]
[Oh, come on]
You scared me.
How can we go past it?
Let's go.
[Peep]
Jimin.
[Jimin put his fear behind
and got the hint]
Let's check it out.
Hurry up.
[Team C found 2 envelopes]
- Where are the 5 tickets?
- Tickets?
I don't know but let's go.
[Team A checks the hint Jung Kook found]
Here it is.
I know what it means.
This is a swipe hint.
[Team A got a swipe hint needed
for all three teams to escape]
Yeah, you know what it is, right?
[Hint]
The most important thing is blood type.
Hang on. Don't we need to enter something?
[Team A goes to carry out a mission
with the hint they obtained]
[Surprised]
Sorry.
What should we do?
[He found something]
What's that box with the skull?
[Box containing a skull]
What's that?
That's a box.
Hang on.
[Jung Kook and V are not scared
of zombies any more]
[Except one person who is still scared]
Hang on.
[Reads it repeatedly]
The most important thing is blood type.
[Trying hard]
I don't think we can't solve this yet.
But this is something we need to solve.
[Is RM finally overcoming his fear?]
Blood type is the most important...
Got it. Come here.
[But he asks Jung Kook to do it instead]
Look. There's a QR code.
[Each picture has a QR code]
[Rummaging]
[Humming]
[RM giving directions outside]
Scan the QR code. There you go.
Dear my Brad. I miss you more today.
There's a letter in the box.
[Reading it the 3rd time]
Blood type is the most important.
[Holding tight]
I think it's a hint.
[RM, come here]
Where did you find it, Taehyung?
That one? Here.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Hang on.
[Finally got it]
The daughter!
[Realized the QR codes
and drawings are related]
Right, she grew up like this.
[Meanwhile, how are the other teams doing?]
Aren't we supposed to go straight?
[Team B hasn't even found the mission yet]
Let's run.
[Dash]
[Frightened]
[Got surprised several times by the camera]
Who's there?
[I know what you're up to]
Who's there? You can go first.
[Who?]
We need to catch it.
[Hobi's scream can be heard everywhere]
There it is!
What's wrong?
[Team B found a swipe hint]
I got one!
[But they can't decipher the hint]
- What's this?
- Go to no.1.
No, this is the pattern.
No.1... What should we do?
It's so...
What's this place?
[Boo!]
[Huddled]
- Why?
- Where are we?
[Pushing each other to go first]
I can't go.
[Team A is solving the quiz smoothly]
Here it is. This is her when she was born.
- She graduated from middle school.
- It's her graduation photo.
After this...
I think this is the last time
she walked on two legs, right?
[Moving to the side]
Why?
- It's related to the surgery records.
- Surgery records.
[Team A is getting closer to the answer]
It's related to the surgery records...
[Still fighting against zombies]
Is he standing still?
Why does he not move?
[Hobi screamed 10 times tonight]
Please.
[Hands clasped]
Please let us pass.
No? It's a dead end.
[Dead end?]
- But it says C.
- Does it?
[Careful]
[Boo!]
Oh, my...
[Embarrassed] [Checking anything]
Is there anything behind it?
[Two teams end up going back in fear]
- This is not the right place.
- Let's go.
[Trembling]
[Back in the same place]
[Making a fuss]
[Why is the director here...?]
This is crazy.
[Nobody cares about the zombie...]
- The daughter's surgery records.
- This is too difficult.
[Busy solving the puzzle]
It's in English. I don't understand.
[Great acting]
- Most important thing is her blood type.
- Blood type AB.
[Concentrating]
But I don't know.
Surgery records...
[Jung Kook found another room]
I can't solve this.
Shall we move on, guys?
[Moving on to the next hint]
- Steel bars.
- Should we bring this?
Let's take it.
Where are the steel bars?
[Team C going back to
find the mission place]
[Like practicing high pitch songs]
This way!
[Wandering after finding the mission place]
- This is the right place.
- Are you sure?
Right. We need to go inside.
This is the one. That's scary.
[Boo!]
- Seriously.
- Are you sure?
[That's not the one... Jimin...]
It's locked.
There's a key.
[Team C finally found the quiz]
[There's a hint on the back of the ID card]
[Find out how to go into the vent
in the night duty room]
- Where's the night duty room?
- Night duty room.
Did you take anything
from the night duty room?
[Rummaging]
- Two items.
- Look.
The red one and the blank one.
[Found hints they don't understand]
The pattern codes...
Should we go inside?
There might be something.
[Ahhh!]
[Repeatedly surprised by the same zombie]
That scared me.
[Scared] [We need to get in there...]
How can we go inside? The zombie is in it.
There are 8 pattern code cards.
[Jimin and j-hope check the hint properly]
Do we have to open them all?
[Find 4 other cards]
[Confused] [Ridge? Road?]
"There's a road on the opposite
side of the ridge."
I don't get it. I guess I brought
the hint that was meant for other teams.
[Confused since they didn't read the puzzle
and just took any hints they could find]
- Really?
- Yeah.
There's a zombie right next to us.
[Negotiating with the zombie]
We've met so many times. You know me.
[Boo!]
[Team B wins against the zombie
and enters the room]
[Searching through]
Should we put on a costume?
Right, to be like one of the zombies.
[Why aren't you finding the hint?]
I found one! I got one!
[It's for fun...]
It's empty! Stop doing this!
[Covering up]
We tried so hard only to find an empty one.
[Team A arrived at
the next stage, steel bars]
Is this the right place?
DNA.
"No matching data"?
Hang on.
- The order.
- The order?
I guess this is right.
DNA, the order?
What does it mean?
Let's go back there.
[Team A leaves the steel bars empty-handed]
Let's go back.
- This is driving me crazy.
- What's this and what's that?
This is B! We're at the wrong place.
[They were struggling at team B's place]
- It's B.
- Hang on.
[Frightened]
Whoa
[Scared]
- Please! It's so scary!
- Let's go.
[Picking up the traces Jimin left behind]
No?
Ahhh!
[It's about time you got used to it...]
Come here.
There's no hint.
There's nothing.
Hey, hurry up!
Found anything?
[Rummaging]
There's no hint.
[Hobi wants to get out of here]
Here it comes.
Did you find a pattern code?
I don't know what we have to do.
If zombies were real, I'll cry.
There's nothing.
[Can't find the hint
that's right under their nose...]
I think we're in the wrong place.
No, this is the right place. I'm sure.
[Ran away in fear]
Weren't we supposed to do something here?
[The cards are mixed up]
We don't know what to do because
the cards are mixed up.
[3, 2, 1]
- I don't think so.
- Triple A.
Ack!
[Save Hobi]
That was scary...
[Jin & SUGA disguised as zombies
instead of solving the mission]
I think they've noticed us.
[Bad attempt at trying to mimic zombies]
[What are they doing?]
That's not the one.
We...
Hang on. Do you have the tickets?
They're with you.
[Lost the tickets during the makeover]
No? Don't play jokes on me.
[They lost all the tickets]
I guess we left them there.
[Dumb and dumber]
Where are they?
No way.
[Boo! Boo!]
We lost all the tickets.
[Boo]
[Team B returned to find the tickets]
Hey.
[Luckily found the tickets right away]
I found them.
[Great acting]
- Great acting! You're a good actor.
- Method acting.
Method actor.
We're in the wrong place. B?
[These three don't care]
This is not our place.
What are you doing?
- Where is it?
- Whoa!
[Boo]
[Team B approached the steel bars
that team A already dug through]
Whoa.
What's the password?
What's that?
Password.
[Serious]
- Should we climb over it?
- Can we?
[Not knowing that team A took the hint]
Based on my experience in escape rooms,
there must be a hint here somewhere.
[Complaining]
But they ruined this place.
[Found the hint that team A tore off]
DNA. I see.
[Well experienced with escape rooms]
A, B, C, D, 1, 2, 3, 4, A, B, C, D, E, F...
[However, he's not good at counting]
13, A. 43. 1.
4131.
Sorry.
[Team B almost got it
but counted N instead of M]
[Disappointed]
[Team A and C got confused
because the hints were mixed up]
Seriously...
Spade, heart, diamond...
Hey, this is our room.
[Confused]
You're on course 4?
- These are all jumbled up.
- Are you on B?
[Discussing]
We need to find the password to the room.
[Jung Kook pressed the tablet carelessly]
But we don't know what to do.
[So Team A went to Team B & C's course]
We don't know what to do.
This is confusing.
Members, gather up at the center please.
The courses are mixed.
[Three teams couldn't solve the mission]
We couldn't solve the mission.
- We failed.
- We messed up.
[Disappointed]
We went to the wrong place.
We had to stay on course.
[Envy]
- We got one.
- You did? We found nothing.
[Mimicking zombies?]
They were all blank.
[Where did you get that, Jin?]
We couldn't even enter B.
[They should've found hints by
reading the map and puzzle]
[But were in a hurry to find free tickets]
- Right.
- We weren't careful.
[And hints for ARMY]
We just wanted to find more free tickets.
We entered any room
and got the hints mixed up.
[All teams failed the secret mission!]
[They will escape through
the laser stage instead]
[Why are you cherishing the skull?]
We need to solve the pattern.
Should we solve the pattern?
[V starts solving it right away]
Can we go in now?
[Careful]
What's this?
[Failed 5 seconds after he started]
[V took care of the free tickets]
Let me go. I'm an expert.
- Let's go.
- It's back on.
Jimin will go through.
[Jimin, the escape room expert]
Beware of the lasers.
[Moving between the rays]
- Jimin!
He's amazing.
[Looking up]
You need to go over it.
- For fun.
- He's so good at this.
[Jimin, you're doing great!]
- Jimin.
- Jimin!
[He just needs to go through the last one]
[Beep!]
[Too bad]
[Disappointed]
Almost there.
- My turn!
- Jung Kook, go!
Look at Jung Kook.
[Golden Maknae Jung Kook's turn!]
- You can start now.
- There he goes.
Can I just run and jump?
[The members hum him a tune]
I'll just go under the laser rays.
[I will crawl when others go over it]
Good!
[Way to go!]
[Jung Kook succeeded with crawling strategy!]
Press the button.
Keep pressing it.
[Laser pattern changed
when he pressed the button]
It's easy to go through now.
Should we go through together?
[Rush]
- Let's go one by one, slowly.
- Come here.
No, no.
We made it.
[BTS walks out sadly
after failing the secret mission]
Is this the end?
That was too hard.
Too difficult.
[Spitting facts]
[Made it out without any big feats]
We made it out anyway...
[Picked up some random props]
I got a lot of items.
Did anyone get anything?
I think we found the most free tickets.
[Envious]
Really?
[Team B focused on getting free tickets]
1, 2, 3, 4 tickets.
[Four tickets!]
I guess this is the biggest number.
[Sorry]
Amazing. Nothing.
- Really?
- You guys messed up with the hints!
[Just had to find the entrance to a vent]
We had to crack the password.
[Team A's result]
We found 1, 2, 3, 4...
[5 free tickets]
- 5 tickets.
- More than team B's.
[Disappointed]
We wanted to find more
but we were in a hurry.
- Is this it?
- We found nothing.
We only got 9 tickets?
[RUN BTS: BTS vs Zombies]
Lastly, you can play freeze tag
with the zombies
[Last round: Freeze tag with zombies]
to get more hidden free tickets.
- I see.
- Let's go.
[Still in their zombie costumes]
[Disappointed to have found no tickets]
1, 2, 3. BTS, zombies!
[Let's go take down the zombies
and find more free tickets!]
This zombie sounds so weak.
It keeps saying "ehh..."
The last game is freeze tag with zombies.
[RUN BTS: BTS vs Zombies Round 3]
[Play freeze tag with the zombies
and find free tickets hidden around]
[The members can "freeze"
when a zombie approaches]
[But they can't move until another member
attaches an "Unfreeze" sticker]
[Members who attached "Unfreeze"
stickers to other members]
[will get free tickets according to
the number of "Unfreeze" stickers]
Please take these.
[A pouch with "Unfreeze" stickers]
Jung Kook, you be the healer
since you're a fast runner.
We should divide our roles
like a role-playing game.
[Distributing stickers]
- Your name is on it.
- RM.
- Here they come.
- Whoa.
[Surprising visual]
We didn't start yet.
[Nervous]
It's so scary when they start acting.
- Oh, my. With them again...
- They're getting ready.
- Oh, my.
- They're great actors.
[Still scared]
Let's not do this again.
[Chant]
Since we're playing as a group,
let's shout out our chant,
"Bangtan, Bangtan, Bang Bangtan"
Let's do this.
Let's run right after the chant.
[Led by the leader]
- Bang Bangtan
- Bangtan!
[Dash]
[The name that can even make SUGA run]
[Zombie]
[This one?]
No.
[Is it here?]
[Hurried]
Where is it?
[Today's ace, Jin]
[Found one free ticket]
[Looking around]
[Duck] [Dash]
Whoa!
[You got me]
Where should I stand?
[Foreign zombie
who understands Korean well]
1... How should I count?
[Frightened]
[Golden Maknae]
[Jung Kook is busy tagging other members]
Unfreeze.
[Gasping]
[SUGA was doing his best to avoid zombies]
Why are you here! Get out of my way!
[Knockdown]
Zombie...
[Hey, I'm here!]
[Careful]
[RM found one free ticket]
[Escaping]
[That was close]
[This one is working so hard today]
Help me, Yoongi!
[Unfreezes a member on the same team]
[Who freezes again shortly after]
Freeze! Oh, my.
[Hehe]
Can you turn off the light?
[V gave up on appearing on camera
to find more free tickets for ARMY]
- Oh, no.
- Why are you bringing them my way?
[Today's extreme job, camera directors...]
Why are they bringing zombies?
[Anything here?]
Nothing.
[There it is!]
Don't come near.
Don't!
Freeze. Freeze.
Please go away. I said freeze.
[Throw]
It's a blank!
[Looking around]
I can't find any envelopes.
There's nothing. Why did you bring them?
It's a dead end!
I found no envelopes.
[Got caught]
I can't find any.
[Why can't you find any, RM?]
Here it is.
- I searched through this place.
- I got one.
I couldn't find any.
Wait a minute.
[The zombie just passed by]
[Standing alone]
[I got you!]
Unfreeze! Now I got caught.
[Glad to see you]
Unfreeze!
[Standing still]
[Pretending as if he said freeze]
[You can't fool me]
[Ha ha]
[Lonely]
Somebody needs to unfreeze me.
[Jimin found an envelope while frozen]
It's within my reach.
[Catching a glimpse]
[Walking around]
Nothing. Oh, it has one.
[Excited]
A lot of tickets. So happy.
I'll rescue Jimin!
[Jin is going to unfreeze Jimin
who is excited to find free tickets]
[Making a fuss]
[Oh, great Jin]
Okay!
[He's just over there]
[Jimin, I'm coming to unfreeze you]
[Fake]
[Dash]
Here, here.
[BTS is trying their best
to find free tickets for ARMY]
We can't beat them.
They're so fast.
[Deep insight]
If zombies really appeared,
humans would be extinct.
Please stand in the opening formation.
Good. Jin.
[Hi, my name is Jin]
It's me. Jin sticker.
Worldwide handsome.
- How many did you get?
- One envelope had 3 tickets.
[Showing off]
Jimin, I unfroze you at the perfect timing.
[Emotionless] [Yes, you're the best]
- It was awesome.
- The perfect timing.
- I found the perfect timing.
- I unfroze two members.
I found the perfect timing.
BTS vs Zombies game at Everland.
[So sure]
- If there are zombies, humans will be extinct.
- Right.
[After a battle with the zombies]
It was our complete defeat.
[BTS came to believe humans can't beat zombies]
- Zombies should not be real.
- Give us weapons.
Zombies are perfectly prepared.
[No, you can't]
I thought it would be a fight with zombies.
[Shaking his head]
- No.
- But you can freeze in front of them.
I couldn't move.
[The members were all frozen
in front of the zombies]
[Time to find out how many
tickets they found]
Should we count the number of tickets?
Starting from Hobi.
[j-hope couldn't overcome his fears]
I got one.
And the other was a blank.
- I am so happy.
- Amazing.
[So happy]
I can give free tickets to ARMY.
[Jimin got a jackpot from one box]
- I got 3.
- 3 tickets.
Taehyung. V.
[V focused on running and got 0]
- I found... Sorry.
- What did you do?
[Nothing to say]
Did you keep running?
- I kept running.
- Just running?
[Sorry]
I guess so.
[RM found tickets quietly]
I got 2.
[Proud]
I unfroze others a lot.
- As you can see your back...
- You unfroze Hobi, too.
[SUGA's stickers
to unfreeze others]
I unfroze so many times...
- Healer.
- Hang on.
[Doubtful]
SUGA has never unfrozen me.
I did several times.
Didn't you attach it secretly?
[Suspicious]
He's cheating.
["Unfreeze" stickers are included
in the number of free tickets to get]
[Sensitive BTS]
I was never unfrozen by SUGA.
- Replay it.
- See? I unfroze him.
OK. How many, Jung Kook?
[Jung Kook who ran around got 0]
- Nothing.
- 0 for Jung Kook.
[Today's MVP Jin got 6 tickets]
I found 6 free tickets.
- Really? 6 tickets?
- I did my best.
6 free tickets! Amazing.
- I ran here and there. Look at my face.
All sweaty. - Really. - Great.
- We've got 12 tickets.
- A sticker for your good work.
Great!
It's time to announce
[How many tickets did BTS get for ARMY?]
the final number of free tickets.
[Final score - Secret mission]
[Team A - 5, Team B - 4,
Team C - 0]
[Freeze tag with zombies]
[RM - 3, Jimin - 4]
[SUGA - 2, V - 2]
[Jin - 8, Jung Kook - 3, j-hope - 3]
[In total, BTS got 34 free tickets
to Everland!]
[Who is the MVP for BTS vs Zombies?]
- The MVP is...
- Jin.
[Jin ran until his clothes
were soaked in sweat]
It's Jin.
- You were so cool tonight.
- Kim Seokjin played a big role.
[Jin, respect]
- Here's a sticker for you.
- You were amazing.
[Self-praise]
- Today is Kim Seokjin's day.
- You were amazing.
- Give him a sticker.
- Stick them on his back.
[Attaching]
He did a great job.
Let's give him stickers.
- You can hold these.
- Thank you, free tickets.
- We found a lot.
- Right, we did.
[Let's add 6 tickets to make 40.]
6 members excluding Jin will
pay for 6 more tickets ourselves.
[Others except Jin add 6 to make 40]
6 members excluding Jin.
[We will announce how the lucky fans who
will get the tickets will be picked later]
[Halloween special drink for Jin]
[Eyeball-ade]
Can we turn a zombie into a human?
[Saying-whatever-party]
It's MP.
- Recovering juice?
- I guess it's a potion.
[Sniff]
It's a cure-all.
[It tastes great]
- He smelled before drinking.
- It's almost melted.
So, the rest of us will pay for 6 tickets.
[At Everland, the world of dream and fantasy]
With cool and beautiful zombies,
[RUN BTS with zombies!]
we enjoyed a horror maze in Everland.
[34 free tickets for ARMY]
We are glad that we can give
[(+members' donation of 6 tickets)]
34 tickets for ARMY. Thank you.
Everybody say, boo!
[See you later]
See you next week!
It's so scary.