[RUN BTS: King of Games]
[(-TS)]
- R. U. N.
- B...
My voice is gone.
RUN BTS!
[Where are they?]
Where are we now?
- This is...
- Nonhyun-dong.
[PC cafe?]
I can see computers. Isn't it a PC cafe?
- It's a PC studio.
- It's not a PC cafe. It's a PC studio.
[What will they do here?]
PC studio?
It's my first time hearing it too.
[Game expert 1]
You've seen some game broadcasts on TV.
[Hopes up]
Are we playing computer games?
[Today's RUN BTS!
BTS will show off their gaming skills]
[2 teams will play Crazy Arcade,
Bubble Fighter and Kartrider]
[The losing team will face a penalty
and the winning team will enjoy snacks]
[SUGA is the MC]
Let me be today's MC because
I'm really bad at playing games.
- Really?
- RM was supposed to be the MC.
[Games are too hard for me]
I tried it just now but I can't do it.
[RM likes games]
- I'll play. I like games.
- So I'll be the MC.
[SUGA's smooth MC skills]
I won't engage in
how to divide teams.
[Let's start playing games already!]
Because from what I've seen,
you all have similar gaming skills.
I think we can divide teams
on the PC we logged in.
[Dividing teams]
- Well, first...
- We logged in just now.
- There are 3 seats on each side.
- V, me and j-hope.
[Jin, Jimin and Jung Kook]
And the rest are on another team.
- Does it strike a balance?
- I don't know.
[Putting his arms around their shoulders]
- I think we won.
- Balance...
[A match between Jung Kook and V?]
Except for Jung Kook and V,
- it's hard to say they can play games.
- I think the teams are well-balanced.
I think so, too.
Can we decide teams like this?
[Teams are divided by the order of log-in]
- I guess so.
- All right.
[Staring at each other for nothing]
Let's have a stare-off.
1, 2, 3.
[Joking]
Oh! Your breath smells.
The one who says
stuff like that first wins.
[SUGA's advice]
You should've said it first!
- Right, so I said it first.
- I lost.
Let's start playing games.
What games will we play?
First game is Crazy Arcade.
- Crazy Arcade.
- The classic game!
[Crazy Arcade: Lock other players in
water bubbles and burst them first to win]
[Team match: Crazy Arcade!
Win 2 out of 3 rounds first to win]
[The characters and the map
will be randomly selected]
[Before their debut on January 1, 2013]
In January 2013,
[They played this game together]
- we played it together
- We did.
- It was January 1 in 2013.
- Yoongi wasn't there.
[V is excited to talk about games]
- Because I don't play games.
- We used to say we were at a mine
if someone called us while gaming.
- No, I was at my parents'.
- You were not in Seoul.
- He was in another region.
- Are you confident in Crazy Arcade?
[Not confident] [Enthusiastic]
I'm not. But I'll do my best.
[Enthusiastic]
- I think we can win.
- This game is back in 4 and a half years.
- I will...
- I'm worried too.
[Good]
- I'll help you.
- Let's go!
[Staring]
Let's start right now.
[Nice enough to play along with j-hope]
You can just explain what happens.
[Prize for the winning team]
The winning team can choose
a late night snack.
[I love it] [I'll have Jokbal]
- Late night snack!
- Jokbal is the best.
[Already excited about playing games]
Let's have fish cake.
[SUGA's opinion]
There's a lot of good food in Nonhyun-dong.
The losing team will face a penalty.
[These two are excited about playing games]
Each team will decide a penalty.
[Chatter]
Go to the food alley wearing these.
[Saying anything that comes to mind]
What about going home in this?
[Loud]
- And say hi to everyone that passes by.
- You know it's raining outside.
"Hello, I'm V of BTS".
Is there anything that we
can do with a computer?
[Whispering]
Completing Minesweeper.
[So confident]
- It's impossible.
- Minesweeper is easy.
[So proud]
- I'm good at that.
- Really? Then write it down.
Any suggested penalties?
Pick up after the winning team had snacks.
[Good idea]
That's great!
Cleaning up after we eat.
[V holding the cue card backwards]
[The two teams chose their penalties]
Done.
- What's yours?
- Something funny.
What's yours?
- What late night snack do you want?
- What do you want?
- Patbingsu
- Patbingsu!
[Great]
- I want to have something cool.
- Great idea!
[Jin is lauded as a genius]
- He's a genius.
- Patbingsu, amazing.
- That was a good one.
- Taehyung, write that down.
[Everyone is talking about
different subjects]
All right. Are you ready?
- Are you ready?
- We're ready!
Warm up your fingers.
[Everyone is stretching in earnest]
- Let's go.
- Then...
Let's go play Crazy Arcade!
[Great!]
It's been a while since I last played.
[Members are seated to play the game]
Are you ready?
Let's choose pink for our team color.
Then, let's choose blue for ours.
- No, we'll choose red.
- Is it an individual match?
[We've divided teams...]
No
[Con-SUGA-fused]
Here we go!
[Everyone, get ready]
- Ready?
- Get ready!
[Already looking like a game master]
- Everyone, ready.
- Go!
[Game starts!]
Let's start playing.
Where am I?
[Team Blue: Has a lot to say
about their characters]
I don't know his name.
[Team Pink: Serious and concentrating]
- Guys.
- They're breaking blocks.
- I don't know how to play this...
- That's my item. Jung Kook, don't take it.
[SUGA (25): Game commentator
who knows nothing about the game]
What does the potion do?
[Fully concentrated]
[Jin died while answering] [Sad]
- Out. Who is that?
- V killed me!
[Smiling] [RM raps while gaming]
Jin's out.
Oh, he's saved.
V is good at this.
Kill him! I killed V!
[Everyone is so focused] [Disappointed V]
- V is dead.
- Dead?
- Jung Kook, kill RM.
- What's that ghost?
- It's just a ghost.
- Is it?
V is so fast.
[All got blocked inside water balloons]
- So close!
- Love shot!
[Game expert's jargon]
Love shot! It's a love shot!
[Excited]
This is a tie.
[The first round ended with a tie]
[Disappointed]
We got a love shot.
[Game layman]
- Do you call it a love shot?
- It's our first tie.
[Jin helps him understand]
A love shot is when two are hit
at the same time.
- Love shot.
[SUGA, the game commentator
who knows nothing]
I'm the commentator but I'm clueless.
[Request from V who played this game before]
Can you change it to
the popularity random mode?
OK, the popularity random mode.
[2nd round, start!]
Here we go.
[So confident]
We'll win this time. Don't worry.
Hey, I got a hidden item.
[Feeling so happy about a hidden item]
- It's Pirate Hook.
- It's Hook.
[Hidden? Hook?]
Who is Pirate Hook? What's that?
[So concentrating]
- There are several items and options.
- Hook...
[What's the hook for? Can't understand]
- Hook is so annoying.
- How do you play this?
[RM and Jimin are both out]
[Disappointed]
That makes it 2-2.
[Concentrating]
He got caught!
[Jin is locked in a water balloon]
- He got caught!
- There you go!
[Proud]
Taehyung is good.
[Concentrating]
[SUGA is amazed by V's skills]
V's great play!
[Amazed 2]
- V's amazing.
- I could have saved it.
[Amazed 3]
Taehyung is awesome.
[Concentrating]
[Not being swayed by any compliments]
[Happy and sad]
[Peace sign to celebrate]
- He's great.
- Why couldn't I use the item?
[So happy]
I read this from the web.
"Why couldn't I use the item?"
actually means
"I used the item but it didn't work."
[Confused with the keys]
- He tried to use it...
- I had to press Ctrl.
- I thought it was 1.
- So, we lost a round.
Is it 1-0 now?
[Current score: Round one was a tie!
RM, V, j-hope 1-0 Jung Kook, Jimin, Jin]
[Actually the 3rd round]
We just began the 2nd round.
[Special quest: Protect V]
We need to protect Taehyung, guys.
[Don't take my item]
j-hope, you're trying to take my item...
Oh, that was close.
[What's going on?]
[SUGA is full of questions today]
How did you kick the water balloons?
[Immersed in the game]
OK!
- You missed it.
- How come you have 2 needles?
[Silent master]
- Did you not remove your item?
- It's not a needle. I saved him.
I saved him.
[Oh?]
- Bad players always...
- Please help!
[Making a fuss]
- Help!
- You're saved!
[Locked again in a water balloon]
[Let's go!]
Jimin, down there!
[No!]
Jimin!
[I can't believe this...]
It's a clear victory of Team Pink.
My character is dead! Why?
[Team Pink gained confidence] [So confident]
This is a perfect victory.
You guys are no match for us.
[Cut us some slack]
- Can this be a practice round?
- No
[RM, j-hope, V]
In the first game, Crazy Arcade,
[Victorious pink]
Team Pink won.
This is how you play a game.
[I'm the game master]
- I told you, I'm a game master.
- Crazy Arcade isn't easy.
- The 2nd game is Bubble Fighter.
- Bubble Fighter!
Please explain the game, Bubble Fighter.
[Bubble Fighter! Use water guns to attack
other players and burst them locked in bubbles]
[Team match: Bubble Fighter
Win 2 out of 3 rounds to win]
[The characters and the map
will be randomly selected]
It's our first time playing this.
[Game expert RM]
This is a type of FPS.
It's the FPS version of Crazy Arcade.
I've never played this but
it looks so cute and fun.
- The characters are so cute.
- I want to try.
[Cute]
- Let's download it back home.
- Did you open a room?
[The members are preparing to play]
Wait, I'll open one.
- Ready.
- Are you all ready?
[Ready to play, I'm sniper Hope]
- Guys.
- One Sniper, one Rifleman.
[Nice enough to play along with j-hope]
- Who is your team's sniper?
- Let's begin.
Let's go!
[Team Blue: RM, j-hope, V
vs Team Red: Jin, Jimin, Jung Kook]
This seems fun.
[Confused as he hasn't played before]
What's the button to explode?
[Game, start!]
- Just come closer and shoot.
- Approach it and shoot.
Oh, this is going to be exciting.
[He's about to go into the screen]
[Disappointed]
It's harder to play a sniper.
[Concentrating]
It's a FPS game but not cruel.
Help, help, help!
[Shout for help]
- Help me! Behind you!
- Behind. Help me!
Oh, it's here. Help me!
[Desperately running to survive]
- Behind! Help.
- Where are you?
[What a mess]
[It's so fun]
Jimin, what are you doing?
[I think you got confused]
This is a team match.
Bang.
[Concentrating with his mouth open]
Jung Kook's getting better by the minute.
Keep running. Very good!
[Team Red (Jin, Jimin, Jung Kook)
has a knack for this game]
- They're doing well.
- Right, they're playing well.
[Didn't even know how to load]
- How can I load the gun?
- Press R.
[His off-screen way of talking pops up]
You didn't know that?
[Embarrassed]
That's why I couldn't shoot.
Here we go!
Run, go forward!
Help!
[So much fun]
OK.
- It's hard to play sniper.
- I need to play the rifleman.
We're ahead by a lot.
[Continuous requests for help]
- Help!
- I'm dead.
[Interim score]
11-8.
[Everyone keeps saying the same thing]
- Save me.
- We're all dead.
I think you can turn the tables!
[15-14, Team Blue (RM, j-hope, V)
is rapidly catching up]
10 seconds left.
[Finally, SUGA starts giving commentary...]
He got two as soon as he respawned.
[Survive! This round is important]
No more dying this time.
- I got one!
- Cover me!
[Staring]
Behind you? OK.
Team Red won by 1 point!
Wow!
[Both teams understood how to play]
- I know how to play now.
- I got it now.
- We can win.
- 14-15.
[Explaining the rules]
You can escape even
if you're locked in a bubble.
Team Red won the first round.
[Who am I talking to?]
[So excited] [Fun]
This is fun!
[Round 2: What's the new map?]
- What's this map?
- What is this?
We need to set a plan.
- Bang!
- I got shot.
[In a hurry] [Communication with one word]
Help! Help!
- I saved you.
- Jimin, help me!
[Both teams are doing well so far]
OK.
[Jung Kook is locked in a bubble]
- Behind you. - Where? - Behind, hurry!
[But the bubble bursts finally]
[Team Blue is winning]
Team Blue scored first.
[Staring so fiercely]
Nice, I killed him.
- I died trying to save JK.
- Loading.
Back!
[Two rappers are rapping]
- Go back!
[Will Team Blue win as SUGA said?]
I have a hunch that Team Blue will win.
[Watch out]
You better go out.
[Serious]
I can't shoot.
[Kook locked Hope] [A close match]
I got one.
- Go inside.
- We got them all.
[The match became a tie again]
- We got caught.
- I caught them all.
Let's run!
- Where are you going?
- Go in there!
Jin is good at this.
[Worried]
I think we will lose.
[I'm today's MVP]
I'm the MVP.
Please save me.
I'm here.
[Came back to life]
20 seconds left.
- Help me.
- Help!
Behind you!
[Help]
Taehyung, help me!
[Will Team Red win?]
Will Team Red win?
- No way. I need to use a rifle.
- Watch out!
[Concentrating] [Countdown]
6 seconds.
5, 4,
- One more time.
- 3, 2...
[So desperate]
- One more time, please! Who will save me?
- 1 second.
[Time over]
OK!
[Round 2: Team Red won]
I covered for the sniper so well.
[Disappointed]
We lost.
[So proud] [Way to go]
I did an amazing job.
- Team Red won two rounds first...
- Awesome!
Team Red won the 2nd game.
Class E. Who's the player?
[Player with class E]
- It's me. - Class E.
He's a Class E player.
- Let's move on to the last game.
- What's that?
[Kartrider]
It's Kartrider.
[Kartrider! A racing game where
players are ranked by order of arrival]
[Team match Kartrider!
Win 2 out of 3 rounds to win]
[Excited]
I've played this game a lot.
[A great driver at arcades]
Kartrider!
[Serious] [Making a fuss]
Kartrider.
Today's last game is Kartrider.
Is there anyone good at playing?
[Confession]
I'm not a good player.
[RM selected V as the best player]
Taehyung is good at this.
[Proud]
Really?
[I'm a speedy driver]
I'm good at the speed match on Kartrider.
All right. Let's play an item match
for the 1st round.
Then, a speed match for the 2nd round.
[Love it]
Great.
The last one is the item match again.
[Charismatic SUGA]
- Let's play a random match for the 3rd.
- OK.
- You can't randomize the match type.
- There's no random mode.
[We like the item match]
Let's play the item match.
[MC's authority: up to SUGA's choice]
I'll choose the one that looks more fun.
[What you like is what I like]
[SUGA says item matches are based on luck]
Because item matches aren't
determined by skills.
You need to leave it to luck.
[Nervous]
Am I right?
[Smiling]
[Playful V]
V just said "Yoongi talks too much"
in the chat room.
[SUGA talks too much]
Let's see who is the best rider.
Let's start.
[Displeased]
- What's that tone?
- Get ready.
[What are you doing?]
Please get ready.
- What's with that childish tone?
- Get ready.
[Press F5 and get ready to start!]
- Press F5 and start.
- Let's start.
[Serious]
Let's go!
[First round start]
The desert. I think I've seen this map.
[Legendary map]
This map is really...
[Anyone who played Kartrider knows this]
All you need to do is keep running.
[j-hope got off to a good start] [Excited]
j-hope!
[Game newbie]
If you press harder, will it start faster?
[Hope and V are 1st and 2nd runners]
Banana.
[Stepping on the banana]
He stepped on the banana.
[Team Red is concentrating]
He got shot.
Water balloon, V!
[Sad] [Jin shot V with a water balloon]
He got shot by a water balloon!
[j-hope is the first runner]
Who's the first runner?
[Locked in the spaceship]
I locked him.
[A totally unpredictable race]
What's that in my way?
It's a traffic accident.
[Hehe]
Can I fill the booster?
[Aiming for no.1] [Will Jin turn the tables?]
- j-hope, I'll catch up with you.
- He overtook him!
[No way]
[Disappointed]
A bomb!
I'm the worst, as expected.
[Jimin and j-hope are good at this]
j-hope's doing the best.
[j-hope crashed into V]
Good.
You better call the insurance agent.
[Team Red is leading thanks to the accident]
Good. No.1 and 2 are our team members.
[Complaining]
- Who's no.1?
- I'm last place.
The first one is Jimin.
[What?]
Jimin was leading but got abducted.
[Talking so fast]
j-hope used a booster.
- j-hope is the fastest runner.
- I'm the fastest.
[Warning: You and I are on the same team]
Jimin, don't throw bananas like that.
[Sigh] [Jimin was shot by a missile]
He got shot!
[#Missile_Runner up_Successful]
No.2 is overtaking no.1, j-hope.
[I hate the missile]
That missile got me so behind.
[I will win!]
[j-hope is speeding up]
[Jin lost the no.1 spot due to the missile]
[Way to go, my team!]
j-hope!
[Wow!]
j-hope, all you have
to do is cross the line.
[Round 1: Team Blue won!]
[Jung Hoseok / 24  (Professional handler)
I'll always be no. 1]
[Disappointed]
We lost.
[Taetae is happy his team won]
[Team Blue won contrary to expectations]
Team Blue won!
It's amazing.
[Excited V] [I see]
Jimin, you couldn't finish the race?
[Ranking of round 1]
[j-hope, V, Jin, RM, Jung Kook, Jimin]
Jimin, I can't believe you retired.
[Jimin couldn't finish the race]
- Jimin, you couldn't finish it?
- Really?
[All I can do is smile]
Jimin!
[Match like a scene from a movie]
It was so dramatic.
[MC's commentary]
[Missile, the key to turning the tables]
Team Blue turned the tide with a missile.
[Emphasizing]
I shot behind them.
Jin's team needs to try harder.
[Discouraged]
They haven't gotten the hang of it yet.
As I said, round 2 is a speed match.
[Bring it on]
We need to play a speed match.
[I am so confident]
- Let's play that.
- Let's have the match.
Jung Kook and Jimin said they're
confident in the speed match.
[Self-proclaimed no.2 Team's speed king]
I'm our team's no.2 in the speed match.
Are we switching to the speed match?
[Current score 1:0]
Since everyone's ready, let's get started.
[Team Red showed confidence in the speed match]
- Speedy commentary, good.
- Jin's team said
[Serious]
- they're confident in the speed match.
- It's 1-0 now.
[Not confident]
I'm not good at this map.
[Speed, aim] [Shoot!]
- Do you know this map?
- j-hope!
[Serious mode] [V is dashing forward]
- V is so fast!
- V!
[Taken aback]
It's moving.
[Drift skills matter in the speed match]
[V's car bumped into the guardrail]
The speed match... Oh, he's going back.
[Amazed]
j-hope is amazing.
[j-hope is good at the speed match, too]
[Amazed] j-hope is good at this, too.
[Perfect cornering]
j-hope!
[About to become a fan of j-hope]
Did you see that drift?
[I'm the ace]
j-hope is the ace.
[Acknowledging]
What's this?
[Surprised] [Landscape mode]
What's this? My screen rotated.
[Dumbfounded]
Jung Kook, stop hitting me.
[Someone take notice...
Jimin's screen rotated...]
- j-hope is leading.
- Jimin...
- Why are you with me?
- My screen flipped 90 degrees.
[Acting cute]
Can we start over?
[No way]
- That's not going to happen.
- No way.
[Upset]
What's wrong with this?
[Struggling]
[I'll keep playing anyways]
[Teasing]
Jimin, are you behind me? Awesome.
I'll catch up with RM.
[Staring]
- I caught up with RM.
- Hang on.
[While Jimin is struggling with his monitor]
j-hope is moving to the lead!
j-hope!
- Did he turn the game?
- What!
[While j-hope came first]
- What?
-Am I the no.1?
[Oh, I guess we won]
Winner!
[It ain't over till it's over]
We won!
[It's not over till it's over]
We can win if we finish 2nd and 3rd.
What are you doing?
[Proud]
- I was going in reverse.
- Why?
[Reversing is the easiest
(Feat. No.1 player is my friend)]
I thought you would win.
[Speechless]
Jimin and RM haven't finished the race.
Look at Jimin's monitor.
[My back is hurting...]
I played like this.
[Team Blue wins!]
We won!
[Winners' relaxed attitude - Good game]
Everyone.
[Jimin has a lot to say]
[Asking for a rematch]
We need to play this round again.
I played like this.
[Jimin played with a flipped screen]
I'm not even kidding.
- Jimin, you should've done this.
- I played like this!
[I played like this!]
In this posture.
[Recognizing his passion]
He deserves a rematch.
[I'm sure I can win this time]
[They decided to play the
2nd round of speed match again]
The 2nd round, a speed match.
[Excited]
Everyone, ready?
[j-hope started a bit late]
He failed.
[Smooth cornering]
j-hope failed.
[Serious mode]
Nice move, pigtails.
[My team members]
Everyone's doing well.
Hang on. I'm going backward now.
[P-please don't go backward]
You can't go backward.
I'm sorry but you two
need to carry the team.
[He's so silly]
[Jung Kook stopped V]
- Don't do that.
- I blocked V's way!
[j-hope and V rapidly chase after]
[Wait for me!]
No!
[Amazed]
I think Hobi played this before.
[j-hope and Jung Kook are fighting to win]
- j-hope...
- He's a dark horse.
[Why me?]
He keeps blocking me!
[The world of competition is cold-blooded]
I don't know who it is.
[Commentary 1]
But Jung Kook is furious.
[Commentary 2]
Better apologize to Jung Kook back home.
Right, say sorry at the dorm.
[j-hope is defending well]
He's great at defense.
[Hobi is winning!]
You need to repent today.
I think j-hope got the hang of this map.
[Team Red is making a fuss]
- Oh no!
- We lost.
[No way]
We lost.
[Embarrassed]
- What's happening?
- No.1 and 2 are from Team Blue.
No. 3, 4, 5 are us.
[Cold-headed commentary] [Team Red is...]
They were full of confidence and nothing else.
[Admitting]
True, but confidence is the best.
Jimin, are you really in 5th place?
[Jung Kook is not doing well, either]
Hang on. I messed up.
[Cool-headed commentary]
Even if the monitor mishap didn't happen,
Jimin would have finished 5th.
[All I can do is laugh...]
[Disappointed]
Hobi blocked me!
[No.1! j-hope, do whatever you want]
You're an amazing player.
[Giving up]
Let's buy snacks.
- Let's play the last round for fun.
- Then, let's make it a bet.
[I want it]
Let's play the last round with carts.
Let's play an item match.
Speed or item? Please decide.
- Let's play an item match.
- It's up to you.
[Jimin wants to change his cart] [Busy changing his]
- Can I change my cart?
- Let's change it.
What's that fish?
[Jimin's new car: Fish car]
- Item, team match.
- What's this fish?
We've got a general.
You can see a general.
[Jung Kook plays a general]
[BTS are showing off their fancy carts]
- The items are so fancy.
- I haven't joined yet.
[Displeased]
Do you really want to do this?
[Then, I will...]
- Do you want to do this?
- I'll equip all items.
[BTS is carefully choosing carts]
- I changed my cart.
- Me, too.
[What's that?]
That character is in the air.
[RM's car is in the air]
- What's that?
- It's a broom. Awesome, huh?
[Surprised]
Is that a Rolls-Royce?
[V's car is huge]
A jeep car came up.
[Loves it]
[Games are all about items]
[The last game!]
Hang on. We need to make a bet.
[Serious]
What should we bet on?
If we lose, we will give a massage
to the winning team members.
[Not interested]
I'm not interested.
[Taken aback]
What's up with you?
[Kidding]
I'm a game commentator.
[Jimin's suggestion]
Since we're going straight home...
[What about a shower?] [Shakes his head]
No, we'd have to change our clothes.
[Interested]
- Let's do something fun...
- Shower? - What about that?
[Persuading]
We'll go straight home, anyways.
[Falling for Jimin's suggestion]
- Let's do that.
- 1 out of 3!
- OK, a water bottle shower.
- Go!
[Sounds fun]
Then, play individually.
[Sounds better]
- Individual match?
- The last one in will get the penalty.
- Let's do this!
- The loser of the individual match!
[Extra round: Kartrider - item match]
[The members will compete individually]
[The one who comes in last will
dance to "Blood, Sweat & Tears"
while getting drenched in water]
[The members are ready]
- Ready?
- Ready!
Let's go!
[So nervous]
[A lot of tension]
[Sweeping his hair up]
[Excited] [Excited to see the penalty]
Someone will get drenched!
[Anyone but me]
You just don't have to be last.
[Jin is sad he doesn't have a pet]
Hang on. I don't have a pet.
[Ignoring]
Let's start!
Here we go, everyone!
[Commentary]
They're running in
the 13th anniversary items.
[Jung Kook jumped into the water]
What? Death from a fall?
[Jin drowned after Jung Kook]
This is your fault, Jung Kook!
[Pied Piper Jung Kook, follow me]
Sorry, my bad.
[Hehe]
- j-hope is the last one.
- What's this?
[Surprised]
- What?
- What's this?
[Making a fuss] [Surprised]
- I'm the 6th.
No way!
[What's happening?]
- Oh, I messed up
- What's this?
- I'm in trouble.
- What?
[SUGA laughs and the members are perplexed]
- What!
- Oh no!
What's this?
[What's going on?]
[They’re struggling with a cleaning robot]
- Oh no.
- What's this?
- What?
[This map is the best!]
We should've chosen this map.
[Surprised]
- Hey!
- It's blocking us.
[Nervous RM]
- Hang on.
- What's this burger?
[The individual match is fiercer]
The individual match is funnier
than the team match.
Please, I don't want to be the last one!
[Apologizing to himself]
Sorry, I'm in 6th place.
[It's an individual match]
You only have yourself to be sorry to.
[RM apologizing to himself in the future]
Sorry to myself. I'm the 6th.
[j-hope and Jung Kook are
no.1 and no.2]
[Jung Kook pushed j-hope
into the water] [No!]
Jung Kook!
[So relaxed]
- He tricked me into this.
- Jeon Jung Kook!
j-hope and RM...
[Please, I don't want to get showered]
No way. I will not be the last one.
[j-hope the ace is currently in last place]
- j-hope is coming in the 6th.
- Here I go.
[RM plays Kartrider with his voice]
- Here I go!
- But it got you.
[Screaming from here and there]
No!
- Please!
- No!
[RM] [Cleaning robot time!]
It got you.
[You've entered the congested section]
[Jimin is left behind because of the robot]
- No! - Help!
[Screaming]
No!
[Bye, friend] [Rubbing salt in the wound]
- Jimin is the last one!
- No!
Please!
[Shouting]
What's this ghost?
I don't want to get drenched with water.
[Thank you]
I am so thankful to be the 4th.
[I did it! I'm no.1!]
I'm the winner!
[Like they're riding a roller coaster]
[j-hope came in second]
[What a mess]
[Please, the 3rd!]
No.3!
[No. 3, 4, 5- RM, V, Jung Kook
are excluded from the penalty]
[This is a desperate scream from
Jimin, who failed to finish the race]
Nooooo!
[Failed to finish the race]
[Festive mood]
I told you it would be you.
[Is it true? Am I the last one?]
At the end...
[Shouting]
What was that ghost?!
[I'm not a ghost... I'm the cleaning robot]
What was the ghost at the end?
[Jimin was no.1]
- What was that ghost?
- Jimin, you were no.1.
I tried to go this way but
[Reenacting the scene]
- it pressed me into the corner.
- All right.
[The one who proposed the penalty]
So, Jimin will get doused with water.
[His sad back]
[Jin, Jimin, Jung Kook choose
a penalty for the team match]
Please pick one.
[Oh]
- The losing team...
- Is this for the team match?
- We need to choose a penalty
for the team match.
- Let's pick any.
[What's Jimin's penalty?]
Jimin, please open it.
[Throwing it to the floor]
Pick up after the winners eat...
- Jimin has to clean up after getting drenched.
- Oh, poor thing.
[Teasing Jimin 1]
I will drop food everywhere.
[Teasing Jimin 2] [Can't hear you now]
Let's drop some food on the floor.
[Prize for the winning team, Patbingsu!]
That's mean. It looks so good.
[Approaching like being bewitched]
It looks so delicious!
[Penalty]
What music do you want?
[Right after the producer says]
"Blood, Sweat & Tears". A sexy one.
[Innocent]
Jimin, show us something sexy.
[Commentary]
How did you enjoy today's game?
Since we won
we'll enjoy this snack and
talk about how we felt.
Right, Jin's team always loses.
[Sad]
- Right.
- Jin's team always loses.
- That's our Kim Seokjin.
- I laugh so much on "RUN BTS."
[Satisfied]
- It's so much fun.
- There were a lot of funny situations.
- If you're on Jin's team, you will lose.
- Actually, it's been a while since
[Nom nom]
we played a game all together.
Although SUGA was the MC.
I think that's why it was fun.
[Jimin's inevitable penalty time]
Jimin, please say goodbye
and wrap this up with your penalty.
I really enjoyed today's game.
- I learned a great lesson.
- Don't get carried away.
[Today's lessons learned: Stay still]
Everyone, stay still.
[Teasing him]
If you had stayed quiet,
this penalty wouldn't exist.
[Do not open your mouth, by Jimin]
Let's not say anything.
That's the lesson I learned today.
[Please show the penalty]
Then, the last penalty.
[Jimin is posing]
- Music, cue.
- They won't even give me a bite.
[Oh?]
- Will you play music?
- Will you?
- What?
- Let's start again
[So nervous]
I'm so nervous right now.
[For him]
Play it out loud.
[We're looking forward to seeing
your penalty, Jimin]
[Blood, Sweat & Tears]
[Satisfied audience]
[Dancing machine]
- Oh, my.
- Jimin!
[1, 2, 1, 2]
[Laughing out loud]
You need to dance.
[Jimin, show us what you got!]
The highlight is coming soon!
[Dancing machine, I'm Jimin of BTS!]
So sexy!
[Jimin looks good even when he's drenched]
Be careful, it's slippery.
It looks cool.
Like a scene from a music video.
[I'm not cute anymore]
It's like a scene from a music video.
- Jimin.
- Oh.
[Pouts]
- Only Jimin can do this.
- Cool.
[Applause]
- I could have never pulled this off.
- Right.
See you next time on RUN BTS!
Bye!
[Pouts]
The water's in my eye.
[Team Red cleans up the studio]
- Enjoy.
- It was delicious.
[Jung Kook was eating patbingsu]
Why did you eat this?
- You're on the losing team.
- SUGA told me I could.
[Jim-derella]
I'm not on this team.
[The winners leave first]
Please clean this place up.
You can eat the leftovers.
- Make sure it's clean.
- Thanks.
[Taking a bite]
I'm good at cleaning.
[Pitiful]
[Working hard]
Delicious.
[See you in the next episode of RUN BTS!]
[RUN BTS: King of Games]