[Run BTS]
[Secret Agent]
Everyone has mold on them
[Run BTS begins with mold on everyone]
[Microphone fluff]
♪ You're my white mold ♪
Let's start
[Stopped]
Based on your outfits today
[Black suits]
can you guess what you'll be doing?
- Wedding? Guards?
- We look cool today
We look like we have to dance
to "Rainism"
[Rainism style]
Are we bodyguards today?
What are we doing?
[Nobody's listening] [Dancing]
Today's Run BTS theme is
[Full of feeling]
find the best secret agent team
[Real theme! Find the best
secret agent theme!]
- Secret agent?
- Finding a secret agent?
[That's what it was]
Something like Kingsman
[Timid gesture]
[Run BTS! BTS: Secret Agent]
[3 teams will go through 2 types of test]
[To find out who is the best secret agent
Who will be the most qualified?]
Let's decide teams
[Members start diving teams]
All right, just let luck decide
- What will you pick?
- Me? I'll pick this
1, 2, 3!
- B!
- C!
[What member combinations will occur?!]
- C
- I'm A!
[BTS Secret Agent Teams
Team A: Suga & V]
[Team B: RM & Jung Kook
Team C: Jin & j-hope & Jimin]
Please decide your team names
- Let's just be A
- A
[Team A]
Brain? Or BTS?
BTS from B
[Simple] [Team B - BTS]
Let's be Bangtan Boys, then
[Simple]
No, it'll be white mold
[Obsessed with white mold]
[Using their team name right away]
[Glaring]
It's too long, it's hard to add subtitles
[Thanks, RM]
Let's play rock paper scissors
and the winner will decide
[Suggesting rock-paper-scissors]
- The winner will decide
- Rock paper scissors!
- I've never won this game
[Eliminated right away]
- Our team name is Kim Seokjin
- Team Kim Seokjin
We've never won with that team name!
[Complaining]
Let's start
[Jimin has no choice]
Please explain the rules
What are we doing?
- We don't know the games yet
- That's right
[Curious] [Please tell us]
- Do we start now?
- I don't know
[What is today's mission?]
[1st test: Fantastic M]
[Pass a total of four mission stages
with the highest point!]
[400 is the perfect score! The closer
the score is to 400, the higher the level]
[Team Kim Seokjin has three members
so their lowest score will be added
to the other's]
- Let's go
- Good luck
[M-kit needed for the cellphone mission]
- The door is open
- Are you going in now?
[Team Kim Seokjin is up first]
- Are you ready?
- Please walk in looking cool
[Starting with cool poses as agents]
- Are you ready?
- Where's our guns?
- Gun?
- Where are they?
[Clumsy]
- Are you ready?
- Let's go
[Secret agents? Or silly agents?]
- What are they doing?
- Hey!
[Will they be fine...?]
Hurry up, guys!
[Mission START!]
Okay!
Hey! Phone!
[M-kit must be scanned before each STAGE]
[Huddled together]
[Stage 1: BTS Secret Agent]
[Shooting ability test: Team mission]
[If one hits a target, the target's
color will change into their gun's]
[A higher score is given if one
hits a target that matches their gun color]
Okay
[Sound effect created by themselves]
[Making shooting sounds]
What are we supposed to shoot?
[Confused]
[The two don't answer as they're
busy shooting targets]
[Finished understanding]
[Jimin looks like a real agent]
Aren't we supposed to move on?
[Not listening] [Focused]
Hey! We're a team
[Today's concept is agents, not children]
- It's an individual match
- No, we're a team!
[What team?] [Shooting from the back]
Let's move on
[Time limit]
Let's shoot until 50 seconds
[Can't give up]
Let's run inside after 50 seconds!
[Jin and j-hope rushing to shoot]
Hey, don't follow me
50 seconds is up!
[Jin trying to get one more]
- 1, 2, 3!
- Done! Let's go
[There's one over there]
Look at him. He was shooting
until the last second
[Last shot]
Hey! Hey! Hey!
[Internal conflict]
Don't do that!
- Put your gun down
- I won't shoot anymore
[Stop!]
- Put it down!
- Oh!
[Sounds like they caught a spy...]
- Scan it
- Okay
[Where are we?]
Let's scan first
[Gathered together]
[Stage 2: BTS Secret Agent]
[Ally recognition ability test: Individual match]
[Scan the M marks on the wall
with the M-kit to score a point]
[However, you lost a point if you
scan the enemy's V mark!]
V will reduce your points
so look carefully
[Be careful!]
It's kind of scary
[Let's go together]
Hurry up, it's not scary
[Whew]
Hey, don't scan the V
[A perfectly dark room!]
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'm scared
Please go with me
[Save j-hope]
- Nothing to be scared of
- I'm scared, go with me
[Ignores him] [The situation before...]
Where are you?
[Where are you? Can you hear me?]
I shot one
[Jimin found the M mark right away]
Where are you?
[Feeling around]
Oh, my point was reduced
[Jin scanned a V mark]
- I found two
- Where?
[Crawling around]
Please, don't
[Jimin approaching j-hope]
Why are you so scared?
[Startled]
- Sorry, my point got reduced again
- I did as well, it's okay
There's one more...
Will this reduce my point, too?
- It's a V
- If you touch it, you can tell
[Who are you talking to?]
- We can feel it by touching
- Right, I got one
[j-hope and Jimin now understood it]
[Touching]
What's this?
[Eyes widened] [Startled]
- Camera director...
- How much time is left?
- 20 seconds, let's go
- Let's go
[Must move to the next STAGE in 20 seconds]
- We need to move on
- Let's go
- What's that?
- Scan it, the last one
[Where are we?] [Let's just scan it!]
[Gathering around]
[Stage 3: BTS Secret Agent]
[Searching ability test: Individual match]
[There are portraits all around the STAGE!]
[Scan the ones shown on your M-kit
to get a point!]
- Okay
- This lady!
[Got it]
Let's split up and find them
[A plan]
- I can't tell from just this
- Okay
[I can't tell...]
- Oh, they're over there as well?
- Okay, I got one
- It's difficult
- There are so many
[Many pictures make it confusing]
- There are some here, too
- I got one, no, two
- Good job
- There are so many
[Scanning it everywhere]
There's nothing here
[What is this?]
Oh, I got one
[Lucky]
- There are more if you open the doors
- Okay, I found three
[Sharing tips]
I got one
[Finally finding the pictures within
the portraits]
If you need someone here, scan it
- There's one in the mirror
- In the mirror?
[Can't seem to see it himself]
- It could be in places like this
- Where is a mirror?
[Mirror?]
I can't find the mirror
It's here, there's some pictures here
[Jimin is the ace of Team Kim Seokjin]
[A flashing light?]
- Oh! Wow
- There was something here
[j-hope trying again]
- This isn't it
- I got one!
[Finally]
- I need to find a skull
- It's here
[Help me!]
- The skull is here?
- This is a skull?
[Team Jin showing off their teamwork]
- There it is
- Okay, done
[Gathered together]
- The last one, this lady
- She's over here
[Their teamwork getting better]
- Where?
- Let's hurry, there's 30 seconds left
[Not much time left before they must go on]
- Hurry up!
- Not this one, have you seen this?
[In a rush]
- Here
- Success!
- It's this one, isn't it?
- No, it's different
[Certain]
What is it?
- A lady with short hair
- 30 seconds left, let's move on
[In a rush]
- 10 seconds
- Let's go in
[Going on with 10 seconds left]
- I'm going to clear it, okay?
- Okay, 10 seconds left
- I still haven't found it
- That's okay, let's move on
[Sad]
We need to finish in time
Hurry up!
[Scanning the M-kit in front
of the next STAGE]
Ahhh!
[The crow reappeared today as well]
- They're shouting, it's a mess
- It's that intense?
[What's going on?]
Is it something scary?
[Brings back old memories]
- One person has a very low score
- It's j-hope, isn't it?
Of course it's j-hope
[Certain] [Everyone agrees]
What's this?
[Getting ready for the next stage]
I'm good at this, you know?
[Working hard]
[Stage 4: BTS Secret Agent]
[Infiltration ability test: Team match]
[All members must pass the laser room!
Everyone goes back to the beginning
if they touch a laser]
[Flexible Jimin begins first!]
If you touch the laser, everybody
has to start again
[Be careful]
Don't touch it!
[Back to the beginning if laser is touched]
- Don't touch it!
- If anyone does, everyone starts again
Don't touch the laser
Jimin, let's go!
- Jimin!
- Keep going!
Jimin!
[Working hard]
Jimin, be careful!
[Struggling] [Following behind]
Okay, great
Don't touch it, go lower
[Jimin arrived among the mess] [Loud]
- Lower your head
- Sorry
- Don't touch it
- Lower your head
[Pressed the button but nothing happens]
- It's up there
- Where?
[Is it this one?] [Fumbling around]
[Just then!]
- No!
- It wasn't me!
[Jin's card touched the laser beam]
- Hey, come back!
- Come back
[Louder because he's embarrassed]
Let's do it again
[Back to the beginning!]
Hurry up, there's no time
[Slide]
Go faster because we have no time
[Reliable ace Jimin arrived quickly]
- It's you, j-hope!
- Ugh!
[Working hard] [A mess]
- Really
- j-hope, it's you!
j-hope...
[Will they pass within sometime today?]
How many times are we doing this?
Carry j-hope on your back
[Out of breath from laughing]
How many times am I going back and forth?
[Perfectly passing through now]
[One with the floor]
I arrived, hurry up
[Laughing]
[Because they were caught in the laser...]
Hurry up!
[Laughing again]
[Because they weren't caught in the laser]
[Laughing machine]
[Every moment was great]
[Bright]
[Almost crying]
[Pressing again]
Jin!
[Last one left, Jin] [Close]
Why? I didn't touch it
[I'll do what I want regardless]
[Serious]
If you have short legs, you won't
be able to pass this
[Team Jin would have been in trouble
if it weren't for Jimin]
[Clumsy]
- It's opening
- We're here
[Team Kim Seokjin finally exits!]
[Scanning]
Hurry up
[All stages complete after the last scan!]
[Scanning]
- It was nothing
- What?
[All stages are over] [The trio escaped]
It was a mess inside
[Confident]
It was nothing
Can you see the scores right away?
[Checking their scores]
[BTS Secret Agent]
[Team Kim Seokjin / Scores]
[Jin - 350 points, j-hope - 290 points
Jimin - 330 points] [Total: 970 points]
- Let's go
- Is 350 a high score?
[Second Team: Team A]
Are they going before us?
- We could have gotten a perfect score
- Okay
[Confident]
Everyone...
[While Team A is getting ready]
Two people have gotten the red level
[Team Kim Seokjin]
Two of us?
[Anticipation]
Red means more than 300 points
[Correct]
Two got the red level
Jin and Jimin
[High-five!]
You got blue
[What about me?]
Everyone, there are levels, look
[MASTER LEVEL depending on scores]
White, yellow, green, blue, red and black
Like the Taekwondo belts
[Focused]
White, yellow, green..
[Color levels where higher the level
the darker the color like Taekwondo]
- Nobody got the black level
- Black level is like the master
- If you want the black level
you have to go in alone
- Really?
We started fighting as soon as we walked in
[The reason is...]
"Get out of my way!"
[Like this]
Don't we need to move on?
[A lively review from someone
who's experienced it firsthand]
Hey, we're a team!
- We're a team!
- No, this is an individual battle
[Can't tell if they're a team or not]
Let's go
Let's see what scores they get
[Self BGM] [Already being secret agents]
[Not nervous]
[V and SUGA walking in confidently]
We can say this. Since there were
three of us, we were at a disadvantage
There are places inside where
you need to place your phone
[The place to scan the M-kit]
They're all placed together
[Located tightly together]
So, we...
[I see]
- The three of us
- Our faces were all together
[Perfectly reenacting]
Against the wall...
[Like this]
[They became one with the wall]
[Close together]
We were up against the wall
like this
We were like that
The three of us were pressed together
- I want to see it like this
- He's still playing a game
[Sits down] [Perfectly natural]
Scan it
Aren't you supposed to scan it?
[Powerful] [In a rush]
- Where?
- Here
[Confused]
Here, at first...
[Watching it live] [Standing around]
- My face got pressed
- Right
- Jung Kook is watching
- I can't see anything
[Excuses?]
You shouldn't do that
- You have to be fair
- I'm just curious
[Curious]
Jung Kook...
What if someone gets injured...
[Incoherent speaking]
What if someone gets injured?
[What's he saying?]
He wants someone to get injured?
[I think he wants someone getting injured]
[Embarrassed]
They just walked in
[Live streaming] [Fumbling around]
What's this?
It's BTS
[The paper from picking team]
Oh, it's BTS
- Let's change it to Brain
- I folded it up
- Brain sounds better
- Okay, brain
[Changing their team name?]
- Or Bingsman
- Bingsman
Where do we shoot?
[Team A is also confused]
[This way]
We have to move this way?
[Shoot]
You take care of this area
[Trustworthy] [V taking care of SUGA]
- Where?
- Where are the targets?
[Team A confused but staying calm]
Where are other targets?
I don't know. Why aren't their
colors changing?
[Just shoot]
[Skills of someone who enjoyed
shooting games before]
They are working hard
[Worried]
I've never done escape rooms before
[Inexperienced person 1]
V shoots at the targets SUGA already shot
[Laughing at Team A's actions]
Are they fighting?
[Curious]
- They're fighting?
- They will eventually
[His own experience?]
There are 59 seconds left
[Shoot]
It feels like I'm cutting weeds
There are 15 seconds
We need to go on
[Must move to the next location in 15 sec]
Here, the next area
Move on, there you go
[Dark]
It's here
[Team A carries out the mission calmly
unlike what everyone expected]
We have to find M
[Slowly understanding the game rules]
[Perfectly understood]
You're good at this
[Impressed]
[Second zone]
[Enter the completely dark room]
It's completely dark
It's very dark
- Here it is
- I can't see anything
[Can't see] [It's dark]
Hang on
[Enthusiastic V and SUGA who can't walk]
What's this?
[Touching the air]
It's funny now that I'm watching it
[Relaxed as they're finished]
[Funnier now that they're watching]
V
V, poor thing
[His enthusiasm stands out
even in the dark]
I want to film this, where's my phone?
[Touching around]
They're relatively quiet
[Team A quieter than the previous team]
[Turning the camera]
[Laughing]
He's turning off the camera
Why is he doing that?
He's doing it for purpose
[I got it]
He's doing it because of the light
[He's smart]
They're breaking the rules
[Protesting]
I can't see the cameras, though
[V continuing to touch the cameras]
You can use this light
[V's cute cheating]
M, M
[Found it!]
- M
- How do you scan this?
[Finally found M!]
Where is it?
[Touching around]
- It's here
- Here?
[Hawaiian Couple] [Not their first time as a team]
- Why does it suddenly work for me?
- Wait, we can't touch all the V's
[Patting around]
[I can feel it]
[There must be something here]
Here it is
[V & SUGA finding it rather easily
in the dark]
Done?
- I got it
- You did?
[Thanks to SUGA] [Finished scanning the M]
If they touch the camera again
they should get some kind of penalty
[Observing their behavior]
[V turned the camera again]
- They're breaking the rules
- He did it again
Did they break the rules?
[What rule did they break?]
They're using the camera lights
[Team Kim Seokjin agitated by
V's cheating]
- He's turning on the light
- It's the third time already
[Caught him in the act]
This is the third time
the camera director is closing it
This should be minus 10 points
for each time
They need some kind of penalty
[Everyone appealing for points being
taken off]
- Do you accept?
- You should accept this, director
It's a dark room, so they shouldn't
be using the camera light
[Firm]
The producer accepted it
[Staff agreed to take off points]
- Here
- Let me know
[The two communicating without knowing]
Where? Hurry up
This is a V!
[Told him the wrong one] [What is this?]
We're not supposed to scan the V
[Points taken off]
Aren't I supposed to?
[Even touching the ceiling]
Nothing on the ceiling?
We have to hurry up
[Must move to the next stage]
V, come here
[Hurry up]
[Starting the next stage by scanning
the M-kit]
[In a rush]
Is it something scary again?
[Close to tears]
This looks easy
Mine's the one with a hat
[Team A also struggling amidst
the many portraits]
[Surprised]
[Looking around]
Here it is
[Found it]
Why isn't it working?
This is right
Why are there so many doors?
- What's this?
- This is right
Try opening it up
[Portraits on the other side of the door]
There are two more here
Why isn't it working? Work
[Acting cute towards the portrait]
There's no person
[I can't find the person I'm looking for]
This is right, though
I want to take it off the wall
[Team A struggling in the third stage]
Hang on. This one is right
[Nothing here?]
- There's no skull
- Let's find the one with two people
[Sob]
Skull
[Can't find the skull picture]
There's no skull
This one...
[V standing in front of the mirror]
Here it is
[Found it]
Where?
[SUGA rushing at the news of the skull]
This one
- Was it there?
- Yes, this is the one
Oh, so this is how it works
[V figured it out too late]
This is how it works
[Eureka! He figured it out, too]
- 20 seconds
- We need to move on
[In a rush] [Not enough time left]
Let's go
[Flailing around]
We have 15 seconds left
[Passionate]
[I can't give up]
[Caster Jimin is broadcasting live]
They're here
[Arrived]
They just entered the last room
They're crowded together like us
[Looks just like us]
Are they fools, too?
They're doing the same thing
- This is hilarious
- This is the funniest
[Right up his alley]
Jung Kook will like this
[Me?]
I don't know how many times
I went back and forth
[Allowed to talk about it]
He was the worst, but he kept
saying things to us
I was dumbfounded myself
I could have gone on my own
[Team A is carrying out the last mission]
[Working hard]
[V touched the laser
as soon as he started]
[Crawling]
Can't we just go through
if we touched the laser?
- No, we have to start again
- From the beginning?
[This team is also uneasy from the start]
[Laughing out loud]
Why?
[Tell me]
- They don't know how to do it
- You need to try this yourself
It's a relief I figured it out
[Good thing we figured it out then]
Otherwise, we would have never know
- What is it?
- What?
[Curious] [Unknown world to them]
What's going on?
[Feet stomping]
[Look at them]
[They're filming "Mission Impossible"]
I'm so curious
[They're super curious]
SUGA is so cute
[So cute]
[SUGA is confidently failing]
They didn't tell us the password
Where is it?
[Confused]
Just press it
[Do I just press this?]
Come back here
[Come back]
I guess we touched the laser
Come back
Okay
[Decide to calmly restart]
Oh, this is how you press it
[Working hard]
[V is crawling with his necklace
in his mouth]
Hurry up. There you go, jump
[Restarting the mission with help from
instructor SUGA]
[Camera is crooked after
bumping into V]
[V successfully finished!]
[But the problem is...]
[SUGA who started over]
Come back!
[Oh no]
No, go
We need one more person
[This scene is... "Saving Private Ryan?"]
[Working hard]
I got caught
- Done?
- Yes, done
What do I do here?
[Wants to get out]
Jump
- Jump?
- Jump!
[SUGA finally passed through the
laser beams]
[Confused] [Password?]
[Leaves]
[Wait for me]
Now...
[Are they done?]
Mission clear!
[Team A finishes as well]
[Exhausted]
Scan it
You need to scan it
[Team A uneasy till the very end]
- It was fun
- Watching is more fun
[Hehe]
Watching is more fun
[You're right]
- You two were really bad
- V
We saw you cheating
[There were mistakes but had good teamwork]
[Team A's score?]
[BTS Secret Agent
Team A / Scores]
[SUGA - 228 points
V - 300 points - 50 points = 250 points]
[Team Kim Seokjin's lowest score - 290
= 769 points]
There are reasons behind it
[V got 250 points for green level]
[Smiling]
V, do you know why you're green?
[Bingsman trying to get hints from
his confession]
- Please confess
I'll confess once you go in
[Not falling for it]
If you go inside
he will tell us the reason
[We're not telling you]
Because you broke the rules inside...
He broke the rules
[Telling on his own team member]
How much was taken off?
[Anticipation]
- 50 points
The violation was too serious
[Hehe]
I did my best
But my score was lower than
their lowest
SUGA, as you're on the same team
we tried to reduce yours as well
But after seeing your score
[My score?]
We decided not to
[A sad score] [Felt bad for SUGA]
[How bad was his score?]
- It was 178 if you reduced it
- I'd be the white level
[If cut, SUGA would get the lowest level]
It's 178 points if cut
[I worked really hard...]
I did my best
Next team, get ready please
[Finally, the last team] [Team Bingsman]
- Let's go
- It was fun, wasn't it?
[Excited]
Since this was the beginner's level
[Waiting]
Let's do the intermediate level now
[Confident]
- Let's go
- RM and Jung Kook
[Team Bingsman is off!]
The dream team is going in
[Walking through]
Here
[Up against the wall like magnets]
- Done
- Mine isn't working
[In a rush]
Press it. No, use your thumb
- What's this?
- Do we go through?
[Team Bingsman confused in the start too]
No
We can shoot
Oh, so this is why they say they fought
[Got it]
They're fighting, right?
[Everybody watching it live]
They'll shoot what's already been shot
[Statements coming together like
puzzle pieces]
Jung Kook is very competitive
You need to let him win
[Jung Kook manual]
This is an easy stage as long as
you get along
Between M and V...
[SUGA found STAGE 2 difficult]
They're confusing
[You're right]
That's where he broke the rules
[Dark room mission that caused
rule breaking]
You're not supposed to scan V
- If you do, your points get reduced
- Oh, really?
They're fighting
[Jimin excited over their fight]
They're hitting each other with the guns
[Collision]
No! I will shoot more than Jung Kook!
[RM is struggling]
[Bang bang]
28 seconds!
Let's go
[Acting different from his words]
[Jung Kook is super focused]
I got it
[They really have to move on now]
[Listening]
RM is so funny
He's exactly like you
"Let's go"
[Perfect reenactment] [Bang bang]
[That's hilarious]
You can't help it
I was almost hit by j-hope doing that
[Suddenly solemn]
We're entering the darkness
[Team Bingsman moved to the second area]
Go first
[The younger goes first]
Only M, not V
- Only M?
- Only M
- Hey!
- What?
[Bingsman enter the dark room as well]
What's this?
Why is it going down?
[Feeling around]
- How do you find this?
- You need to touch the wall
Oh, it's the camera director
I'm sorry
[Sudden apology]
[RM is scanning the camera]
[It's hilarious]
To the camera...
Touch the wall
[They're still touching around everywhere]
If it's V, don't scan
- If it's in the shape of M, scan it
- In the shape of M?
Where are V and M?
[Jung Kook hectic because he's looking
around and giving instructions]
You can feel it
I got two already
- Did you? Where
- Yes
[Confused]
- Over here
- I have to feel it to know
[Teamwork shining in the dark]
- Here
- Where? Here?
- This? It's V
- Yes
- It's not V
- Oh, it's M
Here, it's M again
[Our ace] [Agent Jung Kook working hard]
- Where?
- Come here
- Here
- I'm sorry
[Hit his face on accident] [Sudden apology]
He hit him
RM hit Jung Kook
[Breaking news]
- With his elbow
- RM hit Jung Kook's face
[I saw it]
He hit Jung Kook's face with
his elbow
[Hilarious]
Their teamwork is great
[Perfect teamwork]
I got it, thanks
[Showing great teamwork]
[Searching thoroughly, even on the floor]
Hang on
[Feeling around]
Here it is
[Grab] [Found it]
I haven't scanned there
- Here
- I see
Good, our teamwork is great
- Here
- Where?
[Bingsman getting better with time]
Here?
I think we've scanned everything
We're done, right?
I think we scanned them all
Let's go
I think we did it all, let's go on
[RM & Jung Kook having the easiest time]
We're moving on smoothly
A lady
We need to zoom in
Let's do this calmly
Calm down RM, you should not get excited
[Convincing himself]
RM, don't get too excited
[Don't get too excited]
RM's chin is sticking out
He's so serious
When he does that, it means he's serious
[RM gets serious when his chin sticks out?]
Let me tell you all this
[Attention! Doctor Jimin's analysis
on RM]
There are two reasons his chin
sticks out
Either he wants to get something done
[Analysis 1]
Or he wants to look cool
[Analysis 2]
- RM is really...
- Scoring high?
RM will struggle in the last room
[j-hope's prediction]
Jung Kook may get angry in the last room
[That's right]
"Please just stay still"
[Full of dialect] [Acting like Jung Kook]
If you find a skull, tell me
[Jung Kook focused despite what they say
outside]
There's no skull here
[Where is it?]
I can't find it
[High difficulty]
[Everybody struggled with the skull]
- This isn't it
- The skull?
- Focus on yours, first
- Here it is
- Did you find it?
- Yes
But it won't scan
Zoom in on the one inside
[Smart RM is acting in STAGE 3]
I haven't found the skull
What should I do?
[Got it]
I can't find it
- I got 2
- Did you?
33 seconds
[Only have 33 seconds left]
I got 3
Hey, 26 seconds
We need to move on
[In a rush] [Where is it?]
- We need to go
- Okay
- Let's move on
[Team Bingsman arrived at STAGE 4]
- Go, go
- Let's go
- They're in the last room
- Last room, this is really...
Only one person has to go through, right?
[Huh?]
I'll go then
[That's why I'm going now]
[Agent Jung Kook going through
so smoothly]
No, we need to scan it together
[Working hard]
[Can't tell if it looks difficult because
of his height or inflexibility...]
Hey, come in
I'll go
Try not to touch the lasers
Above!
[OUT before he knows it]
- He failed
- RM failed
[Accurate prediction]
- Everyone's the same
- We're the same
[Didn't press the buzzer]
They didn't press the buzzer
[Excited]
158 seconds
Watch your head
Legs
[RM didn't see the buzzer]
No, no
You touched it
- Did I?
- You did
You go first
Oh, you have to press this and restart
[Bam] [Now saw the buzzer]
- Yeah, there you go. Your legs
- I see
[Can they escape sometime today?]
[Careful]
[Holding his breath]
[Entered the difficult section]
Argh!
[He failed again]
[So hilarious]
Did RM fail again?
Is RM crawling?
[Crawling] [RM pulling together
his long limbs]
Why is he going like that?
It's so silly
I can't escape this place!
[Hilarious]
RM keeps failing as we expected
If he fails one more time, I will love him
[Ecstatic watcher]
No...
You go first
You need to go first
That's the only way to succeed
[Older one first] [Younger one first]
Where do I go from here?
[Pause]
Lift your knee
[RM became Jung Kook's avatar]
Just crawl. You just need to pass it
Go pass there
Hurry up
84 seconds
[Please don't cover the camera...]
[A piece of cake for Jung Kook]
Pass it, okay
They passed it
[Finally]
They finished
[Team Bingsman finally escaped]
[Oh, I forgot]
[Scanning]
Great job
- Did you scan it?
RM made us laugh out loud
RM, you did a great job
[RM is today's MVP]
I heard you scored the highest
- Really?
- No, Jin scored the highest
- This is so hilarious
- Really
- What's your score?
- How much did you get?
[BTS Secret Agent]
[Team Bingsman / Scores]
[Jung Kook - 288 points, RM - 320 points]
[Team Kim Seokjin's lowest score - 290 points]
[Total = 898 points]
- So, Team Kim Seokjin won?
- Amazing
Kim Seokjin!
- Prize! There's none
But Secret Agent is not over yet
[Not a paused screen]
- Really?
- What do you mean?
[This is just beginning]
[More exciting and adventurous 2nd test]
Really? I love it
Let's go to the 2nd mission!
[Let's go to the second mission!]
Are we going to jump?
1, 2, 3
[Teleport]
So bright
Run BTS, Secret Agent episode
[Hosting]
The 2nd game
[What are you doing, Jimin?]
What are these?
It's the cart rider
[An important skill is driving!]
- Isn't it a cart?
- Like Mario Kart?
Real carts
[BTS Secret Agent]
[2nd test: Cart]
[Test to see driving ability
an important qualification of a secret agent]
[The game is a relay team match
For teams with 2 members
the first runner drives one more time]
[300, 200, 100 points will be given
based on their ranking]
I think the starting position is important
What about deciding the starting places
according to the ranks of the last game?
They are separate matches
[What are you talking about?]
Let's play rock paper scissors
- Let's play rock paper scissors
- Representatives, come up
Our team's leader
- Jin
- Kim Seokjin for our team
Rock paper scissors
[Won] [Lost] [Lost]
- 2nd place
- 2nd?
[Won] [Lost]
[BTS Secret Agent]
[Carts' placement and order on the track]
[1st Track Bingsman: Jung Kook - RM -
Jung Kook]
[2nd Track Team A: V - SUGA - V]
[3rd track Team Kim Seokjin
Jin - j-hope - Jimin]
[First runners going to their carts]
First runner, Kim Seokjin
Please cheer me up
1, 2, 3
- Kim
- Seok
- Jin!
That's good, let's go
- Bingsman
- A
[Cheering them on]
- Love you all
[You're both weird, stop it]
- Everyone, move behind a bit
- Move behind, just a bit
- Are you ready?
- Be careful
[Waiting at the start line]
[Get ready]
[1st Jung Kook (Team Bingsman)
2nd V (Team A) 3rd Jin (Team Kim Seokjin)]
Kim Seok Jin!
He's off to a good start
[1st V (Team A)
2nd Jin (Team Kim Seokjin)
3rd Jung Kook (Team Bingsman)]
[Jung Kook's view]
Great!
[Powerful]
Jung Kook!
V is racing well, in course
[Fast]
[Humming while enjoying the speed]
[So hurried] [I'll go on my way]
[Forgetting about the track and racing]
Jin is off the track
Stay in the track
[Safety first, please stay on track]
V is going so fast
[Best racer V going steadily] [Cool]
Jeon Jung Kook!
[Cheer up a bit]
[You're doing great
Let's finish first]
Jeon Jung Kook!
[Current ranking]
[1st - V, 2nd - Jung Kook, 3rd - Jin ]
V is leading
[V is way ahead]
He's great on the in course
V is the best driver
V, you're doing great!
Last round
[I'm pretty good]
Jung Kook, way to go!
[Last turn for the first drive]
[Shouting way to go!]
- Will Jin turn the tables?
- Jung Kook, no!
[Jin came from behind]
[2nd Jin (Team Kim Seokjin)
3rd Jung Kook (Team Bingsman)]
- Cool
- No!
Jin turned it around
[I'm a good driver as well]
[Replacing the racer with the 2nd one]
[Hurry up] [SUGA in a rush]
[1st SUGA (Team A)]
[Replacing racers quickly]
Let's go!
[2nd j-hope (Team Kim Seokjin)
3rd RM (Team Bingsman)]
[So serious] [My turn]
[RM is starting now]
[Left alone]
[Left behind]
[So relaxed]
j-hope, you have to be quick!
[Dancing]
Wow!
[RM, hurry up!]
I'm scared
[RM's point of view]
[SUGA driving well and not
getting overtaken]
Wow! SUGA is so cool!
[SUGA seems so proud]
[Wait for me! I'm coming]
Wow! j-hope, you're so cool!
j-hope, hurry up!
[I love speed]
RM, hurry up
He says it's scary
[So scared]
[I think this is fast enough]
SUGA, you're so cool!
[Team A not losing the first spot]
[Wow! Excited!]
[Applause]
[SUGA, please keep going as you are]
[So interesting]
[j-hope is closely following SUGA]
[Vroom]
[1st j-hope (Team Kim Seokjin)
2nd SUGA (Team A)]
[Let me show my driving skills]
[j-hope cornered inside
and caught up with SUGA]
j-hope!
[Please get out of my way, sorry]
[Drifting]
[Desperate]
[I can't believe it!]
[The last runner's turn]
[The last chance to turn around]
[1st Jimin (Team Kim Seokjin)
2nd V (Team A)] [Quickly seated]
[Jimin starts first]
[I will take over the lead]
Park Jimin!
Jung Kook, you can do it!
[V quickly chasing after him]
Here we go!
[Wait for me!]
There you go
[V turning close to the corner]
Go get him!
[Getting close behind Jimin!]
[Loud]
- Run!
- Jimin, way to go!
Let's go!
[I'm going]
Jung Kook, it's okay
You can go slowly
[Safety first]
[Run] [Great]
[Art of doppelganger?]
Jimin!
[I'm first]
Let's go! Let's finish
[Sure of 2nd place]
[Thumbs up]
[Our Manggae is going]
[Jumping]
[j-hope and Jin cheering]
[A wide gap] [Jung Kook is coming behind]
Kim Seokjin
Jung Kook, enjoy it
Enjoy
[It's okay]
[Disappointed]
Kim Seokjin!
[We're first]
[Great weather for racing]
[The answer is already decided
Jimin just has to keep racing]
[Jimin finishes first with cheers
from j-hope and Jin]
Don't take off your hands
[Enjoying his victory] [It's dangerous]
[V finishes second]
[Smiling]
Great job
[We won]
[I'm Manggae Jimin]
[Jung Kook finishes the race]
Jung Kook, you're the best
[Our youngest did great]
[3rd]
[Jung Kook has arrived]
[Applause]
[2nd test cart relay race is over]
[BTS Secret Agent]
[Cart racing result]
[1st - Team Kim Seokjin: 300]
[2nd - Team A: 200
3rd - Team Bingsman: 100]
Today's winner is Team Kim Seokjin!
The runner up is Team A
The 3rd... What were you?
[Taken back] [What was your team name?]
- Bingsman
- Team Bingsman
- Final result
- What's the final result?
[The final result everyone is curious about]
Please announce it
Isn't our ranking still higher?
[Even though we placed third]
[BTS Secret Agent]
[Final result]
[1st Team Kim Seokjin - 970 + 300 = 1270
2nd Team Bingsman - 898 + 100 = 998]
[3rd Team A - 768+200 = 968]
[50 points were cut due to rule breaking]
I've never done anything wrong
Once again, emphasizing sportsmanship
- It's a lesson to learn
- 30 point gap
[Because of the cheating]
If their points were not reduced
- They would have won
- Right
If V hadn't done anything wrong
- We did our best
- Hold each other's hands
[Let's hold hands]
Are there prizes for the winner?
There's something
[Curious] [What's the first place prize?]
What's that?
It's in the size of a remote-controlled car
It's an RC car
[Confident]
That's 100% an RC car
[Jealous]
- RC car
- Really?
I'm so sure
[Shake]
Let's open the box here
It would be fun
[Will RM's prediction be correct?]
[Correct]
It's an RC car
It's BOgatti
[That's amazing]
- It's an RC car!
- BOgatti!
It's BOgatti!
[Hurry up] [Awesome]
BOgatti
Hang on
Let's give it to one person
- Right, do that
- Give it to one person
[That sounds fun]
Do one more round of carts
[Can we?]
[Sure! Do whatever you want, Jimin]
[BTS Secret Agent]
[Extra cart racing to get the RC car prize]
[The person who finishes first after
racing three rounds will win]
[Team Kim Seokjin members
are waiting to decide who will get BOgatti]
[1st Jin 2nd j-hope 3rd Jimin]
[Get ready] [I want to have it]
[BOgatti is mine] [I will win]
[BOgatti, wait for me]
[Let's go]
[Beginning of the race to get BOgatti]
[1st j-hope
2nd Jimin 3rd Jin]
Jimin
[Jimin racing to be first]
[1st Jimin 2nd Jin 3rd j-hope]
[Fierce competition to get the 1st place]
[1st Jimin 2nd j-hope 3rd Jin]
[This is fun, even though it's the 2nd time]
[The 1st turning point]
[I'm winning]
Why is this cart so slow?
[Twins? Jin and j-hope coming in together]
The car is slow
[Looks like fun]
[With a small gap]
[Team Kim Seokjin members
are moving the track at similar paces]
j-hope!
j-hope is catching up with Jimin
[I won't allow that]
[Racing fast]
[Neck-and-neck]
j-hope is overtaking him!
[j-hope overtaking him in the corner]
[1st j-hope 2nd Jimin 3rd Jimin]
[Won't let you win]
[Today's colleague is the enemy]
j-hope, let's go!
[Full concentration]
[What's happening?]
[The two crashed together trying
to go fast]
[1st Jimin 2nd j-hope 3rd Jin]
[Squeak]
[Surprised]
[j-hope stopped]
[1st Jimin 2nd Jin 3rd j-hope]
[RC cars can be scary everyone]
[Innocent]
[Should I try again?]
Jin finishes 2nd against
everyone's expectation!
[1st Jimin 2nd Jin 3rd j-hope]
[Disappointed]
It was so close
[Individual match for the RC car is over]
Bummer
Best driver Park Jimin, how do you feel?
[RC car goes to Jimin who came in first]
- This...
- You ensured the victory at the last round
I think other members need
to practice driving
Everyone, be careful when driving
You can't drive like we did
Thank you
Let's shout out "safe" and "driving"
as we finish
- Safe!
- Driving!
- Eco
- Drive
[Sounds like a campaign]
[We ran and ran today as well]
[Run BTS! Please look forward to next week]