[RUN BTS: Billboard Hot 100 Pledge
- Become each other's stylists]
RUN BTS!
- RUN BTS!
- This is our home.
[Why did they gather up?]
Why are we here today?
- Again?
- It's our second time shooting at home.
- It should be the second or third.
- It's the third time.
We're here today to keep our pledge
for entering the Billboard Hot 100.
- Oh.
- Styling each other.
[This is how it all began...]
[2017.9.30 BTS' pledge for entering
the Billboard Hot 100 chart]
I saw an interesting suggestion.
- Which one?
- Styling each other.
- That's a nice idea.
- Nice.
[Today's RUN BTS! Become each other's stylists
to fulfill the Billboard Hot 100 pledge!]
[Use your own outfits to style each other!]
[Play a game to choose partners
and put on a fashion show]
[Who will show the best style?]
[You already thought it out?]
I thought about a pink ensemble.
[Disappointed]
But I just remembered
I threw away the pink pants.
- Bummer.
- I can't do that.
[Is Jin the worst fashion stylist?]
Anybody but Jin, please.
I'll create a look with
my favorite pajamas.
[Soulless]
Pajamas are nice.
[Serious about his styling]
I won't make it a joke.
- Sounds crazy.
- I'll do my best.
[Jung Kook is known for his unique style]
I guess you all know my style.
- Gray track suits again?
- Track suits?
[No way]
Pants I bought from overseas.
[All members are suspicious]
- Oh, you bought...
- You bought pants from overseas?
- Aren't they dress pants?
- No.
- Namjoon.
- I'll use the piece I always wanted to wear
[Which one?]
but never had a chance.
- Wow.
- I'll dress you guys in my style.
This pouch is the accent piece.
[Hobi's must-have item]
I'll attach this pouch to you.
- And...
- People hate it.
[Taetae language]
Jin's birthday is near(?) around the corner.
[True]
Right, it's just around the corner.
[Oh?]
- I bought his birthday gift.
- Already?
[V bought Jin's birthday gift]
- Yes.
- Will you use the gift for Jin?
- That's what you'll use?
- To see how it fits?
[I am serious]
Yes, I'll see how it fits.
[Smiling] [Precious gift]
There's only one of it in the world.
[Tempting]
- Oh...
- Because
[Hand gestures] [Like this]
they make only one piece at a time.
[True leader RM who summarizes V's words]
- It's custom-made?
- Yes, custom-made.
What if another member gets to
wear that custom-made item first?
And Jin may not even like it.
Nah, it's the heart that matters.
[The biggest problem is size]
I'm worried about the size as I'm the smallest.
[Worrying]
- Right.
- If Namjoon wears my clothes...
[It will be OK, Jimin]
- It will look interesting.
- I'll select clothes
- They'll look like cropped pants.
- which fit me tightly.
[Soullessly]
I'm so excited to do this.
[Jimin's fit is so nice]
- Right.
- My legs are not that short!
Let's go to our rooms.
[Let's go choose clothes!]
- Let's choose outfits.
- Let's go.
Let's go! RUN BTS!
[Jung Kook's wardrobe]
What should I choose?
[Empty laugh]
[Jung Kook looks lost]
[Scratch]
[What should I choose?]
Pants...
[I got one! I found one!]
[Hehehe]
[Kookie's back looks so excited]
[This is the one!]
[All right, this is it]
Yes, this is the one.
[This is it!]
I'll make them wear these.
[Jung Kook's pants]
And since I like an ensemble...
[Jung Kook can't help but smile
thinking about dressing the others]
So nice!
[When did you change?]
[V's wardrobe]
[The members came to take a look]
It's getting worse.
[Gasped at V's unique style]
These ties...
[V's wardrobe reminds him of his grandpa]
I've seen this in my grandpa's closet.
[Quickly leaves after his business is over]
I have neckties that will look
great on each member.
[V thinks it will go well with RM]
This is for Namjoon.
[...The rest are for RM too]
They'd all look good on Namjoon.
[Graphic patterns]
I should check out the fit.
[V's birthday gift for Jin]
It goes on like this.
[A praiseworthy collab of
pajamas and the coat]
[Rebellious look]
Like this...
[Striking poses]
[RM's wardrobe]
I really wanted to wear this.
[The look he had in mind]
I wanted to try this style
but I didn't have the chance.
[Kim Daily's proportions stand out]
I'll dress them in this.
[Who do you want to style?]
Jimin or Yoongi.
If you've ever felt upset
about looking small,
[Kim Daily's styling recommendations]
if you wear something like this,
[A fit that will never make you look small]
you will look much taller.
I'd respect anyone who
[Mysterious tie... A necklace?]
could pull this off.
That's too much.
[SUGA's wardrobe]
Where are all my clothes gone?
[SUGA, you have so many clothes]
Did someone steal them?
[Jin who shares the wardrobe]
I don't have any new clothes.
[Rummaging]
[Stark difference in fashion style]
To revolutionize fashion...
[The origin of "World wide handsome"]
I wore this shirt for the Billboard event.
[This would be nice]
I wore slacks with it.
[Shirt + sweat pants?]
Let's match it with sweat pants.
[Where are all my clothes?]
Are they mixed with his?
[SUGA and Jin are busy
doing their own thing]
[Making a bold entrance]
[j-hope and Jimin's wardrobe]
- Jimin, you're not done yet?
- I'm about to start.
[So excited]
I'm so excited to pick an outfit.
[Jimin is curious of his styling]
Are you going to use what you're wearing?
[Good idea]
Should I do that? Not a bad idea.
[I inspired him]
Did I give him an idea? What an idea bank.
Let's choose clothes.
I hope my partner would be Taehyung.
[Jimin wants to style V]
- Taehyung?
- Yes.
[The members always care for each other]
Because I bought his birthday gift.
- Really?
- Yes.
[Ta-da]
I bet Taehyung will love it.
[One more for V's necktie collection]
[Another gift from Jimin]
You gifted this T-shirt to me.
Should I dress a member in this?
[Perfect] [My pouch is the perfect finisher]
Then, add my pouch.
[Will Hobi style the best outfit?]
This is the best fashion!
[BTS - Best Of Me]
[Oops]
Sorry
[Which member can pull off this outfit?]
I look forward to seeing who
will pull off this outfit.
[Careful consideration for his partner]
The pants may be a bit big for some members
so I'll bring this belt.
[Good]
This is going to be my look.
[Who will wear RM's outfit?]
Done!
[Mulling]
[SUGA is thinking carefully]
[Jin appears holding a track suit]
[Korea's national flag-inspired fashion]
Done. It's game over. How does it look?
[V is busy choosing]
Let's hurry up.
[A man who knows how to wear a tie]
[Proficient]
Done.
[Putting the tie around a shirt]
[The coat is Jin's birthday gift]
[Satisfactory smile]
[SUGA looks satisfied]
This is going to be enough.
[Those who finished styling gather up]
[Satisfied]
This is enough for me.
[Jung Kook is still thinking]
Let's get it over with.
[Searching through]
I have very few items.
[Giving up?]
Well, I don't know.
[His fashion philosophy]
I won't dress them in
a style I've never tried.
[Don't know when it was though]
I'm sure I wore this before.
[Obviously Jung Kook's jacket]
[Hehe]
[It's so funny]
[Worrying]
They want to see the pink ensemble.
[Jin feels pressured about the other's
expectation of the pink ensemble]
I don't have any pink pants.
A pink jacket and a pink coat...
[Jin's passion for pink
is seen from his clothes]
[j-hope shows off his outfit to the 94z]
Namjoon, look. The pants you threw away.
[Perfect]
Top it off with a bucket hat...
[RM doesn't recognize his pants]
- Did I throw these pants away?
- Yes.
Look at Jung Kook's jacket.
[Drawing all attention]
Amazing.
[Still choosing]
Ahhhhh!
[Jimin found an "it" item]
I love this.
[You do, Jimin?]
This is so cute.
[I love it]
I love this thing.
I will bring three sets of outfits.
[First case]
If my partner is Taehyung,
this is the outfit.
Tuck this shirt into the pants
and wear a tie.
[V = Shirt, pants, tie and jacket]
I'll add a jacket, too.
[Second case]
For someone whose frame is similar to mine,
[Pretty shirt]
I'll make him wear this shirt.
[The last case]
For those who are tall
and have a bigger frame like RM,
[Cute overall for those with a big frame]
I will make them wear this cute one.
- You can look forward to it.
- Really?
[Worrying]
His fashion style is a bit comical.
[Like-minded]
I don't want Jin to be my partner.
[Please]
Me, too. Anyone but Jin.
I'll try a chic look.
[Taetae language]
For Jin's birthday party... birthday gift,
this is the perfect outfit
[Black turtleneck is
the essential item for a chic style]
No.
[Finished with a fashionable hat]
No, no.
[So proud]
Done.
I hope you prepared an outfit
that you can wear yourself.
[I've tried the look before]
I've worn this exact style before.
[Me, too]
I tried them on just now too.
- I brought two styles I've never tried.
- OK.
And one that I've tried.
[Well-prepared]
- You brought so many things.
- A lot.
[Curious of Jimin's look]
To suit your partner's taste?
Or is it to suit your taste?
[I prepared...]
One is for those with a bigger frame.
[Jimin even considered the members' frames]
- Oh.
The other one is for a slimmer frame.
[Listening]
And one is something special.
[Clever]
Will you choose a style depending on
who your partner is?
Yes.
[Acknowledging]
He's so well-prepared.
Will we get to see BTS fashion week today?
[Excited] [Cute]
- I think we're playing a game.
- Let's go!
[Go, go to the BTS fashion week!]
RUN BTS!
[The clothes they selected
show their distinct fashion taste]
Let's take a look at them.
[SUGA brought pajamas with a price tag]
- SUGA, are these pajamas?
- They're pajamas.
Pajamas with the price tag still on.
- Jin's and Jung Kook's catch my eye.
- Right.
The clothes are grabbing my attention.
[Jin, the worst fashion stylist]
I wish I won't have to wear Jin's.
I want to try Jung Kook's style.
[Jimin + Jung Kook's clothes = ?]
- I want to see if I can pull it off.
- How will it fit?
[Unique challenge]
- I want to take on the challenge.
- I'm curious, too.
[Came running to see Jin's outfit]
Hey, this is too over-the-top.
What's the point of this look?
[Hear me out]
- Hang on.
- Let him speak.
- You're going to wear all of these.
- All of them?
[Bingo]
Don't tell me we're wearing
pants over pants.
[He'll explain it later]
Let's hear him out later.
If someone wears these,
[Jin's outfit looks extreme from the back]
- From behind...
- It looks like you're not wearing pants.
I thought about that, too.
[The oldest is so caring]
- Some of us don't wear short pants.
- Right.
- So I prepared these long pants.
- Oh, no wonder he came to me and asked,
[Now I get it] [Having a mental breakdown]
"Jimin, can I borrow your leggings?"
[A few minutes ago]
- Jimin.
- Yeah?
- You can't spy on me.
- Can I borrow your leggings?
- I don't have one.
- You don't?
Are those long pants?
- No, they're capris.
- Where did you get these socks?
[Even his socks are pink...]
- Where did you get these?
- Do they sell socks like these?
[Socks that remind you of strawberry milk]
- Did you soak them in strawberry milk?
- I wore them once.
[It's OK]
- Did you?
- Yes.
[Styling is done] [Who will style who?]
Then, now,
we need to decide our partners.
- How will we decide our partners?
- Let's leave it to fate.
[Game to decide partners]
[Each member will throw a rose
with his back to the others]
[The member closest to the rose
will be the partner]
[However, if the rose hits a member,
that member will be the partner]
[SUGA's turn to choose his fate]
- SUGA, you go first.
- My pajamas
[SUGA has never worn them]
have never been worn.
Why do they look so small?
[Too small]
I can't wear SUGA's clothes.
- I can't either.
- No, it's going to fit.
[Is the size big?]
Is it a bit big?
[It fits me so it will fit you]
It fits me just right.
- How can I wear it then?
- I can't wear it.
[So confident]
But my clothes will look fine.
[Shuffling around]
[I'll walk my own path]
SUGA, your clothes are not popular.
[j-hope and V are bickering]
[Guys, stop fighting]
1, 2, 3.
[Drop]
[Who will SUGA style?] [Nervous]
Done? Can I turn around?
It's j-hope, I guess.
[Most members are saying it's j-hope]
I think it's j-hope, too.
No. From here,
the rose is close to this side.
[Asking for the production crew's help]
Can you make the decision?
Let's throw it one more time
with just Jimin and Hobi standing.
[Clear solution]
- Great.
- Solomon.
I don't mind getting chosen.
So why am I so nervous?
[1, 2, 3]
[My eyes are only on you]
Go to Jimin!
[Oh no]
[Whatever SUGA says will come true]
Is this a proposal?
[Amazed]
How did you know where Jimin was?
[Hobi is envious as Jimin avoided Jin]
- Congrats on avoiding Jin.
- Thanks.
- I'm so jealous of you.
- Thank you, everyone.
- Congrats.
- Thank you!
- I'm afraid of Seokjin, too.
[The members start worrying]
But I'm scared of Jung Kook, too.
I think Jimin would look
great in these.
[SUGA will be Jimin's stylist]
This look is made for Jimin.
[Jimin's turn]
Let's shuffle!
[Getting ready]
1, 2, 3!
[Hehe] [Let's see]
[The rose went past the members]
[BTS referees]
[It's me?] [Jimin will be Jung Kook's stylist]
- It's Jung Kook.
- It's exactly Jung Kook.
- Good!
- I've never seen him in this style.
[Satisfied]
- Jimin!
- What should I dress Jung Kook?
[Lala]
Something I won't wear.
[The youngest is so excited to tease others]
Jung Kook....
[Jin's shadow is looming over]
When Seokjin's turn nears, I feel nervous.
- I hope I can be Jung Kook's partner.
- We have to be chosen this time.
We have to get chosen now.
[So excited] [Who will wear Jung Kook's?]
Let's see who will be his partner.
[Shuffling]
[Yup]
1, 2, 3!
[While everyone is looking forward...]
[Whish]
[Making a fuss]
- j-hope!
- No.
What do you mean? I was here.
- You two stand there.
- Two of you.
[Arguing]
Let's replay the video clip. It wasn't me.
- You must really hate Jung Kook's style...
- Jung Kook, it's SUGA!
[The youngest checks out SUGA's place]
[Nervous]
Will you stand there?
[Let's see]
1, 2, 3.
[SUGA? Or j-hope?]
[Ambiguous]
Hold on! Stay still.
[SUGA? j-hope?]
- Hold on.
- This is j-hope.
No.
[Do you really want to measure?]
- Let's measure.
- Let's go again.
The production team concluded
it was SUGA.
[Too excited] [What do you mean?]
It doesn't make sense!
[Jung Kook will be SUGA's stylist]
- It's next to him. How can it be me?
- You should have put your feet together.
- At least it's not Jin!
[Mad]
- No.
- What's wrong with my style?
[Stammering]
I want to try it.
- I'll choose you.
- I want to try your look.
- I will find you.
- I want to try your style.
[Me]
- Who's next?
- I'll go.
- Your turn?
- Yes.
[For fun]
- Taehyung, I'll go first.
- Jin should go first.
[So nervous]
- Is it Jin's turn?
- This is exciting.
[Everyone can't stand still]
[So nervous]
I'll keep my eye on j-hope.
I'll keep watching j-hope.
[Those with partners look so relaxed]
[Nervous vs Relaxed]
They say "out of the frying pan, into the fire"
j-hope, I'm telling you
this is a blessing.
1, 2, 3!
[Let's see]
j-hope!
[Rose between j-hope and V]
- That's so ambiguous.
- Hold on!
[It's j-hope as he got hit by the flower]
- I think it's V.
- Hobi was hit by the rose.
[The one who loves it
and the one who hates it]
[As long as it's not me]
Well!
You put yourself into this!
I'm a fashionista.
Trust me.
- Jin! I'll dress you up nicely.
- Really?
[A look that only the chosen can wear] [No]
Don't you want to wear these?
Let's go.
[Members are busy shuffling around]
[Scared...]
Jin is on the left side.
He's back to the center.
[Amazed]
[Can he see me? How did he know?]
[1, 2, 3] [Ready]
Ready?
[It fell in front of Jin,
as if they planned it]
[Amazing]
Awesome!
That's awesome.
[Jin and j-hope will be
stylists for each other]
He's scary!
[Both got the partners they wanted]
We're styling each other.
[j-hope found Jin with his instinct]
So, are we partners?
[Automatically RM and V are partners]
We'll be a pair.
[Got it]
- Right, you two are a pair.
- Right.
[In front of the clothes they will wear]
- Let's get into place!
- Let's go!
[Game result]
[Jimin -> Jung Kook -> SUGA -> Jimin]
[j-hope -> Jin,
Jin -> j-hope]
[RM -> V,
V -> RM]
[Introducing his style]
The style I prepared will change
depending on my partner's frame.
[I am?]
But he's somewhere in the middle.
[It depends on Jimin]
You can dress him however you like.
[Thinking hard]
I'm mulling between two outfits.
[No... I don't think so]
[Looking forward to seeing
Jung Kook's new style]
I've never seen him wear that.
[So enthusiastic]
I want to try this style.
[Jung Kook in pink]
- I've never seen him in pink.
- It will look nice.
OK.
[SUGA's pajamas are now unveiled]
I finally took out my pajamas.
[Jimin can wear these]
I think it'll fit him.
- We have similar sizes.
- I think it'll fit Jimin.
He can go to an award ceremony in these.
[SUGA's pajamas = award ceremony look?]
It's like a tuxedo.
I saved it for a special day like this
- I've never worn them.
- Never been worn.
[Even the price tag is on]
Even the price tag is still on.
[Great]
- I hope he wears these.
- Great.
[Looking forward to hearing Jin's concept]
- Seokjin.
- My look has a concept.
- What's that?
- It's coziness.
[Can't understand]
What made you think it looks cozy?
[Busy styling him]
- Don't you think pink layers will feel cozy?
- Why do you keep these shoes?
[What are those shoes?]
- I always wondered.
- They're old enough to get rid of.
[Hilarious]
It's so worn out.
[Confident]
Not worn out. They're just a bit stained.
[So proud]
I saved them for this day.
[Smelling]
Yuck!
No way. My feet never smells.
- It doesn't smell.
- I was planning on taking out some items
[j-hope's misery is my happiness]
but you need to wear them all.
- Congrats.
- This is amazing.
[The members don't understand the pants]
I can't understand.
[Curious]
Where did you get these pants?
[Fashion terminator]
Is this the end-all of fashion?
[j-hope's fashion will be unveiled soon]
- It's over.
- Fashion terminator.
Jung Kook, please introduce your style.
Do you remember these?
[Jung Kook's clothes
remind V of old memories]
It's very similar to the military costume
that we wore for the first
performance on "Show! Champion."
[They know Jung Kook's love for ensembles]
Jung Kook loves an ensemble.
He feels uneasy when his top
and pants are different.
[He needs a bag to complete the look]
He should've brought the Bon Voyage bag.
[Disappointed]
It's in the recording studio.
So I couldn't bring it.
Personally, I don't like the camouflage print.
[Sorry?]
- This is not camo.
- They're trees.
[Jung Kook has been wearing a piece of art]
It's a piece of art, a drawing of trees.
- Right.
- Jung Kook bought an artwork.
[Next, j-hope's outfit]
- Next... These are mine.
- I can't wait to see them.
- So pretty.
- Who gave you this T-shirt?
[Jacket matched with T-shirt from Jimin]
Jimin gave it to me as a gift.
Hoseok likes to play soccer.
I've never worn this type of hat.
[The accent piece to j-hope's outfit]
- This is the best part.
- The accent piece.
[What's that?]
- This is the icing on the cake.
- You can't leave this out.
- j-hope!
- That's the accent piece.
- Why are these socks so...
- I got them from the laundry basket.
- I asked our manager and he got me these.
- They're so worn out.
[Another point to his style: Shoes]
- These are shoes?
- They're what make the outfit.
- There's something I don't understand.
- Yes.
[Can't understand]
- Why this bucket hat?
- It's a must-have item.
Because you're going fishing?
[j-hope's look is completed with this hat]
You need to cover up your face with
this hat. That will complete the look.
- To cover up the eyes.
- I didn't know these shoes were so heavy.
[Let me hold them]
- They're so heavy, like sand bags.
- Wow!
I visited my parents' in these.
My dad asked why
I was wearing aircraft carriers.
[So heavy]
- These must be made of lead.
- That's all for me.
[RM's turn]
- You know, I like a challenge.
- Yes.
[RM has never tried this look]
But I've never tried this look.
- It's a bit big.
- He's wearing it himself.
[RM takes off his clothes to wear it]
Let me wear this sweater.
[Expert on V]
V likes clean and neat styles.
Even when he wears oversized clothes,
[True]
he never wears loose clothes like this.
When you wear this,
you won't be afraid of winter in Russia.
[Empty laugh]
You can even visit Alaska.
[RM's outfit has great insulation]
You could sit in front of a fireplace.
[RM looks bigger]
Wow.
That's an unexpectedly challenging one.
[RM's unexpected look]
- I didn't expect this fit.
- And then a cap to finish...
Wow.
[It feels like he's in Alaska]
You can sing a carol.
When I saw it, I thought it wasn't bad
but the fit was a real problem.
[So burly]
- It makes him look so buff.
- I can go to Alaska now.
[Warm]
You look like you'd read poems
in front of a fireplace.
But I truly believe that
Taehyung can pull this off.
[Looking forward to V's transformation]
I've never seen him wearing such a look.
[Excited] [V's style]
- I'll look forward to it.
- OK.
- Let's see V's outfit.
- I didn't expect Namjoon to be my partner.
[Combination of an oversized jacket
and slim-fitting pants]
I prepared something slim-fitting.
[Is this the material that I know?]
- Is this stretch fabric?
- Yes.
[The pattern of the jacket draws attention]
- Paisley pattern on a jacket...
- Right.
Taehyung is the only one
who can pull this off.
Let me tell you this first.
[FYI, this is a birthday gift for Jin]
This is a birthday gift for Seokjin.
Do I wear it first?
[Coughing]
- Yes.
- Seokjin!
[Coughing at the shocking news]
- No, don't do that.
- He's in denial.
[V continues to introduce his clothes]
There's only one of its kind.
[Quietly spitting facts]
There's only one of its kind
but RM will wear it first.
And then you'll gift it to Jin?
[RM is just a model]
Think of him as just a model.
Think of me as a mannequin.
- Think of him as a mannequin.
- If he doesn't like it, will you return it?
[The receipt left my hands]
But I threw away the receipt.
If I wear this to "Music Bank,"
it will be all over the media.
- That's right.
- What would it say?
Fashionista, the best boyfriend look,
BTS Jin.
[Suspicious]
You always do that on
the way to "Music Bank!"
[Let's go and change]
All the looks were introduced.
Now we just need to wear them.
[While changing]
What do you think about Jung Kook?
Jung Kook?
- It looks great on him.
Right?
- It's the boyfriend look.
- I wanted to make him look great.
- RM, it's a bit unique.
- That's nice.
- Do I have to tuck my collar in or out?
- In! Try to look laid-back.
- I think Hobi will look great in this.
- It looks nice on Hobi.
- V looks great.
- Pretty.
It feels like V is wearing RM's clothes.
It's crazy! Jin is transforming!
- Jin looks great in that.
- How do I look?
Cool!
SUGA, roll up your pants.
- You're so cruel.
- Belt and a beanie hat. Perfect.
[7 No-Faces appeared after changing]
[Satisfied]
- I love it.
- I like the look.
I guess everyone likes
how they're dressed.
[Everyone is curious of his look]
Do you like your look?
I like the look.
Whatever you imagine, it's more than that.
[Today's star j-hope]
- You're the star of today.
- Right.
I got goosebumps while I was changing.
Because I coiled it up.
Right, that and the socks.
- The socks are tucked in.
- Right.
- That's all we'll reveal for now.
- It's amazing.
But I think everyone dressed
each other in their own style.
- It feels like only our faces are changed.
- Right.
[Keeping the pledge for
entering the Billboard Hot 100]
Let's enjoy this.
- Because we're doing this as a pledge.
- Right.
- Right, we didn't talk about it.
- Billboard Hot 100 chart.
I was going to say it at the end,
but our fans recommended that we do this.
That's how this came to be.
- Thank you, everyone.
- Let's enjoy this!
[Finally, time for Jimin to show his look]
Let's keep our promise.
- Jimin, ta-da!
- Wow, it looks nice.
[Cool] [Teasing]
You should've taken off the tag.
[Polite]
- How could I? It's yours.
- You can take it off.
[Model-like aura]
- As you can see...
- Their heights are similar
- Right.
- So the pants fit him well.
Jimin, it's like you're in an info-mercial.
[Perfect]
- That's the perfect fit.
- Give us a twirl.
He could go straight to an award ceremony.
- Jimin, it's perfect.
- It's very simple.
- It's not the style I usually wear.
- I don't wear it either.
[Jimin liked SUGA's clothes]
Anyway, I like it.
[Satisfied]
Thanks for styling me.
[Jimin's outfit for Jung Kook]
Jung Kook.
[Spoiler] [Excited]
- Jung Kook perfectly recreated Jimin's style.
- Right.
- Show us your look!
- Ta-da!
[Smiling]
Sweep your hair back.
[Good at imitating Jimin]
He looks awkward.
[Awkward]
[Praising the youngest]
- The fit itself is like Jimin.
- Show us how happy you are with the look.
[I am so happy]
[Ha ha]
[Posing like a model]
I've never worn this.
[Aren't you a model?]
Jung Kook, you look better than I thought.
- Really?
- It's nice.
Thank you.
[Kookie feels good at the compliment]
- I feel good.
- Jung Kook, tell us how you feel.
[Haha]
- I feel good.
- Good?
[How does SUGA look?]
SUGA, we're so thrilled to see your look.
[High expectations]
- SUGA in Jung Kook's fashion.
- Cool!
[SUGA's back draws attention]
There he goes! He's ready!
- Please show your look!
- The retro mood is back!
[Laughing out loud]
The retro mood is back!
[That's our SUGA]
It's amazing!
Attention, attention, at ease.
Attention.
[Hilarious]
Attention! Salute!
- It's a look you'd see in a movie.
- Right.
- My hair color goes well with it.
- Right, matching colors.
[Jung Kook's big picture]
I threw it to SUGA for a reason.
He can hide in the jungle.
- It's the perfect outfit for that.
- I could go on a safari, too.
[V's styling for RM (Feat. Jin's birthday gift)]
Taehyung dressed me in his usual style.
- Right.
- It's my birthday gift, right?
- Let's see.
- You can see it and evaluate it.
[Kim Daily can pull anything off]
Wow.
[V's trademark V]
- Not bad!
- V was wearing those pants just now.
[Cool]
- Yes, right.
- But it looks so pretty.
[Hobi takes a closer look at the shoes]
- My grandma wears a coat like this.
- This jacket is the main piece.
Whoa, I thought they were sneakers.
[Sandals + black socks]
He's wearing black socks with sandals.
[RM understands my fashion]
V seeks both comfort and style.
[Cool]
- You look like an artist.
- A painter.
[What's he about to show now?]
[SUGA takes care of the others]
Don't do that with the mic on.
[Embarrassed] [RM still continues]
If you take it off...
- Reversible style is back.
- I don't think so.
[Not bad]
- You can style it like this.
- It's nice.
[Realistic Jimin] [Wear it the right way]
No. Take it off now.
[RM's style for V]
This sweater makes you look
like you've worked out for 20 years.
[Curious]
Show us the look!
[So masculine] [V showing off his muscles]
Look at his arms.
Show us your arm.
[Did you work out before the shoot?]
[Body builder?]
He got shoulder muscles he always wanted.
[These are V's actual arms]
His arms are actually this slim.
[Never seen V in cargo pants]
- First time seeing you in cargo pants.
- Right.
- He wears slacks.
- He only wears slacks.
[j-hope's style for Jin]
- Please come up.
- The 2017 fashion terminator.
[Hobi is giving tips on how to pose]
- Remember the pose? Roll up the left side.
- Got it.
There he goes!
[Unveiled]
[Jin, can you see?]
Really...
Among the looks that we've seen...
Don't crack any dad jokes in this look.
[Endless questions]
Did you buy the pouch to match the shoes?
The colors matched unintentionally.
[Curious about what he uses it for]
What do you carry in the pouch?
- A card holder and lip balm.
- Isn't it the perfect size to carry a seal?
- Cool.
- I'm so satisfied.
[Great]
Jin, you look like a real fashionista.
[Jin gave up his eyes for fashion]
- Good.
- Cool.
[Jin's styling for j-hope]
[Nervous]
I'm more nervous than when
we were at the Billboard event.
[So excited]
Everything we've seen so far
is not fashion.
[Great maxim]
If you want to see the future of
Korea's fashion industry,
raise your head and look at j-hope.
1, 2, 3!
[Cozy style as if spring has come again]
[Eyes glaring like a model]
But he looks amazing.
[Clap]
He looks amazing.
These are not one pair of pants.
j-hope did a great job pulling this off.
- But Jin created an amazing look too.
- Jin did.
[It feels like one pair of pants]
With the pants tucked in,
it feels like two pants are one.
- Look.
- Tri-color pants.
The worn-out shoes look
like real vintage shoes.
[Powerful]
It's not over yet.
[This is "I-tucked-in-I-coiled-it-up" fashion]
I tucked everything in for stability.
Focus on how I coiled it up.
- Coiled it up.
- I didn't expect he would do this.
[Respect]
- Amazing.
- Seriously though...
[So hot] [Flooded with compliments]
This is really....
[Self-praise]
So nice.
[Hobi is still amazed by the look]
He tucked the socks in too.
- Please don't step on my coat.
- Sorry.
[Still happy even if his coat's stepped on]
Do you like it?
- Yes.
- Help me put the coat back on.
[Putting the coat back on]
Story-telling is important these days.
The story behind this look is coziness.
[What?]
- The story is coziness?
- Yes.
- What does that mean?
- Feeling cozy.
[Soullessly]
- Is it cozy?
- So cozy.
- Is it warm?
- Very warm.
[Teeth clenched]
It's warm!
[Model j-hope who wants to go down
and stylist Jin who's having fun]
I want to go down already.
I want to see Jung Kook
going outside in this outfit.
- He went out already.
- He does it all the time.
Why are you so big?
[Jung Kook finds his fashion funny]
You look like a fighter jet.
- Namjoon, will you wear that look someday?
- Sure.
[Of course]
- Let's wear the clothes we styled someday.
- Sure, we will.
What nonsense!
All right. Let's go walk on the runway.
[Before]
[After]
[This is BTS fashion week runway]
Go!
[First model Jimin]
[Cool] [So fashionable]
- Nice!
- Take it seriously.
[Perfect from head to toe]
[Even his back looks perfect]
His shadow looked like
the character from "Fashion King."
[Jimin's shadow that looks like
"Fashion King".
[Glaring eyes]
Cool.
[Enjoying it]
- Cool.
- Jimin is so cool.
[2nd model Jung Kook]
[You can see the Jimin in Jung Kook]
[His gaze does it all]
[FYI, this move is Jimin's
part in "Save ME"]
[Jimin laughs out loud
as Jung Kook impersonates him]
[Amazing, Jung Kook]
[Charming side profile]
[Even he himself finds it funny]
Wow, he looks just like Jimin.
[Way to go]
[3rd model SUGA]
[SUGA is glaring at the camera]
Go forward.
[Min Sijin who dreams of
being a descendant of the sun]
[Cool]
Wow!
[What is he doing?]
Look at that angle.
[SUGA looks so excited]
Excellent!
[Well done, SUGA]
Cool.
[SUGA, you need to strike a pose]
Pose, there.
[That was smooth]
Cool!
[4th model RM]
Namjoon!
[Wow] [He's so tall]
A real model!
[Swish]
[Wow wow]
What's that?
[What's that pose?] [Smiling]
What?
[I'm RM]
Oh, great!
[Chic ending pose]
Tight shot.
- What's he doing?
- Great.
[5th model V]
The muscle man's here.
[Calm walking]
Nice.
You look like you'd say
"To the room of truth!"
[Let me show you]
You look like a beast.
[Laughing out loud]
[Don't use your good looks like that, V]
[Unique pose]
[Everything is so chic]
- To the room of truth!
[Cool ending pose]
- Oh!
- Good!
[6th model Jin]
- Jin!
- Show us the fisher look.
[I refuse to look normal]
He's a dancing machine.
[Doesn't disappoint]
- Cool.
[Model aura]
Great! Show your pouch!
[Passionate designer's request]
[Top model in his mind]
[BTS' dancing machine]
That's our dancing machine.
[I love it]
He leads the new trend.
[Fashionista who uses a mic as a fashion item]
The mic looks like a fashion item.
[Jin makes the others laugh]
I can see only his lips.
[Finally, today's star appears]
Go! j-hope!
[The last model j-hope]
j-hope!
[The pink gives off cozy vibes from afar]
High-fashion terminator!
[Smiling]
Oh, cool.
[He looks great even in this look]
j-hope would look cool
even if he's standing still.
[The celebs are so satisfied with the show]
He's so cool.
[Powerful]
Amazing, j-hope.
[Too fantastic to approach]
[He's so amazing] [Like a pictorial]
[Like a professional model]
j-hope!
[Charming gaze] [Wink]
This is so cool.
[I love it]
- j-hope! - Can we go back to the runway?
[Time to walk all together]
Single file.
How can we go in single file?
Should I walk at the end?
[7 members start walking like models]
[International sunshine rainbow superstar]
[We're BTS!]
[V's amazing presence]
[Let's go back, V]
[Their gazes are like a pro model's]
[Will you please show your eyes?]
[Hard to get used to his big frame]
[Jimin & Jung Kook came back
from being models to being BTS]
[Big presence]
That's embarrassing.
[My pose never ends]
Do we keep going?
[SUGA thinks it's funny]
Everyone, RUN BTS will continue.
- RUN BTS!
[Our excitement will never end]
[Ba-dum ba-dum]
[Jung Kook is starting the engine]
- Jung Kook is starting the engine!
- He's revving up!
[Jin does not disappoint]
Jin is here!
[So excited]
[Bye]
See you next week!