[RUN BTS
Retro Variety Show - Part 1]
- RUN
- BTS!
[BTS in retro outfits?]
- Ho, ho!
- Why are we dressed like this?
Is this a special episode
for the "Reply" series?
- Deokseon's mom.
- I got tight curls today.
[Curly]
[Patrasche?]
Don't I look like
a milk or paper delivery boy?
[Jimin's outfit reminds us of "Dog of Flanders"]
- Flanders.
- Or "Black Rubber Shoes."
[Do you know that?]
- Riding a bicycle with a basket.
- I've seen it on TV.
[Mimicking Nello]
[Is that a compliment?]
You always look like an English teacher.
[RM's outfit doesn't look strange]
Isn't it your usual outfit?
- Right.
- You don't look strange.
[Admitting]
You're right.
[Surprisingly, they are his own clothes]
- These are mine.
- Really?
Jung Kook looks like a rich boy.
[Rich boy fashion]
Jung Kook, yours is the most modern.
[Modern Kookie]
- Great.
- What about Jin?
[Comedian]
Jin, are you Yoo Se-yoon?
- Poop color power?
- Poop color power!
[Like a college student]
- He looks like...
- A college student!
[Retro-mood items]
- Blue jeans.
- SUGA and V look awesome.
[Question]
Did people wear belts like that before?
[What's wrong with my belt?]
Was that a thing in 1988?
[Sad]
Is it just me or does he look shorter today?
[Me?]
You look like DAO from "Crazy Arcade."
[Compliments(?) for SUGA's outfit]
I can't understand his style.
- You look like a doll.
- The ugly doll in the car.
[Like this]
The one bobbing its head.
[What's the theme for RUN BTS?]
All right. What are we doing today
- in these outfits?
- What is it?
[Curious]
Today's theme for RUN BTS is
[Today's RUN BTS!]
going into retro variety shows.
Retro variety shows.
[Today's RUN BTS!
Reproduce variety shows from
the early to mid-2000s!]
[With MC SUGA, 2 teams will play
games from old variety shows]
[The losing team will be given
a penalty decided by the winning team]
[Let's go on a trip down memory lane!]
[Today's MC SUGA]
- MC Su!
- We don't know which is which
so please give these out one by one.
[What's that...?]
Are they any different?
[What?]
The sword recognizes its master.
[Various suspicions over a toy sword]
Something must be inside.
[Out of the blue]
- The colors must be different.
- What does a sword says when it's sorry?
- Sorry?
- Sworry.
Ha-ha. It's so funny.
[Understood later]
- Everyone, gather up.
- Sworry. Now I understood.
Let's pick a sword on a count of three.
[I've waited for this day]
- Here comes my sword!
- Half of the swords
have something different inside.
[Getting ready]
Please draw your sword on a count of three.
[Chattering]
- I've been waiting 10 years for this day!
- 1, 2.
- 3!
- Here comes my sword!
[Normal sword]
Here it comes!
[Leek swords vs normal swords]
Here comes my sword!
- Leek?
- Leek!
[Surprised]
Team Leek, gather up.
[Well-balanced teams]
- This team...
- It's well-balanced.
- But it's Jin's team.
- What are you talking about?
[Still making noise]
Team Seokjin is the best team.
[Summarizing] [Noisy]
Everyone, please decide your team name.
[It's fun]
I'll collect the swords.
[Can't proceed]
Focus, guys!
[Dad SUGA is caring for his childish sons]
Give me yours.
[Deja vu]
- Let's move on.
- Our team name is Kim Seokjin.
[To decide the team name]
- Let's play rock paper scissors.
- Let's play it.
- Rock paper scissors!
[Won again]
Rock paper scissors! Rock paper scissors!
Our team name has been decided.
[Team Kim Seokjin]
- What's your team name?
- It's "Kim Seokjin."
Our team name is Glasses.
[Amazed]
- Oh, right!
- They're all wearing glasses!
[Firm]
- What about Glasses vs non-glasses?
- Nope. We're Team Kim Seokjin.
[Team Glasses vs Team Kim Seokjin]
Team Kim Seokjin vs Team Glasses.
[Teams decided by drawing swords]
[Team Glasses: Jung Kook, RM, V
Team Kim Seokjin: Jin, Jimin, j-hope]
- Everyone.
- Penalty.
Let's decide the penalty.
[BTS decides the penalty in advance]
Let's each suggest a penalty.
[Suggesting an idea]
As we're dressed in the 80s style,
what about giving the penalty
from that era?
Let's take a walk on Garosu-gil street
wearing these.
Go to Macao wearing these.
[Macao?] [Amazed]
Go to Macao.
[Love it]
The losing team members will go to
Macao wearing these.
[BTS is slated to go to Macao tomorrow]
Dressed like this.
Everyone will play hard to win.
[Thinking hard]
Hairstyle, too?
- No. You can wear a cap.
- Hairstyle is up to you.
What about doing that
for penalty?
[Sure, why not?]
- I'm OK with that.
- Hey, that's my hat.
[Amazing]
I'll write "This is Kim Taehyung's hat."
[Deal!]
- I'll do it if Jimin does.
- Anyways, the penalty is...
[Nervous]
- Let's do this when we arrive in Macao.
- When we arrive?
What about going to bed in this outfit?
- And going straight to Macao like this?
- I think
[No! Let's wear it when we depart]
I think we should wear it when we depart.
Fashion lovers dress up
on their way to the airport.
[We know that]
- That's why it's a penalty.
- I admit.
That's why it's the penalty...
[Confident]
If you don't like it, win the game.
As long as it's not me.
[Right]
I don't care as long as it's not me.
- What about SUGA?
- He's wearing glasses.
- If we lose, SUGA will join us.
- If he agrees, we'll agree too.
[Straight face]
No way.
[Bet on the team he thinks will win?]
Or we'll give you the right to choose.
- Pick one team that you think will win.
- Write it down in advance.
[My fate is in my hands]
- I'll write it down.
- Yes, write it down.
- Write the team name.
- I'll write it down.
If I write a team name,
[Great MC SUGA]
I may show favoritism to that team.
[Jung Kook's flat refusal]
Nobody asked.
[Oh, is that what you want?]
All right, let's do this.
- So, the penalty is decided.
- Departure or entry?
But the MC has a point.
[Right]
If the MC decides a team, he may be unfair.
[MC SUGA will pick one team and
follow the result of that team]
[It's not fair]
Why are you dragging me into this?
Because you choose one team.
[SUGA at a crossroads]
[I trust myself] [On a winning streak]
I've been on a winning streak.
[Which team will he choose?]
- Don't show the team name.
- Give it to the crew.
Give it to them.
All right. It's fair.
Don't change it.
[Nervous] [Don't you trust us?]
- It's going to be fun.
- Show the team name.
[SUGA chose Team Glasses]
Don't change it.
It's going to be fun
if he chose the losing team.
[Expecting]
- Will it be Glasses or Kim Seokjin?
- Let's make it clear.
[Let's make it clear]
- On the way to the airport.
- Only on departure.
[Sure]
- It's tomorrow.
- Yes.
These are cute.
I'll tuck it into the pants.
[#Shirt_tucking_fashion]
It looks trendy.
Hoseok's is just his usual style.
[RM and V complaining]
He'll wear a fancy cap over it.
[Words of consolation]
Yours is fine too.
[RM starts complaining]
- I'm wearing a purple turtleneck!
- I've never seen jeans in this shade.
[Members got sensitive]
I've never worn such a belt in my life.
[V's style]
Didn't you choose this belt yourself?
[He chose this belt by himself]
You chose it yourself.
[Nothing to say]
Only because we had to
dress in retro style...
[Moving on]
Let's play the games.
[Hehe]
- You brought it onto yourself.
- Let's shout out "RUN BTS" together.
[Into memory lane!]
RUN BTS!
This is the long-awaited moment!
[Retro dance]
Team Kim Seokjin vs Team Glasses.
[So excited]
[Team Glasses vs Team Kim Seokjin]
[A quick talk before the games
just like the old times!]
Please do your best. We can't lose.
What did you do on your vacation?
I went to the beach.
[Kim Seokjin(26) Man of the sea]
I went into the water in
a short-sleeve top and shorts.
[Bragging]
Those in padded coats took pictures of us.
- Really? So, j-hope.
- Yes.
If you could go back in time, when will you
go back to and what will you do?
[Unexpected answer]
- I'd go back to before I learned to dance.
- Why? You don't want to dance?
- You don't like dance?
- No, that's not what I meant.
I thought I might try studying.
[Oh, you want to study?]
- Wow. - Study...
[I'mma start studying ♪]
j-hope!
[Literature boy]
Which subject?
My dad is a literature teacher.
So that's what I want to study.
[Sudden suggestion]
Recite a poem for us on the spot.
Poem, by j-hope.
[High expectations]
- The title is poem?
- Yes.
What the...
[Masterpiece]
[Very satisfied] [Standing ovation]
All right, thank you.
[What the...
Short but impressive poem]
[He would mark a milestone in
Korean literature if he can turn back time]
[He's amazing]
Cool.
[Calm down]
Taehyung, what did you do in 2000?
- I was 5 years old.
- Really?
- 6 years old.
- You were old enough.
I was born in 1995
so I was 5 in 2000.
You were 5 in the Millennium?
[5? 6? 7? Controversy over age]
- Not 7?
- No, 6.
[95z refutes]
- 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
- He was 6.
[Thinking hard]
- 6 years old.
- That's correct, you were 6 years old.
You need to feel like
you are in the 1990s.
Do you know that?
Do you know the variety shows
that were popular in the early 2000s?
[Early 2000s?]
Shows that were popular in the early 2000s?
- "X Man!"
- "Match Made in Heaven!"
- What's that... In the cabin?
- "Love Letter"
- "Love Letter".
- "Rose in the Cabin?"
- "X Man"
- "Live and Enjoy Together"
[Been a while since we've heard that]
- "Infinite Challenge"
- "Conscientious Refrigerator"
[He was four...]
- Right. - I can't remember any.
[Legendary Hidden Camera]
- "Hidden Camera"
What was the show where the cast
played the Kung Kung Ta game?
[Quiet shout]
- "Family Outing!"
- "Alien Baseball Team"
[Confused]
Alien Baseball Team? Alien Kung Kung Ta?
- Happiness of 10 won.
- It was "Happiness of 10,000 won"
[It's hard to be happy with 10 won]
What can you buy with 10 won?
- You need to go back to the Enlightenment Era.
- "Exclamation Mark!"
[OK, I got it]
- I see.
- "Magic Kid Masuri"
[Endless list]
There were a lot of variety shows
[Variety shows were popular in the 2000s]
and TV programs.
- That's enough talking for now.
- All right.
[Expecting]
What was a common feature in these shows?
[The opening was the highlight]
- "X Man"
- The opening section.
[Expecting]
It's none other than the dance ceremony.
The dance ceremony.
[That's it!]
I heard we have a lot of
amazing songs prepared.
As soon as you hear it,
you will say, "Oh, I know this song."
[I get a feeling]
I think I know what songs would play.
[Boyz with Fun are already excited]
[Especially this person]
[I'm so excited]
Everyone,
the best dancer Jin will start off.
[Feeling pressured]
- Starting from Jin.
- Let's take turns.
Dance up here?
[MC Swag]
Come forward to the podium
and dance when a song plays.
[Make way!
The dancing prince is coming up]
[I live for the stage...]
Kim Seokjin!
He will eat up the stage!
[Illusion]
[Chocolate wings?
Flapping his wings to fly to ARMY]
[Cool exit]
- Great!
- I'm done.
[Next turn, V]
V!
[Wiggle]
[Instinct to seduce]
[Amazed] [His dance instinct is not
affected by the abrupt change in music]
[Good, this is it]
This song is awesome.
[Ambitious face that doesn't
reveal what is in his mind]
- Embarrassing.
- Next, dance machine Jimin!
[Wow!]
[Oh?]
[Can you see this?
My body is dance itself]
[Go! Jimin!]
[So immersed]
What's this dance?
What's that?
[Exciting dance time]
[Dancing whatever party]
Good!
[Tired]
Nice!
[Best leader RM]
RM!
[Legend] [This song is...?]
[The song that catches their ears]
Gotta get that!
[Gotta get that!]
[A collab between the soulful camera walk]
[And dance prodigy RM]
[Dance dance]
Here it comes!
- Featuring.
- Wow!
Sexy and provocative!
[One attracted by RM]
[Another attracted by RM]
The next one is a real dance machine.
[Did you call me?]
I think I should go first.
[Special footsteps]
The song will change.
[He smells like dance!]
[I'm here to take the year 2017!]
What's this song?
[His name is j-hope]
[Ho!]
[I need a dance!]
[Way to go, j-hope!]
Hope evangelist.
[Hope evangelist j-hope]
j-hope!
[Joint check]
[Cute pose to finish] [So satisfied]
That was good!
[Golden Maknae Jung Kook]
Jung Kook!
[Oh?]
[I got it]
Forget the naive youngest member!
[This is a whole new Jung Kook!]
[Who would think he's the youngest!]
[So immersed]
Good!
Great!
[Nobody can stop his
endless passion for dance]
[The MC can't miss the welcoming ceremony]
MC!
[Music stopped]
[We planned to play a special
song for SUGA]
[Can I start?]
[I'm SUGA!]
[Robot dance]
He looks like a cartoon character.
[So excited] [Full of talent]
He's good.
I'm looking forward to
seeing today's MC.
[Everyone was satisfied with
the dance ceremony]
- All right.
- I'm tired.
[It's not over yet]
Now we need to play a game.
[Surprised] [Are we just starting?]
- Wasn't this the game?
- No?
[Don't act like an amateur]
- I did my best.
- This was an opening section.
What we're going to do
is the pre-game.
- Not the real game.
- What's that?
The pre-game is...
[A strange game: Losing wrestling]
It's "Losing wrestling."
- Losing wrestling?
- I think I played this before.
[Games from old variety shows]
[: Losing wrestling]
[The one whose back touches
the ground first wins]
[The winning team can pick
a member from the opposing team
to play in the next round]
Should we get right to it?
[Glare]
- Are you confident?
- If you're confident, please come forward.
[Seokjin will start]
Jin will go first,
since we're Team Kim Seokjin.
[Spaced out]
- Jeon Jung Kook.
[Me?]
Please come forward.
Why him?
[Round 1]
Jung Kook from Team Glasses
vs Jin from Team Kim Seokjin]
Everyone, ready?
[Fumbling]
- Are you ready? - Where are you?
Tell us how you feel.
[Fast progress]
Oh, I see.
- Ready?
- Yes.
Hang on.
[Why did you skip him?]
Ask Jin too.
How do you feel?
[Cute]
- Go, Kim Seokjin!
- You need to stand up.
Ready, go!
[Falling down as soon
as the game started]
[Dangle]
You lost.
[Team Kim Seokjin's victory]
- Game over.
- Kim Seokjin won!
You're a good loser.
- Kim Seokjin's the best.
- You're a good loser.
- Jung Kook.
- That's Kim Seokjin.
I think you're talented
in losing wrestling.
[Proud Jin]
We lost but it was a good game.
- It was too short.
- Next.
[Surprised] [Stopping him]
It's not your turn.
It's a tournament.
[Jin chose V]
- You can name your opponent.
- V, come here.
Please kneel down.
[Round 2] [V from Team Glasses
vs Jin from Team Kim Seokjin]
- This is a warm-up.
- A pre-game.
[Don't worry]
- We have a lot of games to play.
- I think
there's no need for me to play this.
[Serious]
- Jin loses easily.
- Just like his name.
[Jin lives up to his name]
Kim Seokjin from Team Kim Seokjin.
- He lives up to his name.
- Yes.
[Struggling]
- Did you hold it?
- Who tied it so hard?
[Flinched]
Ready.
[Revenge]
Ready, go!
[Just like being shot]
[So smooth]
[What's up with him?] [Recognition 1]
He's talented.
[Recognition 2]
He's talented at losing.
[The king of losing wrestling]
[Jin found his talent]
He's amazing.
Me?
[Round 3]
[RM from Team Glasses
vs Jin from Team Kim Seokjin]
- Ready. - Ready.
- Please stand up.
- I think he did it to look cool.
- Stand up.
[Aiming to win 3 times in a row?]
Let's win 3 times in a row.
Ready. Go!
Go!
[Surprised Kook]
[Dumbfounded]
- Why did you apply the technique?
- Go!
[Technique?]
[Happy-go-lucky]
[Why did I do that?]
[Excited] [I saw it]
Seriously, he applied a technique.
- I didn't expect that.
- You didn't?
[Look at him]
[Confused RM]
He won but it didn't feel great.
It was a good match.
[Amazed]
His technique was awesome.
I've never seen such a neat technique.
- Did I win or lose?
- You won.
[RM brought victory to Team Glasses]
Let's move on to the next round.
Jimin, kneel down.
[Round 4] [RM from Team Glasses
vs Jimin from Team Kim Seokjin]
[Starting to dragging down]
Ready.
[Surprised by his overly confident play]
That's too much.
[Surprised]
- That's too much.
- Wait a minute.
I was standing and
he started doing this.
[RM has nothing to say]
It's just a pre-game.
There's no need to be so competitive.
Let's go again.
Go!
No...
[Automatic sleeping mode]
[Are you OK? Were you surprised?]
You got kicked in the butt. Are you OK?
He can't say.
The winner of the pre-game
is Team Kim Seokjin!
- Kim Seokjin!
- Great, Team Jin!
[Today's game is not over yet]
However,
This was just the pre-game.
[Now for the real games!] [Amazing]
Was it just for fun?
Sure.
[Moving on]
Have you heard of
this next game?
It's the cushion game.
- The cushion game.
- Bringing one fast and sitting on it?
No. This is the game from a variety
show in the past.
[The game from old variety shows]
[ Cushion game]
[Step 1: Listen to the question]
[Step 2: If you know the answer,]
[Raise your cushion over your head
and say the team name]
[Step 3: If it's correct, you win]
[Team Kim Seokjin who won the pre-game
can choose their opponent]
That's how it goes.
[Understood] - I see.
- When is my turn?
[Team Kim Seokjin's member will
choose his counterpart]
Team Kim Seokjin's member
will sit on the cushion.
[Oh]
- And point out their opponent.
- I see.
j-hope, will you go first?
Because you didn't play last time.
Sure, will it be OK if I lose?
- It won't be OK.
- As it's a tournament...
[Confused] [Are you confident or not?]
- You should be confident.
- Right.
- Stay there as long as you can.
- Go, j-hope!
Who will you choose?
[Cushion game with a quiz]
It's a quiz.
We have various questions prepared.
[Thinking hard]
This is... Well...
[Quietly]
V, I choose you.
[j-hope pointed out V]
- j-hope chose V.
- Taehyung, come here.
Don't you need a stare-off?
[j-hope is good at stare-offs]
I'm good at that.
[Nervous]
I'm the king of stare-offs.
1, 2, 3.
[Unstirred]
- Think you can beat me?
- Let me give you a quiz.
[Battlefield of the two]
All right.
This song is famous for 333.
- Is this the quiz?
- Yes.
[Thinking hard]
- 333?
- What is the title of that BTS song?
No.1. If it's on fire.
- No.2.
- Should I grab this?
Before it's on fire.
No.3. Don't let it be on fire.
[Listening carefully]
No.4.
[Funny]
Whether it's on fire or not.
No.5. Is it on fire?
- Good.
- No.6. Fire or not.
So many choices!
- How can we know?
- Kim Seokjin!
[Let's guess]
- Team Kim Seokjin.
- Just guess.
No.9. Fire.
[So bold]
No.9, Fire.
[Please]
[It can't be the answer]
[Surprised] [Bingo]
Correct.
[Even j-hope is surprised too]
- Correct.
- Really?
Correct.
[Where am I? Who am I?]
I thought it would be no.7.
- We're so lucky!
- Amazing.
[I'm the lucky j-hope]
- Didn't you read the script?
- I just took a guess.
[How can he?]
- I think the name "Kim Seokjin" is lucky.
- I didn't show the script.
[Should I go to my seat?]
How dare you...
- You're out.
- Taehyung, please go back to your seat.
[Comforting him]
- Next member.
- Did you lose your confidence?
Come on in.
[What's this concept? Tell us...]
Way to go!
Please pick another member.
- Jung Kook, come on out.
- Well...
Jung Kook.
[I am chosen]
If he loses, we need to go.
I think there's something
about Team Kim Seokjin.
[I'm j-hope]
- They're lucky.
- Right, it happened last time.
[A mystery]
- If a team is named "Kim Seokjin,"
- We went up to the top.
[Parallel theory?]
- everything goes well.
- We never lose.
This quiz is also about entertainment.
[Out of the blue]
Think you can beat me?
[He's at it again]
Jung Kook, you can stare.
[Innocent] [Staring]
Let me read the question.
[He's not easy to win]
- He's a strong opponent.
- BTS member V's first drama
[Difficulty level: High]
- was "Hwarang."
- It's difficult.
It's difficult.
What was the name of V's role?
[What?]
- No.1!
- I guess they don't know.
- I bet both of them don't know.
- No.1!
[Amazed by SUGA's faking skills]
Han Character.
No.2. Han Seongsan Ilchulbong.
[Relaxed]
No.3. Han Seongsil.
[Guessing]
No.3? I'll just guess. Do you trust me?
[Let's go]
- May I?
- Just go ahead.
No.4. Han Seong-gong.
[Hi-ya]
- No.5.
- Team Glasses.
[Say it]
- Yes?
- No.6, Hanseong.
[Will the guessing gods
be with him this time?]
[Tilt]
Wrong.
[Now!]
- Kim Seokjin! - Kim Seokjin.
- I know the answer. Do you trust me?
- We do.
[We trust you, j-hope!]
j-hope!
[May luck be with me]
[Ceremony to gain energy]
I need to check its energy.
[Admit]
If he gets it right, it's going to be epic.
No.7, Hanseong.
[Will the goddess of luck
be on the side of j-hope?]
[Reading] [Oh...?]
Wrong.
No.5 is... Han Seonghami.
[What's that?]
No.6. Han Seongjang.
[Nothing else?] [The end?]
No.7, Han Seong...
- Team Glasses!
- is so handsome.
[Team Glasses already shouted]
You said Team Glasses.
[Just guessing] [Bingo]
- No.8 Hanseong.
- Correct.
[I won!]
[Lying down]
You gave him a chance.
Now, Jung Kook can point to his opponent.
Can I do it like Hobi?
[Hobi style]
Park Jimin, come on out.
[I'm older than you]
Talk in honorifics.
About just now,
[Current score 1:1]
I want to apologize.
- Hang on. Did you know it's 1:1?
- From now on,
the questions are a bit challenging.
[Challenging?]
Is it difficult?
[Ready]
- The questions are difficult.
- Oh, my.
In the police station episode
of "RUN BTS"...
- Do you remember that?
- I do.
Jin was charged with two crimes.
[I know]
- I know.
- What was the crime?
This is too difficult.
- Was there a name to the crime?
- Is it a short-answer question?
[Multiple choice question]
This is a multiple choice question.
[Hearing for the first time]
- I can't remember.
- No.1.
For being world wide handsome.
[I love it]
- That makes sense.
- Reasonable.
No.2. For having a crazy handsome look.
- That sounds nice.
- That's plausible.
[Too long]
- Can you even remember the choices?
- That's what I'm saying.
- The one who can remember will win.
- The second crime?
- Yes.
- Oh.
No.3. Acting like a dad.
[Feeling accused]
I've never done that. Don't look at me.
No.4. For stealing ARMY's hearts
with his broad shoulders and handsome face.
[That's it]
Jung Kook!
[Jung Kook raised his cushion]
- Jung Kook, no.4.
- Jimin! Raise it!
[Confused]
- Team Glasses.
- What was it?
[Not allowed to share the answer]
Don't say.
[The player needs to answer on his own]
Don't help him.
With his broad shoulders...
Kim Seokjin!
No.4!
With his broad shoulders,
he stole....
[Hint]
Jung Kook, the prepositional
particle was wrong.
- Team Glasses!
- I know!
[What was that...]
Can't remember.
[Kind SUGA's replay]
- Crazy.
- Let me read the choices again.
No.4. For stealing ARMY's hearts
with his broad shoulders and handsome face.
- Kim Seokjin!
- Team Glasses!
[Raising the cushion]
- Team Kim Seokjin!
- Team Glasses!
Jimin said it faster, to be honest.
[Was it that obvious?]
[Proud]
- You need to get it exactly right.
- For stealing the hearts of ARMY
with his broad shoulders and handsome face.
[Merciless]
- Team Glasses!
- Wrong!
- I know.
- For bombing the hearts of ARMY
with his broad shoulders and handsome face.
Bombing...
[Dauntless Jung Kook challenges again]
- Why did you bomb....
- Team Glasses!
[I think this is correct]
For stealing ARMY's hearts with
- his broad shoulders and handsome face.
- There you go!
- Wrong.
- No?
[Surprisingly]
We have 7 choices.
[What?]
- Why not...
- This isn't the answer?
- Why are you spending all your energy now?
- Team Glasses!
- Is it acting like a dad?
- Acting like a dad.
- Which number?
- No.3. Acting like a dad.
- Wrong.
- I guess that's not it.
No.5. For being super handsome.
[Everything sounds like the answer...]
Team Glasses!
No.5, for being super handsome.
[MC is trying to give hints]
It's about time for the real answer.
No.6.
Oh, I'm an old man over 40.
[What's that?]
This...
[He himself is surprised]
- This is not it.
- Of course not.
- I know.
- Kim Seokjin.
No.6, Oh, I'm an old man over 40.
- Wrong.
- Team Glasses.
- No.1! For being world wide handsome.
- Wrong.
- This was before the Billboard event.
- Right.
No.7. Min Yoongi.
[This is it!]
Jimin!
[No?]
No.7. Min Yoongi.
[Wrong]
No.8.
You said we have 7 choices.
- Did you lie?
- No.8.
Old maaan.
- Jeon Jung... Team Glasses!
- Jim... Kim Seokjin!
[Confused]
[What's wrong with them?]
- Team Glasses!
- Kim Seokjin!
[MC's call]
[Team Glasses got a chance]
Team Glasses.
- OK.
- No.8, Old maaan.
[Out!]
- Wrong.
- No.8.
No.8! Kim Seokjin!
- That hurts my feelings.
- Old maaan.
[Wrong!]
[What's the answer?]
No.9.
- Old man.
- Team Glasses.
[Right?]
No.9, Old man.
[Ding Dong]
- What's the difference?
- No.8 was maaan.
- Maaan?
- No.9 was man.
Man.
- No.8 was Man?
- It was maaan.
- Then, no.3 was dad?
- It was just dad.
Please pick the next opponent.
[Jung Kook is tired]
This is tiring.
Jin, you should go.
Next question.
What is the title of the song that RM,
Jin, and Jung Kook sang during the MT episode?
- OK.
- Short-answer question?
[No! This is a multiple choice question]
This is also a multiple choice question.
- Multiple choice.
- Let's try.
[The members encourage him to take a guess]
- Just take a guess.
- You know the answer.
[Thud]
[Jin takes a wild guess.
Kim Seokjin. No.7 Memory of the Wind.
[Stern] [Wrong]
Team Glasses.
No.5, Memory of the Wind.
[One more time]
Team Glasses!
[No]
Kim Seokjin. No.8, Memory of the Wind.
[Hang on]
Let's hear the choices first.
No.1. Wind of Train.
- Wind of Track?
- Wind of Train.
[Dumbfounded]
No.2. Sound of Wind.
[Fake?]
No.3... But it's too early
to say the right option.
[It's not]
- No.3. Memory of the Wind.
- He fell for that again.
No.4. Kim Seokjin,
Memory of the Wind.
No.3. Wind, Blow.
- No.4. I Hope Wind Blows.
- Try the farthest one.
[Reading letters carefully]
No.5, Wind Wind Wind.
[When will it come out?]
No.6?
The Place Where Wind Blows.
No.7. Memory of the Wi...
- Team Glasses!
- Kim Seokjin!
No.7 Memory of the Wind.
Kim Seokjin.
No.8, Memory of the Wind.
[Amazed by SUGA's great MC skills]
The previous one was "Memory of the Wild."
What's that?
[You're really doing this to us?]
[Even he finds it funny]
No.8 was Memory of the Wild.
Memory of the Wild?
W-i-l-d, wild.
[Hurried]
- No.9! Memory of the Wind.
- No.9! Kim Seokjin!
- Kim Seokjin!
[Jung Kook didn't say the team name]
- He said no.9.
- He didn't say Glasses!
[Confirming the fact]
- No.9!
- He said no.9.
No.9, Memory of the Wind.
[That was the correct answer]
- Kim Seokjin!
- Team Glasses!
I should have said the team name
but I just said no.9.
Team Kim Seokjin.
It's all no.9!
Name five Korean
solo singers in five seconds.
- Glasses! Na Eol, Yoon Geon...
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
[Out!]
[Hurried]
I didn't say anything.
- No.
- Kim Seokjin! I didn't say my name yet.
[Cool-headed] [Checking time]
- I'm counting down since you're holding it.
- Kim Seokjin!
- RM, SUGA, Jung Kook, V....
- 1, 2, 3.
[Hey] [He's actually right]
- Solo.
- We have solo albums.
- Glasses! - 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Na Eol, Yoon Gun, Kim Beomsoo,
BMK, Park Hyo Shin.
[Perfect]
Correct!
[Doing the ceremony]
Great.
[Flop] [So passionate]
- RM at the end...
- He must really not want
- to dress like that to the airport.
- No way.
Good, good.
[Team Glasses won the cushion game!]
- The next game is...
- Yes.
[Steel case game]
Have you heard of the steel case game?
[What's that?]
- Steel case?
[Game from way back when]
- Kim Seokjin!
- That was so fast.
I just blinked and it closed!
[BTS learned how to play
the legendary Kung Kung Ta game]
[The CEO's name?]
Bang Si-Hyuk, 1, 2, 3.
"Bang Si-Hyuk" is doable.
- Thank you, Director Bang!
- Bang is hard.
[BTS Youth Group is back
with the half-asleep quiz]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8.
♪ I will dance ♪
Why? Why are you mad at me?
[Gripping competition to avoid the penalty]
- It's not my fault.
- ♪ I'll dance! Dance! ♪
- Cool.
- No?
I did it first.
[What will happen to SUGA?
What will happen to Min Yoongi?]
[RUN BTS! Retro Variety Show - Part 1]