[Run BTS!
Variety shows from the past - Part 2]
[Previously on Run BTS
Variety shows from the past!]
[Jin's surprising talent in losing]
He's talented
He's talented in losing
You're great at losing
[Fierce competition to avoid the penalty]
Kim Seokjin!
Number 9, guy
[Team Glasses is leading right now..]
Correct!
I can see your will of not wanting to
wear these outfits to the airport
I will never
Have you heard of this?
[Heard of it? Steel case bag game]
- Steel case bag game
- Steel case bag?
- What's that?
[Games from old variety shows!]
[Second game: Steel case bag game]
[Game where an object will be placed
inside the steel case bag]
[and you have to guess what it is
when the MC quickly opens and closes it]
[The team that correctly answers
2 out of 3 questions will win!]
[I remember that game]
That brings back old memories
[Is this the generation gap?]
I don't know what it is
- He opens it up and we guess
- I know this game
- Are you all set?
- I'm ready!
- I have keen eyesight
- Please bring the bag in
[How keen-eyed j-hope looks at
a steel bag]
- One player from each side
- Bring the steel bag in please
[j-hope recommends a rehearsal for the MC]
Why don't you give it a try?
- Let me open and close it
- Open and close
[The members watching his rehearsal]
[Worried]
Can they guess this?
Is it difficult?
[Fumble]
[No worries]
I think we can, SUGA
[Fumble]
Good
That's easy
It'll pass by in the blink of an eye
- Are we starting?
- Get ready
Start!
- What was it?
- Glasses
[Confident]
Body scrub towel
Wrong
- Kim Seokjin
- You can only see the bottom
[Not sure]
- A pencil
- Wrong
All I could see was the bottom section
[Stern]
- There's no other section
- Really?
Somebody got pretty close
- One of the answers was close
- V
- Ah!
- No giving away the answer
[I'm sure]
Glasses! Exfoliating towel
Wrong
Kim Seokjin
[No, this is the answer]
- Crayon
- Wrong
[Are you ready?]
Get ready
[We'll reveal the answer to you first]
[Sponge]
[I didn't see a thing]
- That was so quick
- I'm not lying
But it was gone after
a blink of an eye
- I just heard the noise
- Glasses
[Pretty close]
- Chalkboard eraser
- Wrong
One more time
[Eyes wide open]
Hang on, my eyes are very dry
[V, your eyes might pop out]
Don't blink
[Let me try]
Do not blink
Get closer
[Lightning speed]
[Blink]
[Huh?]
I can't see anything
- I can't see anything
- Answer
[I don't get it]
- I know what it is
- You do?
Answer!
[Strict MC starts counting]
3, 2, 1
- A mechanical pencil!
- Wrong. Here we go
My eyes hurt!
[Master of teasing the members]
Kim Seokjin!
[Absolutely sure]
A towel!
- No, it's something else
- Wrong
- That was close
- You know that
[Spaced out. What is it?]
- You know it, V!
- I'm not allowed to answer, right?
I can't believe you don't know that
- Glasses
- It's driving me crazy
[Not confident]
The thing you use to wash dishes
Wrong
[Could it be?]
Kim Seokjin, a sponge
Correct
[Team Kim Seokjin embrace
each other in joy]
[V is still puzzled]
A sponge
[j-hope's victory ceremony]
- He couldn't remember the word
- It's 1:0
[Dumbfounded]
What's a dish washing thing?
Come to the center
[j-hope's advice]
Watch carefully, Jimin
Keep your eyes open
[Jimin is waiting with his eyes wide open]
Here we go
[Focused]
[Peek-a-boo]
Here we go
[Spaced out]
- Team Glasses!
- Answer
- A shoe insole
- Correct
Awesome!
[A shoe insole]
[Jung Kook quickly saw it]
That's awesome
[Puzzled]
It's 1:1
[Amazed by the youngest's sharp eyes]
[Is it my turn?]
Jin and RM have important roles
[An immersive steel case bag game]
- Okay
- Next round
It's 1:1 now
This is getting interesting
Here we go
[Advice]
Keep your eyes wide open
Don't blink
[The most passionate player]
Everyone
- Kim Seokjin!
- Glasses!
- A microphone
- Wrong
- Glasses
- Earphones
- Wrong
- One more time, please
- One second
1, 2...
[We'll give you the answer first
this time as well]
[A mask that SUGA crumpled]
[I can't see anything]
I can only see the left corner
I'm in a blind spot
[These two have no idea either]
- That's in my blind spot
- Answer
That's what happened to me
when I was sitting on the floor
- Kim Seokjin
- Answer
[Is it right?]
- Telephone wire
- Wrong
- Glasses
- Answer
[Everything but the answer]
- A charger
- Wrong
Kim Seokjin, a cell phone cradle
[MC SUGA says "Wrong" right away]
- Wrong
- I have no idea
- I thought so too
- So did I
But this is so...
[Frustrated] [What is that?]
I saw it, but I don't know what it is
[A familiar item?]
You're very familiar with this item
[I know!]
- I think I know what it is
- Me too, but we can't tell Jin
One more time
[Like this]
At this speed
[The leader and eldest are super focused]
- What is it?
- Look carefully
[Slide]
[Smash]
What is that thing?
[RM doesn't know while Jimin
and j-hope find it funny they disappear]
[Doesn't know what it is
but laughs along with them]
[Venting his frustration]
There's a black lump in there!
- Kim Seokjin
- Answer
- Hi-pass
- Wrong
Hi-pass? Come on
[Looks like j-hope knows the answer]
It's very close to us
- It's close to us?
- Really...
[It's this, everyone...]
[Except the 2 youngest]
[Everyone is focused]
Here we go, it's something black
No discussing it in the back
[So frustrating, I don't know what it is]
- Am I dumb?
- They might hear you, here we go
Argh!
What is that?
[The members suddenly cracking up?]
Glasses!
[Panic]
[Why won't it close?]
Glasses!
[Roar]
- A mask!
- Correct!
[Claiming they didn't yell the team name]
- You didn't say, "Glasses"
- He did
[Yes, we did]
He said, "Glasses"
[That was a rough game..]
Everyone
Why couldn't you tell it's a mask?
[Who would see that as a mask?]
[At a loss for words]
- That's a mask?
- Why didn't you know?
Come on
[Confident] [The one who crumpled the mask]
It's a mask
[Like this]
I didn't know what it was
even after I saw that
I had no idea even after
looking at it for 5 seconds
- I had no idea either
- It's obviously a mask
[Spaced out]
I guess we'll be wearing these clothes
[Team Glasses won 2:1!]
The victory goes to Team Glasses
[Curious]
How many games are left?
There are lots of games left
[You can turn the table around]
Don't worry
We have lots of games left
Everyone, the third game is...
- Kung Kung Ta?
- The legendary game?
It's Kung Kung Ta game
[Games from old variety shows!]
[Third game: Kung Kung Ta]
[The person the MC points to says a word
that begins with the designated letter]
[A word chain game with three-letter words]
[You can only earn points by
playing without any stops]
Let's start right away! The beginning
word is, "Gi." 5, 6, 7, 8
[Excited MC SUGA]
Kung Kung Ta Kung Kung Ta
[Nervous]
Kung Kung Kung Kung
Crane
Kung Kung Ta
Goose
Train ticket
Kung Kung Ta
Road sign
Pannepyo
Kung Kung Ta
Pyo Inbong
Bongseon...
[Yay] [j-hope's victory ceremony]
And that's how you lose
[He knows how to tease]
That was the practice game
- What a relief
- Right, garden balsam
[Disappointed]
- Come on
- I thought you'd answer that
[Please pay attention to SUGA]
[No one is listening]
Like this...
[Whisper]
What did you say?
[Huh? Nothing]
Me? Road sign
- Did you say road sign?
- Pannepyo
Pannepyo?
What does that even mean?
- Pannepyo?
- Ticket
If the answer is ambiguous like that
We're going to search it right away
[It's not fair]
But this is too fast
[Aww]
Was it too fast?
- It's supposed to...
- It should be this fast
It goes fast and then slows down
- I will adjust the speed
- Okay
The first letter is Bang
Starting with Jung Kook
We'll go to the left
[Bang?]
The starting letter is Bang?
[I got an idea]
- There's only one answer
- It's hard
[Get ready]
Get ready for it, Jimin
[Excited]
- Here we go
- I have no idea, but let's start
It's fast
Kung Kung Ta
[SUGA looks particularly excited today]
Kung Kung Ta Kung Kung Ta
- Kung Kung Kung
- Kung Kung Ta Kung Kung Ta
[Glaring]
Kung Kung Ta
Kung Kung Kung Kung
Bang Si Hyuk
Hyukgi hyung
[Hilarious]
I know a Hyukgi hyung
[Are you watching, Hyukgi?]
[Unexpected mention of an employee]
[He can't do that]
It's someone we know
[MC SUGA sets the rules]
He does exist, so let's proceed
Hyukgi hyung
Kung Kung Ta
Big brother
[Did you call me?] [Rolling on the floor]
- Big brother?
- It's an existing word
[Firm]
Please look it up
- Big brother
- Hang on, Hyukgi hyung counts?
[Trying to defend himself]
- I mean, if Hyukgi hyung counts then...
- It's okay because he's a real person
[Adding more rules]
- It's okay if it's someone we know
- Right
[Rumble]
I know a big brother
[You guys... Stop fighting...]
- Even Bang Si Hyuk worked
- He's a public figure
Then why can't Hyukgi hyung work?
[Members objecting to the crew]
- Does big brother work?
- Hyukgi hyung worked
Hyukgi hyung shouldn't count
It becomes endless that way
[The MC's word is law]
It just has to be someone we all know
Is there a movie or book called
big brother?
- There's nothing?
- Books or films
[The crew searched but nothing]
- All right
- Then we lost?
- Then you lost
- We earned 1 point then?
[Team Kim Seokjin earns 1 point]
1 point!
- Focus, everyone!
- Let's move on
[Current score] [Glasses 2 : Kim Seokjin 1]
The current score is 2:1
You can change seats
- You can change your seats
- Seats?
[RM and V change their seats]
Come over here, V
[Being easy]
Let's not allow names
[Not fair]
- Okay, no names
- Then it becomes too hard
- No names
- No names of friends
[Changing the rules now?]
No names from now on?
[Only public figures are accepted]
Everyone knows Bang Si Hyuk
[Our CEO]
- He's more famous than me
- Right
Now starting with V
We'll go right to left
- I'm nervous
- The starting letter is "So"
- So?
- Here we go
[Jung Kook busy thinking about words]
Kung Kung Kung
Kung Kung Ta
[Spaced out]
- Kung Kung Ta Kung Kung Ta
- Kung Kung Kung Kung
[So exciting!]
Kung Kung Ta
[MC SUGA doesn't start right away]
Kung Kung Ta Kung Kung Ta
Ox head
Kung Kung Ta
Barber shop
Rain shower
Kung Kung Ta
Goose
Crane
Kung Kung Ta
- Giyeopyo Kung Kung Ta
- Hang on
What did you say?
Giyeopyo
- That's not a word
- Giyeopyo?
[What does that mean?]
Giyeopyo? A donation ticket?
That is not a word
It doesn't exist!
[Obviously doesn't exist...]
I'm sorry
This is why we should start slowly
[Dissing themselves suddenly?]
We're not very good at this
The victory goes to Team Glasses
[Taken back because it's too fast]
It's hard because I get taken back
Let's start with "Tan"
Starting with j-hope to your left
The starting letter is "Tan"
[Spaced out]
- Give him some time to think
- I'm not sure if I can use this word
- Let's give it a try
- Let me hear it first
[Whisper]
- Tan is easy
- There are lots of words
- So many words starting with "Tan"
- You know that word
[Jimin is puzzled]
- There are a lot?
- Of course
[Even I know some!]
There are plenty
Please go ahead
- Dan Dan noodles
- Sparkling water
[This is a game]
[All the words starting with Tan]
Birthstone, birthday, birth flower
[Thanks]
We'll start! Thank you, RM
- We'll stop talking
- Kung Kung Kung Kung
Kung Kung Ta Kung Kung Ta
[j-hope is excited]
Kung Kung Kung Kung
Birth flower
Kung Kung Ta
Restroom
Slippers
Kung Kung Ta
CBR
Bang Si Hyuk
Kung Kung Ta
Hyukgi hyung
Kung Kung...
[Team Kim Seokjin's victory!]
Yes!
Bang Si Hyuk works well
[Our CEO's name is so useful]
- Nice
- Bang Si Hyuk is worth a try
- Thank you, sir!
- No more "Bang"
[RM's objection]
Think of a 3-letter word starting with Bang
[I'm proud of you]
Hyeokgeose
- Good idea
- Why did you say that?
You should have kept it a secret
[From me?]
- It's getting faster
- From RM, go to your left
- Let's start slowly
- The next letter is "Si"
Si?
- Are you all set?
- What starts with "si?"
- I got one
- Kung Kung Kung
[j-hope stood up out of excitement]
Kung Kung Kung
Kung Kung Ta Kung Kung Ta
[The 2nd and 3rd oldest are excited]
Kung Kung Kung Kung
Spinach
Kung Kung Ta
Hemorrhoids treatment
Yak...
[V helps out the youngest]
- Prescription
[Angry]
- That's cheating!
- It's okay
Bang Si Hyuk
Kung Kung Ta
- Hyeokgeose Kung Kung Ta
- You should have kept it a secret
Three...
[Everyone is holding their breath]
Coun...
tries?
[Wrath]
This is so wrong!
[The MC says it's correct, RM]
- It's correct
- How come?
[Farfetched]
The vowels "e" and "ae" are interchangeable
- At least in Kung Kung Ta
- Kung Kung Ta
Ramyeon noodles
Kung Kung Ta
Foot odor
Sae...
Coward
New world
Kung Kung Ta
- Wrong
- It starts with "Sae"
[Accepted]
Kung Kung Ta
Radio
Toes
Kung Kung Ta
Rock genre
Renaissan...
- Renaissan?
- Wrong
[Just in case]
Is there a word "Renaissan?"
- That is not a word
- It doesn't make any sense
- What did you say?
- Rock genre
What is rock genre?
[Aww]
It's a genre called rock
- Rock is a genre
- Isn't it rak? Not rock?
- No
- It's written as "rock"
[That was logical... Not bad]
This is...
[I'm serious]
- Please check if "rock genre" works
- Of course it does
[No need to kneel down for this, Jimin]
If you do, I will accept the result
[After searching]
A noun called rock genre...
[Nervous]
[Swallow hard]
[No, it doesn't]
It exists
- Three countries works but
rock genre doesn't?
- So we won?
Three countries is listed in
Naver's Korean dictionary
[Frustrated]
Then...
Team Kim Seokjin won!
[I did a good job, right?]
- I earned this
- There's something with this team name
[The youngest is just laughing]
We barely won
I don't understand how we won
- So the current score is...
- It's hard to come up with a 3-letter word
[Final score] [Glasses 3: Kim Seokjin 3]
It's 3:3, so the next game
[A tie!]
- will decide the winning team
- I'm tired
[GO GO to the next game!]
- Run!
- BTS!
The next game is Half Asleep Quiz
[Game from old variety shows!]
[Fourth game: Half Asleep]
[The 7 members will lie down
before listening to a children's song]
[They'll sleep for 30 minutes, wake up
and begin the game!]
[RM is already worried about the penalty]
My airport outfit depends on this game?
Now, please lie down
[Time to get some sleep]
Except the last bed
[What is this?]
Oh my
[BTS makes a fuss even as they lie down]
- It's so comfy
- I'm going to fall asleep
- I didn't think I could sleep
but I think I could
- You can't help it
This is nice
- It's so comfy
- What is this thing?
[Curious]
Does the MC take a nap as well?
[Of course]
I will also go to sleep
Is the MC going to sleep as well?
[Distant memory]
- Doesn't the MC originally stay awake?
- I get up and then wake you up
[That's not it]
We go to sleep together
and then I get up to wake you up
[Satisfied]
- This is so comfy
- This is...
Unbelievable
[BTS all laying down]
Are you ready?
[Jung Kook is already asleep?]
Jung Kook is already asleep
Are you sleeping already, Jung Kook?
- You have to listen to the song first
- He fell asleep
Music, start
[The Amazing Tomato]
[What is this?]
♪ Plump and round body ♪
♪ Wearing a shiny red suit ♪
[Are you sleeping, Jimin?]
♪ Sweet and yummy smell"
[Mumble]
♪ Amazing tomato (tomato) ♪
♪ I will be yummy juice (gulp) ♪
♪ I will be yummy ketchup (squirt) ♪
♪ I will be a great dancer (hey) ♪
[Focused]
♪ Dashing tomato (tomato) ♪
- I forgot already
- Be quiet
[Good night]
- See you in a bit
- Let's just sleep
I don't know
[Whining]
I forgot already
[Why are you so serious...]
- I really forgot
- Be quiet, hush
[Warning]
I'll deduct 1 point if you speak
from now on
[Go to bed, Jung Kook]
You're humming, Jung Kook
I'm going to deduct 1 point if you continue
[They quietly fall asleep]
[15 minutes later...]
[BTS is sleeping well, wiggling around]
[Jimin is completely still]
[Fast asleep]
[Next to MC SUGA is...]
[Jung Kook who is fast asleep]
[You must have all been tired]
[The members are sleeping well]
[Wiggle wiggle]
[Jung Kook who was tossing and turning]
[SUGA wakes up and looks around]
[Jung Kook is wiggling around]
[SUGA finds the situation hilarious]
[That's so funny]
[Jung Kook, get back on top...]
[What's up with him?]
[Everyone is sleeping well
like nothing happened]
[Except for him]
[30 minutes later...]
[Do I wake them up now?]
[Time for the members to get up]
[Jimin is fast asleep]
[Wake up]
[What?]
It's time to get up
It's time to get up, everyone
[SUGA sounds the siren in Jung Kook's ear]
What? What?
[RM gets up first and waits]
[Jung Kook is still half asleep]
It's time to get up
[Where am I? Who am I?]
What do we do now?
[The members start gathering around]
We have to begin the game right away
Are you all awake?
Did you sleep well? Please sit down
[V is testing the mic]
Do you know it?
[Jung Kook slept so well]
- Jung Kook is almost...
- Jung Kook!
[It's time to get up now, Jung Kook...]
Give up
[First person to try]
Please sing the song
Ha!
[Wrong!]
- Chupa Chups?
- Next
Please sit in one line
[SUGA is giving them advice]
Listen carefully to what the people
in front of you sing
[Jin is the second player] [Looks around]
Please start
- That's not it
- That makes no sense at all
[RM is the third person to try]
You should at least try to
get the right notes
[RM's expression got brighter as well]
[Someone steals the attention in the back]
[Wrong!]
[There's many people in line to play]
The correct lyrics must be "smell"
- He's still sleeping over there
- Just let him be
[He's famous for not getting up]
He's amazing
[Please let me sleep some more]
[Blank]
[4th one to play, j-hope]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Was this song an R&B?]
Wrong
[Tempo was different, Strict rules!]
[j-hope doesn't know why]
The tempo was wrong
[Give me the mic]
- The tempo was different
- Were we supposed to get that right?
Yes, it has to be faster
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Woah, he's pretty good]
[So cute]
[RM is singing in the background]
Okay
[Wrong!] [What am I doing here?]
- Do you know the lyrics?
- He doesn't know at all
Everyone, please wake up your members
[Discussing]
- Right now
- That's not important, I'm slow already
- Sing it in my ear
- Please tell us the moment we're wrong
[Angel j-hope singing in his ear]
- What are you doing?
- 5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[What's he doing?]
- Red
- Next
[There we go]
The tempo is a little...
[A sweet voice]
[He raises an objection]
Isn't he a little off? Wrong
The pitch...
It seems like you don't know the song
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
Tomato!
[SUGA is getting ready to enjoy himself]
- Ketchup, ketchup
- Wrong
[SUGA was enjoying himself so much
he didn't realize there was a mistake]
- Everyone, you have to do that too
- What?
[Like this?]
The doubling, "tomato"
[The members are listening carefully]
Squeeze
[The children's song sounds sad...]
Juice
- No?
- What's up with you?
[The members are so confused]
Isn't it juice and then ketchup?
I'll give you a hint
Sit down
[Huh?] [What is he saying?]
"Juice" is the hint
5, 6
5, 6, 7, 8
Juice!
- Does singing it loudly make a difference?
- Wait a second
[j-hope even made half asleep Jimin laugh]
Please wake Jung Kook up
Jung Kook
[A complete mess]
Jimin, get in line
[I'm so sleepy]
- Jung Kook!
- We don't know it either
[Should I get up now?]
- Get up
- Are you awake Jung Kook?
[Nods] [All doing separate things]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[What is it?]
You shouldn't have made a mistake there
Do you want to go first?
- I want to go first
- You go first
Jung Kook, that's not the way
to the restroom
[I know]
Jung Kook, that's not the restroom
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Dancing]
That's not it? Pour?
[Looking unsure of himself]
Ketchup
[Jin in the middle of chaos and
all the members sticking out their necks]
This is driving me nuts
[What kind of singing is this?]
Please get the pitch right
[He's a funny fellow]
- No...
- The pitch...
[MC gives him another chance]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Jimin finally got up]
[Moving up and down]
Jjak
[Finally, Jimin's first try]
It's finally his first try
5, 6, 7, 8
[So sleepy]
[Scratches]
[Eyes half open]
You don't gulp down ketchup
[The other members cheer him on]
- Good job
[The tempo's gotten faster]
I'm going to raise the tempo now
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Shrug]
[You're not angry, are you?]
[What?] [Blank...]
- I will be yummy ketchup
- What?
[SUGA giving him a hint]
What brand is famous for ketchup?
[Confused]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
Chop!
[Jimin disappearing a lot today]
That's not it?
[Confused]
- What brand is famous for ketchup?
- Where's ketchup famous?
[You don't know?]
OttoOi
[OttoOi?]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[RM is cute when he sings]
OttoOi
[You believed him?]
OttoOi?
Why would you believe him?
- You said OttoOi!
- I was going to try it
[SUGA giving them a real hint]
I'll give you a hint because it looks like
nobody is catching on
Pour was close
[Jimin steps up after hearing the hint!]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Looks around]
Drip?
[He thinks it's funny too]
What?
- Drip
- That's not it
[Wrong!]
- It's so hard
- It's similar to what?
[j-hope already tried that...]
It's one syllable
Here we go
[That's the hint?]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Jung Kook looks confused]
It's your first try, isn't it?
[His first try!]
Sit down, please
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8
[He's staring hard at SUGA]
[He doesn't care]
[Good job]
[Jung Kook sings well even though
he just woke up]
[Our youngest is doing so well]
- It's your first try today, isn't it?
- Yes
Do you remember falling off
and then going back to sleep?
[A few minutes ago... When everyone
was sleeping]
- You don't remember, do you? You rolled
off right next to me
- He fell off?
He went, "Ah" and then
went back to sleep
[Looks aloof as if it's not about him]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8!
♪ I will be yummy juice ♪
♪ I will be yummy ketchup (clap) ♪
[SUGA is having so much fun]
- That's not it?
- Clap?
[Just in case it's right]
Clap, clap!
[j-hope is trying his best]
It's clap!
[He thinks the youngest is hilarious]
♪ I will be yummy juice (gulp) ♪
♪ I will be yummy ketchup (squirt) ♪
[There you go]
♪ I will be a great dancer ♪
Argh!
[He's just doing his job]
What? Why are you angry at me?
I did nothing wrong
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8!
♪ Plump and round body ♪
- I lost I'm done
- ♪ Wearing a shiny red suit ♪
[Acting cute]
♪ Sweet and yummy smell ♪
[Excited MC]
Okay!
- ♪ Amazing tomato (tomato) ♪
- Almost there! Let's go!
[RM is excited]
♪ I will be yummy juice (gulp) ♪
- ♪ I will be yummy ketchup ♪
- Come on!
[Wrong] [Upset] [V messed up because
SUGA was so excited]
Please be quiet
Me? Why? I'm having so much fun
[So much fun]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8!
[Sweet tone]
- ♪ Amazing tomato (tomato) ♪
- All together!
♪ I will be yummy juice (gulp) ♪
[Loads of fun]
- ♪ I will be yummy ketchup (squirt) ♪
- Come on!
[Main vocalist is different]
♪ I will be a great dancer ♪
[Go]
There's more?
[The members are tired of the doubling]
- That doubling...
- There's more?
♪ I will be a great dancer (dance) ♪
[RM is dancing to the beat]
Yeah!
[So fun]
That wasn't it?
[Why not?]
- Yay!
- "Yay" was what I said
[Jung Kook singing with his eyes closed]
Wow!
Yay!
[Dancing]
♪ I will be a great dancer (oy) ♪
♪ I will be a great dancer (hey) ♪
♪ Dashing tomato ♪
[Jung Kook's singing makes
Team Kim Seokjin excited]
[We're almost there]
We're almost there!
[Whispers]
- We're almost there
- Let's do this
[SUGA gives j-hope the chance
to do a winner's ceremony]
Do a winner's ceremony
- Let's get it
- 5, 6, 7, 8!
♪ I will be yummy juice (gulp) ♪
[The MC is even more excited]
♪ I will be yummy ketchup (squirt) ♪
♪ I will be a great dancer (hey) ♪
♪ Ugly tomato ♪
[j-hope is bewildered, I said hey!]
Hey
[Next]
- You were right until "hey"
- It must not be "ugly"
♪ I will be a great dancer (hey) ♪
My friend...
Why are you saying "my friend?"
- Dreamy tomato
- Tasty tomato
- Exciting tomato
[Everyone is making mistakes]
[So handsome]
[Everything but the answer]
We already sang everything
[The members have no clue]
[Big hint]
For example... Stylish?
[The members are in discussion]
5, 6, 5, 6, 7, 8!
[V is confident]
We're done!
[Before he finishes]
Good work, everyone
[Today's master of reaction]
- ♪ Amazing tomato (tomato) ♪
- Let's go!
[They think they have it in the bag]
[RM and Jung Kook are excited in the back]
♪ I will be yummy ketchup (squirt) ♪
♪ I will be a great dancer (hey) ♪
[2 teams look completely different]
♪ Dashing tomato (tomato) ♪
[We're almost there]
[Correct!] [Unhappy and happy]
That's why we kept hearing "ugly"
[They finally get the answer]
I heard "ugly"
[I'm so excited]
It was "dashing tomato"
[V helped lead his team to victory]
We thought it was "yummy"
[j-hope is still in shock]
We were talking about
[V is still doing his winner's ceremony]
"yummy" as the answer
[V is still dancing]
[The final score being 4:3
Glasses team won]
Glasses team wins
[V is so excited he doesn't have to do
any penalties]
The losers, team Kim Seokjin
must wear their clothes from today
[Wing's Tour] [Spaced out]
for when we leave for Macau
Yes, when we leave for Macau
[MC SUGA did a great job today]
And I, MC Min Yoongi
- really did my best today
- We know
- He did his best
- He's the hero of today
[Will j-hope be right?]
I don't think he'll get the penalty
[Going over the rules once more]
If I picked Team Kim Seokjin earlier
- I have to wear the retro style fashion
when we leave
- That's right
- If I picked the Glasses team...
- Then you can wear
what you want
[Will SUGA be able to wear his clothes?]
Just something comfortable
[V is cheering SUGA up]
- I'd cover my face and wear a mask...
- You're wearing glasses right now
[SUGA looks so nervous]
- Which team did he pick?
- Please sing "Amazing Tomato"
Today's hero!
What will happen to SUGA?
[They want to see first]
Can we look at it first?
-  That's a good idea
- Yes, let's do that
[Shakes his head]
- Change...
- There's no changing
[Please give me that]
- We'll open it behind you
- Don't do that
[Don't get angry, SUGA]
- I don't know why you're saying that
- We didn't do anything
[Sensitive]
Please don't play any jokes
Stick with what I picked earlier
[We didn't switch anything...]
Don't make any reactions
- Don't switch anything, it's being filmed
- Don't turn back
1, 2, 3!
[MC SUGA was lucky]
[[j-hope gives him a chance to switch]
Are you sure you don't want to switch?
[Confident]
I won't
Are you sure?
[What will happen to MC SUGA?]
What is Min Yoongi's fate?
Glasses team!
I have so much experience with
variety programs
[SUGA returns to his confident self]
I read the minds of the staff
[Lucky MC SUGA gets ready to say goodbye]
Today's Run BTS
was the most fun and exciting
episode ever
[It looked that way]
You seemed to have a great time
[He had fun teasing the members]
- I had the most fun
- Please do the closing
[Sweet smile]
Run BTS will continue
Run BTS!
[Bye!]
You can wear the clothes you wore today
to Macau tomorrow
[Team Kim Seokjin is doing their penalty]
[Leaving for Wings Tour in Macau]
[j-hope appears after lucky
SUGA and RM]
I ended up wearing this...
Come over here
[Team Kim Seokjin showing off
poses (Include Jimin too)]
[Awkward]
[Team Kim Seokjin taking a group photo]
1, 2, 3!
[Everyone... Smile...]
[X color power]
[So handsome]
[See you in the next episode!]