[Run BTS - Please Take Care of Santa]
Run BTS!
Is this the famous
"Robot Taekwon V Museum"?
- That's right
- It looks like an underground research lab
[Looking around]
There are amazing stuff in here
I thought it emerges from the dome of
the National Assembly building
[Rumor has it so]
I thought so
[Taekwon V's reputation since the '70s]
Taekwon V has been around for 40 years
[Released in 1976]
That's my dad's generation
[A mega-hit animation in the 1970s]
My dad was so into it
My dad used to watch it when he was a boy
BTS' V is a mega-hit these days
[Busted]
Dynamic V!
- So what do we do?
- What do we do today?
[Christmas season is here]
Christmas
- Today is "Please Take Care of Santa"
- "Please Take Care of Santa"
[Run BTS!
Please Take Care of Santa!]
[BTS becomes Santa for a day]
[Find ornaments with hidden numbers
in 35 minutes]
[Find many consecutive numbers
to decorate the Christmas tree]
[1. Locate ornaments with numbers from 1-50
and exchange with the number on the tree]
[2. Five coupons to exchange with
the number you want]
[3. One star tree topper
to choose three numbers you want]
[Find a key to a box
to obtain the star tree topper]
[4. Santa who finds the most consecutive
numbers get to choose a gift first]
[Example) A - 1, 2, 3, 4
B - 21, 22, 33, 35, 37, 40, 45, 50]
[The winner is the Santa who finds the most
consecutive numbers, no matter what!]
[Who will get to take the gift first?]
We have some bad memories of it, right?
- Let's find a lot today
- That's right
[They didn't locate a lot of free passes]
It's because we ignored the instructions
Santa always comes with Rudolph
[Right]
- Yes
- So, instead of Rudolph
[Pigdolph instead of Rudolph]
So cute!
I bet Namjoon's Pigdolph
comes back ragged
[Agree]
Samgyeopsal for dinner!
- Now
- Do we start right away?
I'm at a disadvantage
because I have a bad sense of direction
[Flustered]
- We've never been here before too
- Doesn't matter, we don't know as well
- I'll give you 35 minutes
- Yes
[BTS gets only 35 minutes]
It starts when the door opens
- Amazing
- Open the door please
Please open the door
[Santas' mission begins as the door opens]
Let's not hit each other
[Everyone heads to the door]
[Wow]
[Puzzled]
What? What's in here?
It's somewhere around here?
[Got one]
I found two!
[Quietly searching]
[Huh?]
Is it just me here?
[Just happy]
Where's everyone?
[RM goes to the corner?]
Oh, no!
My piggy!
[Why are you holding that...]
[God of destruction, Pigdolph broke...]
- It broke from the start
- Oh no
[The staff is in panic,
that's our prop box...]
I think you put something else
[Back then, we had no idea how
the prop box]
This is not it, right?
[that RM found would make an impact]
Why are you doing this to me?
[Jung Kook is running toward somewhere]
What?
[Confused]
Am I going in the right direction?
Where am I?
This is the entrance
[Running]
Where is it?
What? Someone went up?
[Crying, my precious Pigdolph...]
No!
[My Pigdolph]
What does it look like?
[Is this it?]
I found it
[Wow]
What is that?
[Curious, what is it?]
Awesome
[Pretty high climbing zone]
[A coupon is on the top]
- That is it, right?
- Can you get it?
[This is filmed safely with professional help]
Okay
[j-hope cuts V's Pigdolph out of the blue]
Come on, that was too mean
That was too mean
[V cuts j-hope's Pigdolph]
[Announcement]
- The thief begins his operation
- Thief?
Thief?
[Too busy taking care of Pigdolph
to listen to the announcement]
Okay, let's go!
This doesn't feel good
[Confused]
Thief? There's a thief?
[How today's Run BTS episode
was created]
[The staff thought hard about
the spy concept and who should be the spy]
[We chose j-hope to be the spy]
[j-hope heard about the rules beforehand]
Really? So I'm the spy?
[Half-worried, half-excited]
I'm not sure about this
Oh, no
You know I'm a terrible liar
I can get a prize
when I accomplish this mission?
I can choose whatever I want from these?
Awesome
Keep it secret from them
[So, in order to avoid any doubt
about the delivery of the spy rule]
[the staff carried out a pre-shoot
interview with every member]
1, 2, 3
Which episode would you like to try again?
[We said it's the pre-shoot interview]
Are we moving on to the next season?
[But it's a fake interview]
The computer game episode
That was fun
I liked the large-scale one
Zombie episode
[Thanks for doing a fake interview]
We carried out a series of missions
[Innocent]
Bungee jumping
[Meaningful]
Are you guys ready?
All the balloons will get cut off
Watch out
[Run BTS!
Please Take Care of Santa!]
[Today's real Run BTS!
Take Care of Santa (Save the Balloon!)]
[j-hope is the thief among the Santas]
[When he cuts off at least four balloons,
his mission is accomplished]
[He can pick a gift first!]
[Safety scissors for children were used]
[The staff gives an excuse for balloons]
The reason why we're giving you this is
- you guys might run too fast
- Right, there's a risk of injury
[j-hope's thief mission begins
without anyone knowing]
[No one would have imagined]
[this transformation of j-hope]
[Please look forward to j-hope the thief!]
[V obtained the coupon]
V, the pig is cut, and you go ahead?
[I cut V's Pigdolph]
[Suddenly approaching]
[Flustered]
Where is it?
Here it is
Wait up, SUGA
[The next target is SUGA?]
Why are you chasing me?
[Why would I follow you...]
Don't follow me! Why are you following me?
[To cut your Pigdolph]
Hey, why did you cut mine?
[Two missions accomplished]
[Exchanging the numbers on the tree]
- Did you find any?
- I did
- 28
- 27
- Where's 28?
- Where's 27?
[Panic]
Where is 28?
- I think I'm at a disadvantage
- Good luck
Let's go, piggy!
[RM roams around holding his Pigdolph]
I can't help but carry this around
I need to find everything in here
before they come
[Looking around]
- Where is it?
- I found one, it's over!
- It's over!
- Nothing more here?
- No
[Runs hurriedly]
[I got it]
[There is actually one more coupon hanging]
Let's go
Are there coupons here?
[The poor lamb had no idea]
I'll go for Jimin
[That he became the target of the thief]
- What is this place?
- How many did you find?
- Huh?
- About seven?
- Really?
[j-hope's awkward acting]
Where is the safe?
[What's wrong with him?]
Isn't that where the tree is?
Jimin! Let's go together!
[Someone tell me what concept it is]
Give me one!
No, no!
[Snip]
Come on, Jimin!
[Takes off right away]
Jimin!
I got three
[The thief mission is going smoothly]
It's a piece of cake
[Thanks to the gullible members]
They're dummies
[Looking proud]
Good luck finding your coupons, guys
[A little excited]
Is it hanging up there?
[No] [I see]
- I got everything
- You did?
- Yes
- It looks fun
[Jimin saw Jin running around]
Jin is running around
[Flustered]
Where's my piggy?
[Pushing each other]
[Rustle]
[My Pigdolph disappeared]
My piggy is gone
[Fiddle]
- How many did you find?
- Me? Not many
[He immediately found an ornament]
[Nimble fingers]
[Can't stop smiling]
[Bulging bag]
My bag is full
[j-hope is looking for an ornament?]
[... Not, look at his eyes]
Where is your pig?
[It's so not fair]
It's cut off
I guess someone cut it
Isn't that mine?
[Flustered]
I'll give you one
Give me some slack
[BTS!] [Acting cute]
Let me retie it
Give me one
[There is a thief hiding
among the Santas]
[He's been cutting your Pigdolph]
Really?
[This is so not fair!]
I know
Mine was gone before I knew it
j-hope cut it and ran away
[When your Pigdolph is cut, the thief wins]
There's a thief among us?
[What?]
Really?
[What is with him...]
I think j-hope is the thief!
[I know]
I'm not a thief!
[A shower of complaints]
I found the thief!
[Everyone is in panic]
We found the thief!
[It's unfair]
Mine was gone before I knew it!
[All the pieces are falling into place]
He cut mine!
Yes, j-hope is the thief!
j-hope is the thief!
[Tramp]
Hang on
What's wrong with him?
Mine got cut already
Out of the way!
[Huh?]
[Jimin bursts Jin's balloon]
I'm not the thief!
Jimin popped it! It's Jimin!
[I don't believe you]
- He popped mine
- Are we a team?
[Running at full speed]
I'm not the thief
[Detective SUGA]
I heard you're the culprit
- No, I'm not
- You cut mine and ran away
[I know everything]
Go away
[So cool]
Yours got cut already
[Worried]
I need one more, but they found out
It's tougher now, what do I do?
[Jung Kook is hiding from the thief]
I should hide here
[Peek-a-boo]
Jung Kook, what are you doing?
- I'm hiding
- You're the thief, right?
[Umm... You're barking up the wrong tree]
No
[Crawl]
I'm not a thief, but I ruined Jin's balloon
[Run away]
[Why would you... Getting more suspicious]
I'm not a thief, really, but I cut Jin's
[Tinderbox]
What? Why are you avoiding me?
[Breathtaking chasing,
one chases, the other one is chased after]
We're running out of time
[I'm not going to give you]
You're holding scissors
[I should get out of this place]
[What just passed by...?]
I can't defeat Jung Kook
[Jung Kook escaped to a safe hideout]
Where did my hat go?
[Change the target!]
I should go for Jin and RM
[Lounge around] [RM is located!]
What?
[Chaotic again]
We can take j-hope's, right?
Why are you carrying it?
[Puzzled]
- What's this for?
- Aren't you a thief?
I don't need it
[Cool j-hope left...]
Huh?
- How come you don't have one, Jin?
- Jimin popped my balloon
[j-hope cut the strap]
No!
[Elaborate]
The evidence
[Focusing on locating ornaments]
It should be hidden somewhere unexpected
[Not here]
[It's hanging on a doorknob]
I guess not
[He walked right past it]
[j-hope is scary]
I'm scared
[Huh?]
[So happy]
[Found something]
[What is it?]
[Jackpot!]
[RM found the key with the star on it]
[He's surprised too]
[No one saw this, right?]
It's the key
[RM found all the ornaments SUGA missed]
Very clumsy
[Jimin looks around]
What is this place?
What is that pig?
[Jimin found a Pigdolph]
[It's mine now]
I have a piggy now
[SUGA thinks the mission is to pop it]
No popping
Go away
What? Popping it is not the mission
[Shoo shoo]
Go away
I just need to get my hands on Jung Kook
[V & Jung Kook work together]
It's not in here
There's nothing in here
Not here
- No
- Not here
No
Hang on
There's a camera
[Where is it?]
It should be somewhere
[Jung Kook tries to locate the ornament
based on the camera angle]
There's a camera, the angle...
[Panic]
- This way?
- Yes
[Looking for each and every corner]
Did you find it?
- They're going crazy right now
- Huh?
- They're going crazy
- j-hope is cutting all the strings
[I'm scared of him]
I guess he's the thief
[It wasn't an easy game]
Yeah, it wasn't just a scavenger hunt
[BTS members]
[I need your attention for a minute]
Huh?
[Puzzled Jimin]
Attention to what?
[Pay attention to what?]
I don't know where
[You can pay attention at where you are]
Okay
[Protect the members
whose strings haven't gotten cut yet]
[And proceed with your mission,
so Santa can win]
Mine got cut once
You want to have it?
[Jin has no Pigdolph, as Jimin popped his]
- You can keep this
- Really?
[Donation angel]
Yeah, you can keep it
Mine got cut anyway
- Would that be okay?
- Why not have it back on?
[No big deal]
Let's give it a shot
[Jin adopted the pig]
I cut j-hope's
[j-hope looks for Jung Kook]
Where's Jung Kook? I need to find him
What is that?
[Santa Kook finds where the camera is]
There's a camera
[Hi]
What?
You went everywhere, Jin?
Yes
This is my third time
[The box is empty]
Really?
[Now...]
Then I won't find anything here now
[Don't come too close...]
[Found a camera]
Can I take this camera to film myself?
[Yes... go ahead] [Voluntary self-coverage]
Kim Seokjin is doing great!
Where did they hide it?
[Here? There?]
[RM is looking for the star tree topper]
The box with the star
[The key box, RM found it already]
The box
[j-hope's voice is coming near]
[Run away]
[j-hope]
Jeong Hoseok
[RM is scared]
Where is he?
[Scared]
j-hope is out there
Hobi is playing that role, right?
[j-hope's cover is blown]
- The thief
- Yes, I think so
I saw him cut it
[Checking if he left]
[Wandering about]
Is anyone here?
[Oh my]
[Running wild]
[Listen to it with your eyes closed
It's like prehistoric age]
[The camera shows the panicky situation]
[Whatever! Scatter off!]
[Is he gone?]
What!
[Here he is!]
No! No!
[Hiding without breathing]
Be careful, RM!
[Pause]
[What? What?]
[Looks like the ending scene of a TV show]
[So shocking]
[Peeking]
I'm tired
[RM ended up getting his string cut]
[Got four!
Proving with the evidence]
[RM took his Pigdolph]
He carried his piggy
[Jin's scared]
j-hope! He should be called j-kill
♪ Have some fun as you dance along ♪
[Humming]
There it is
See? I can find it if I keep looking
[Jimin found two more!]
See? There are two here
Where's the star?
I can't find a sign of the star
Where is it?
[RM found the star tree topper]
The star
This is it
[Tough]
[RM got the star]
[Amazed]
[Surprised]
[Why are you climbing up there?]
[Smiling]
[This place displays Robot Taekwon V
that V Center boasts]
[Proud] [And V, the handsome member
that ARMY is proud of] [Looking ahead]
[RM on the way to find an ornament]
[Catching a glimpse]
[Knock knock]
[Surprised] [I won't say]
How did you get there?
[Let's go]
[Scratching]
[Frozen]
[Finally]
I found the star
[My precious star]
[Your dream will come true]
[RM can choose three numbers that he wants]
[Serious]
I'm so scared of j-hope!
[He's here]
[Jin is trying to find a way to escape]
- Jin
- j-hope!
I've cut Jin's already
[Running away]
Do you want me to do it again?
[I found you!]
Got ya!
Isn't it the coupon box?
[Correct]
Did someone leave it after taking coupons?
[Why?] [SUGA brought the empty box]
- j-hope is coming
- Is he coming?
[Jin brought the camera back to its place]
Cam, go back to your place, bye
[RM arrived at the tree to hang the star]
[Serious]
I will hang this star on the tree
I've won this game
[SUGA looks like a part of the facility]
[Chameleon?]
Oh, are you looking through
the mirror to watch?
[SUGA leaves a quote every day]
Don't look at trees, look at the forest
[Great, SUGA]
What have you found?
[But he got nothing]
I've found nothing
- Hey! SUGA!
- What?
[V looks so curious from behind]
- How many have you found?
- Huh?
- How many?
- I've already decorated ornaments
[He found just one]
I found one, thanks to SUGA
By looking at the mirror
Has he decorated already?
Don't look at the trees, look at the forest
Should we hang ornaments on the tree?
[Confident]
I've cut all the members'
[j-hope successfully completed his mission]
I've already finished my mission
But I need to cut
the key player's, as a spy
[Key player Jung Kook]
[Jung Kook is almost playing hide-and-seek]
I've found only two
[Searching through carefully]
[Spy quietly approached]
[Jin is running away, terrified]
j-hope, please don't do this to me
j-hope!
[Jin is talking nonsense]
j-hope, we've done that together
[Sweet-hope who cares about him]
- Stop running, you may get injured
- I might get injured
[I'll go away]
j-hope, thank you
It was touching
[j-hope is going to catch the ace member]
I'll catch Jung Kook
[Kind]
Have you looked into this place?
[Dark shadow that is approaching them]
- I'm so scared of Hobi
- Did you find any coupons?
[Shaking his head] [Spy is sneaking]
Did you have any coupons?
- I have two
- Do you?
[j-hope saw him]
[j-hope started asking how they are doing]
- How are you?
- So scary
I've cut everyone's except for yours
[Hugging] [Come here]
- I'll protect you
- Two versus one? Too much
[Running]
Don't let the thief win
[V is protecting the younger Jung Kook]
[Jung Kook asks Jin for help]
Jin! Please hold j-hope back
- j-hope saved me
- Seriously, look at this
[Scary spy j-hope to others]
j-hope, thank you!
[j-hope doesn't care]
- j-hope, you saved my life!
- Because yours is cut already
- Go, go, go
- His lame acting
[Confrontation]
You have 10 minutes left
[Strong desire to cut Jung Kook's Pigdolph]
I will cut Jung Kook's
It feels like taking away Jongkook's
name tag in "Running Man"
[The older one cares about the youngest]
Jung Kook, don't let him cut yours
I'll let you go, this time
[Pigdolph that Jung Kook is carrying]
[Smiling]
Go! I'll let you go
[Members can't trust each other]
I'll go after he's gone
[Talking nonsense]
I won't be fooled by him
[Looking around]
I need to find some more
[Brain RM is calculating in the middle]
Now, 40. 41
And 10, 12
Okay
[SUGA, what are you doing?]
[Searching through]
[SUGA found the extra star ornament
inside the item box]
[This one has started everything]
[SUGA didn't know RM found the star]
[Jin is so creative]
What if the directors carry ornaments?
[Disappointed]
No? No? Seriously?
[Looking around]
[Members get scared when
hearing j-hope's voice]
I heard j-hope's voice
[j-hope suggest trade]
Anyone who wants a prize?
Except for when I learned how to dance,
this is the first time
when I am scared of j-hope
[Peek-a-boo]
[A chasing game that started again]
I'll catch you, Jin!
There must be some places
that I've never been to
[Stop]
[Scared RM is running away]
I'm so scared
That way!
No, no
[Looking around]
They'll bring this place down
[j-hope is omnipresent with his voice]
[I need to run away]
[1st floor and 2nd floor are
in different worlds]
[Running away]
[j-hope is coming to get Jung Kook]
[Tired]
[The chasing game never ends]
[Going back and forth]
[RM is still confused]
Where is it?
[SUGA is walking slowly
to find an ornament]
The production staff does not
hide it in an easy place
[Oh?]
[You've taken the bait]
What's this box?
[Looking inside]
It's not ours
[Yes... It's ours]
[Then]
If I sit here, I can catch him
Wow, you're so scary
[Jung Kook is holding the Pigdolph tightly]
[He found j-hope]
[I'm scared of him]
[Jin is checking what he's got]
35, 36...
[What's that?]
Oh?
[Jimin found a coupon someone left behind]
I guess someone dropped this
May I take this?
Someone dropped this on the way
[Jimin got a coupon]
[I love it]
Someone left it behind
[V was the one who left
the coupon behind]
[Oh! It's Jin]
[Innocent hands that have
no idea what's to come]
[j-hope who is good at spying]
[Busy counting numbers]
35, 36, 37, 38, 39
[3]
[2]
[1]
[Float like butterfly, sting like bee]
[I'm j-hope, the best spy]
[Jin stays calm and does what he has to do]
[Jung Kook couldn't find many
because he was busy running away]
I need to find a coupon
I have no idea
Where is it?
[Jung Kook peeps out]
[What's that?]
[Relaxed]
[Where is it?]
[The leader and Jung Kook
are so scared of j-hope]
j-hope is like Hong Gildong
- Nice to see you
- What are you doing there?
- Are you looking for Jung Kook?
- Can we negotiate?
[I have a secret offer you can't deny]
I've cut six members'
If I cut Jung Kook's...
[j-hope and V started a negotiation]
5 minutes are left
I will help you cut his for 5 minutes
What will you do for me?
I will give you the presents
[V sold his brother for a gift]
Jung Kook is there
[So proud]
5 minutes are left
[The alliance was formed like that]
[V started trying to fool Jung Kook]
He's not here
He's gone down
[Why is he saying that?]
I was there, in the block part
[A master of hiding]
[Nervous]
[V is calling j-hope]
j-hope!
[Did he?]
He took the elevator
Go to the 1st floor
Wait in front of the elevator
[It bodes ill]
No, I think we should walk downstairs
[V was surprised]
Let's go down
[This is not what I expected]
- I want to keep this safe
- Hang on
I won't let him cut mine
[Flustered]
[V is checking Jung Kook's whereabouts]
- Will you stay on the 2nd floor?
- Yes
But it's blocked
[Disappointed]
Right
[Whispering]
I think I need to sneak in
to catch Jung Kook
If I hide for 5 more minutes, I win
[He's crawling all the way
to catch Jung Kook]
[Showing off to Jung Kook]
I've got these
Where's the other one?
[V found out his coupon is missing]
Oh? I had two coupons
[Jimin picked up V's coupon]
10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17
I have two coupons
[j-hope's hair]
[Members are carrying their Pigdolphs
even after j-hope cut theirs]
RM, is your pig safe?
[Spying on]
Oh!
Wow, he's hiding like that
So scary
[His target is Jung Kook]
Bring Jung Kook!
[Checking what he's got]
[SUGA is focusing on finding things]
[Peeping]
[Acting cute]
[Chu]
[RM's confession]
I'm so scared of Jeong Hoseok
I've never been so scared of him like this
He looks crazy
[Back of j-hope, in search of others]
[V is coming to report to him]
Jung Kook won't use the elevator
He's staying on the 2nd floor
[Bowing]
If I catch him, I'll give
all the presents to you
I'll do my best
[Still thinking where to hide]
In the theater?
Where is the star?
[Jin is searching through so carefully]
You have 1 minute left until
the end of the mission
Just like an angel
Box!
Can I insist this was in the box?
[I need to use this box]
May I insist? I'll do that
You have 1 minute left until
the end of the mission
[SUGA is so relaxed]
You have 1 minute left
[SUGA's busy hand to check items out]
[What are you doing, Jung Kook?]
I've found only two
I did a great job in the beginning
Jung Kook is missing
[Jung Kook is going to the meeting place]
May I go now? Only 1 minute is left
[Now he can see what this place is for]
I guess it's a ride
[Looking around]
3D theater
[Mission is over]
It's over
[Disappointed]
I think it's around the blocks
but, because j-hope is waiting here...
[j-hope couldn't find Jung Kook]
Where is he?
[Jimin, let's go now]
Wow, Jung Kook, I've cut
everyone's except for yours
[We didn't hide]
Who hid this?
[You took it on your own]
I was confused by this
- The thief, how many did you cut?
- Everyone's except for Jung Kook's
Did he cut mine?
[Thoroughly prepared]
I expected him to say so
So I brought the strings
Thoroughly prepared
[After cutting two members' strings]
As evidence,
[Jin's string]
I left the string after cutting Jin's
[RM's string]
This is RM's
[Shaking his head]
Jung Kook was so fast
[But he found nothing]
Right, he found nothing
[Complaining to older brothers]
I kept running away
Got two numbers but they're not consecutive
27 and 23?
Let's see who got more numbers
that are consecutive
[Game result: numbers, stars, and coupons]
[j-hope: Finished his mission by cutting
everyone's strings except for Jung Kook's]
[Game result after using the stars
and coupons (In the order of exchange)]
[Final result] [Winner: j-hope who cut
all the balloons except for Jung Kook's]
[2nd place - RM and SUGA]
[4th place- Jimin, 5th - Jin,
6th place - V and Jung Kook]
[Completed exchange]
The exchange is done
Can I get a gift that I want?
[j-hope chose a gift before the game began]
The curtain will drop down
after you get this
- Wow
- Really?
- Taekwon V will come out?
- For real?
1, 2, 3!
- Wow
- Wow, it's huge!
As Hobi won the game, let's get in!
Wow, amazing
[Members chose the gifts]
- Who was in 2nd place?
- Let me see
- Small thing is cute
- This is so cute
They will give away eventually
Jung Kook, please wrap this up
[Inhaling helium gas]
- As he inhaled the helium gas
- I enjoyed a lot
Do it later
Not now
[RM, where are you looking at?]
- We're at the V Center
- Right
[Busy inhaling the helium gas]
We found interesting things about Taekwon V
- Also, new aspects of j-hope
- Right
j-hope, you did a great job!
[Today's MVP: j-hope, who showed
a new aspect of his character]
[Peeping out]
What's that noise?
[Spy j-hope's amazing acting]
Why are you running away from me?
We wish you a happy Christmas!
[Merry Christmas with BTS!]
2, 3, merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas!