[Run BTS]
[BTS X Manito Part 1]
- Run!
- BTS!
Where are we?
- This is our practice room
- Our new practice room
I've never seen anybody attach their
mic onto their scarf
[Microphone on scarf = j-hope's fashion
philosophy]
I had to do it for the fashion
- He's creating fashion
- When will you take that acorn pouch off?
[The acorn pouch catching attention]
I can't. This is very important
[All eyes on j-hope's acorn pouch]
- What's in there?
- Right now?
- I'm expecting something big
- Nothing?
- Yeah, there's nothing
- Then why are you wearing it?
[94z protecting his friend] [Curious]
- That's just how it is
- What are we doing today?
The theme of today's Run BTS is
"Manito and Games"
[Manito]
[Today's Run BTS!
Three games with Manito]
[Before the games, the members will
choose their manito and mission]
[During the game, they must conduct
their mission without their manito knowing]
[If they succeed, they can receive their
manito's present. If they fail or get
caught, they can't]
[The two members who place 6th
and 7th place will get the penalty
regardless of their missions]
[The presents each member prepared
for their manito]
Everyone's saying that their present
is the best
[But it's for your Manito]
- Mine's the best
- I need mine in my room
[Showing off his gift]
- I bought something everyone needs
- Mine's what I need in my room
- I'm really curious about yours
- What if we don't need it?
[Young members doubting the eldest]
- You will
- What if he just packed water?
- I didn't do that
- Mine looks expensive
- Really?
- But when you think about it
it could be the most useless present ever
- Let's pick our manito
- Yes
[Manito: V - Jin]
[Mission: Hear "You're really smart"
from your manito]
[Manito: Jin - j-hope]
[Stroke]
- What?
- Are you his manito?
[V is suspected of being SUGA's Manito]
- He's already been caught
- I think so, too
He's my manito!
He touched his neck as soon as
he picked
Why would you touch my neck?
[What's this?]
[Mission: Have your Manito tell you
"Stop it now"]
[Who is it?]
[Manito: Jimin - Jung Kook]
[Members swarming around SUGA]
He must have put on perfume
[Hehe]
I put it on this morning
Don't touch me
[Mission: Make a heart towards the
camera with your manito]
This is too difficult
How do I do this?
[Deep sigh] [Manito: RM - Jimin]
He said his gift was useless
It's easy!
[Mission: Make a V sign behind your Manito
for the staff to see]
[Confident RM dissing V]
V already got caught stroking
the back of someone's neck
[Manito: SUGA - V]
[Mission: Make a finger heart next to
your manito]
[Manito: Jung Kook - SUGA]
You all saw the missions, right?
Do you think you can do it?
[Jimin disappears then reappears
as soon as SUGA approaches]
Don't touch me
[Mission: Lock fingers and hold hands
with your manito]
When I only saw this
I thought it was the name of a dinosaur
[Manito: j-hope - RM]
[Mission: High-five with your manito
at least three times]
This is difficult
It's too difficult
- Did you all check your missions?
- Yes
As soon as the first game begins
the manito missions also start
[Worried]
How do I do this?
[Focused]
Let's choose the penalties
for the 6th and 7th place
V, you're so bad at acting
We haven't even begun yet
[Maybe he's the smartest member...]
Can't believe you're trying to
fake things like that
You're so obvious
- We're taking penalty recommendations
- For 7th place
- Wear clothes picked by someone else
for the airport
- Wow
[The acorn pouch?]
For 6th place, how about wearing this
to MAMA?
[Alarmed] [Funny]
No, I'm going to wear it
[j-hope placing 6th to wear it?]
Then make sure to place 6th
You should be in the 6th place then
Go ahead
The one in 6th place wears that
Or maybe before the next shoot
they eat three packets of ramyeon
[RM still wants j-hope's acorn pouch]
- With a bloated face?
- Wear this in the next shoot
I told you, I'm going to wear it
With a bloated face...
[Jimin finds Jung Kook very cute]
Why is Jung Kook so cute?
[Ugly shoes?] [Please listen to j-hope...]
- And wear the shoes as well!
- I told you, I'm wearing them
How about this? 7th place
wears hanbok on the way to MAMA
- Not bad
- That's not bad
[SUGA dislikes the idea itself]
I imagined myself wearing it
[Jimin is full of ideas!] [That's me]
- Okay
- That's for 7th place then
[Penalty for 7th place decided by Jimin]
Wear hanbok to MAMA
Whoever gets this penalty will
be in trouble
[That sounds great]
You'll get like a hundred articles that day
Now let's decide on the 6th place penalty
You each have your BT21 character, right?
- Wear your character's costume for
the next shoot
- I like that
[Too good to be a penalty?]
That's a good thing, though
It promotes your character
Wearing your own cute one
feels like promotion
[The 1st place's character]
How about wearing the 1st place's
character instead?
[Members admit that he's full of ideas]
- You're full of ideas today
- What's up with me today?
- Let's go
- He's full of ideas
[Impressed by his own ideas]
I came up with them, but they're
really something
No, I'm proud of them
- You should be
- V might lose on purpose
[V being cornered from the beginning]
You like the attention
He's excited over the idea of wearing
a hanbok
- Then let's go
- Okay
[Let' do this]
- Ready, go!
- Run BTS!
The first game is the photo zone game
[Hear the keyword and then jump
within the photo zone along with
the 10 second timer]
[Success if face and shoulders are included
and an expression or pose is made that
matches the keyword!]
[Fail if face can't be seen, expression
or pose doesn't match the keyword!]
[Order: Jimin & V → j-hope & Jung Kook → RM
→ SUGA & Jin]
[Who's up first?]
Who will go first?
[What concept is this?]
To the front, with confidence!
[95z Jimin & V are up first]
- Let's go, 95z
- Please give it to us
[Keyword: Flower pose]
- 1, 2, 3!
- Flower pose
This is easy
[Dissing Jimin] [Dancing]
Jimin might not be in
the picture even after jumping
[Focused] [Jump!]
I don't think they got it
[Laughing hard]
[Guess who the flower is?.jpg]
[Everyone approaches the monitor]
[Jimin disappears from laughing]
- Did they succeed?
- No, that's a fail
[Everyone's busy laughing]
It has to be above your shoulder line
[Jimin's shoulders]
- This is Jimin's best picture yet
- Those are my shoulders
This is your best picture ever
[j-hope is about to cry...]
[Fail as their shoulders didn't show!]
Come one
Let's go for a second
- You guys need to do it at least 10 times
- 10 times
[RM carrying out his mission behind Jimin]
How did that face...
[Engaged in a discussion without knowing]
- So it has to be up to here?
- Yeah
Here we go
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Bullet]
Bullet! Bullet!
- What's a bullet?
- Above the shoulder line
[Ready, Focused]
Just the face won't work
[Jimin almost levitated]
Hey
[Are you okay?]
Whoa
[Hilarious] [What's that?]
[Members bursting out laughing]
He looks like Count Asura
[Jimin's hard work]
Jimin's gonna do all the work today
- Success?
- Is that a success?
[SUGA refutes with seriousness]
But it's cut off on the left
[Generous]
Let's be generous because there's
two of them
[Jimin & V succeed]
- Okay
- Let's go
[Jimin risking it all to avoid the penalty]
I'm risking my everything
[Keyword: Awkward smile]
Awkward smile
[I'll show you!]
Awkward smile?
[Off beat]
Jimin didn't get it
He didn't jump right
[Jimin disappeared without a trace]
No way!
[Objection]
Wait, I have an objection
That's not an awkward smile
[A strong argument about the smile]
- That's not an awkward smile
- It is!
[I won't accept it!] [Excited]
That's not an awkward smile
[More than half say it is!]
That's an awkward smile
[Keyword: Wink]
1, 2, 3!
[Became timid]
- Wink
- V, you're good!
[Wink] [Confident]
V's really good
[Fighting]
[Jump!]
He didn't get it
[Members burst out laughing]
I can't hear the sound
[The perfect wink.jpg]
Wait
One of V's shoulders isn't showing
One of Jimin's eyes is gone
That's a fantastic picture
Despite the fact that I can't
normally wink well
[Jimin & V succeed!]
- Did V get it or not?
- He got it
Jimin looks really cute
You look like an elf
- I'm an angel
- 1, 2, 3
[Keyword: Fear]
- Fear?
- Fear
[Fighting again]
[What did I just see?]
[That was amazing] [Home Alone?]
[Success, no doubt!]
He got it!
- Okay
- Wait, no
- No, you have to accept this
- His shoulders are in
[Jimin succeeds amid praises!]
- Let's accept it
- You have to admit he looks really scared
[Triumphant]
- He has great expressions
- Should we go?
[Don't touch me]
- Hey! Don't touch me!
- Why?
[Keyword: Silly]
I like you
[Disturbing not allowed]
- Silly?
- Don't touch me, really
Okay, I won't touch you
[Giving hints]
Listen to the sound
Concentrate on the sound
[Again?]
[Silly]
This isn't silly
- That's being scared
- We accept Jimin!
[Both succeed with a big laugh!]
Okay! Jimin's just too funny
Both of them got it this time
[Impressed]
Jimin's doing great today
[Impressive presence]
- You did it all
- His presence is no joke
[Keyword: Cute] [Chatting]
- 1, 2, 3!
- Let's act cute
[Jimin's kind explanation]
Let's do this together
Listen to the sound
[Pfft] [Cute]
[The result of jumping with a weird noise?]
Listen to them! What's that sound?
[Do you see my fists.jpg]
This is a fail
[Both failed] [Cuteness cannot be found]
Both failed
[Keyword: Heart]
[Ready]
- I can't hear it
- Move, go to your place, don't bother me
[Jump!]
[The beauty of emptiness.jpg]
And then there was none
[Both fail the heart!]
Failed
- Next
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Expressionless]
[Can't believe this] [Laughing]
I can't be expressionless
- I can't make such an expression
- Concentrate
[Fighting]
- Oh
- They got it
[Expressionless 80 + raised cheekbones 20]
- Wait, V..
- V is smiling!
He's smiling, too
[No, it's definitely expressionless]
No, I'm expressionless!
[In denial]
It's because my hair's floating up
That's expressionless!
Honestly, only Jimin's got it this time
[Jimin succeeds!]
It's only me this time
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Sadness]
Listen well to the sound
[They don't know the virtue of a win-win]
[Nice jump]
[And the result?]
Both of them are not in
[All the sadness to me.jpg]
You both look so sad
[I'm very happy]
[Speechless at seeing the 95z sadness]
- V's definitely got it
- I can't see Jimin
Only V's got it this time
[Rebuttal]
But wait
The first picture had a similar angle
to this one
[No one recognizes his obvious mission]
Then you have to accept the first one
Can you show us the first picture?
No, you weren't in
Those are my shoulders
[Can't accept it!]
- Your clothes just went up
- No, no
[Being noisy] [Spacing out]
[Upset]
Look, they're my shoulders!
[Both of them succeed!]
- We'll accept it
- Accepted!
[Up next! j-hope and Jung Kook]
This is so funny
- Are we doing it?
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Hurrah]
Hurrah
It's hurrah
[Jung Kook, he's older]
Be quiet
[Intimidated]
Okay
[Hurrah]
[Amazed at Jung Kook's jump height]
Jung Kook jumps really high
[Hurrah]
Wow
[No one can argue against it]
- j-hope!
- This is...
[Can't argue against it] [Both Succeed!]
All right, all right
[Sorry... We did...]
They can't air this
[Everyone thinks it's funny]
This is a little too...
[j-hope is so funny]
- Next, next
- Let's go
[Shocked]
- Do I really look like that?
- It's hilarious
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Rabbit]
- Rabbit
- What about rabbit?
[Distracting him]
[Focused]
This shouldn't be allowed!
[What happened? They burst into laughter]
This isn't right
[I'm the rabbit of this group.jpg]
Come on
- Not like this
- He looks like a rabbit
[Everyone except j-hope says yes]
- Success!
- His face is like a rabbit
[Upset]
Come on
[Only Jung Kook succeeds!]
- Yes
- Yes to rabbit
[The reason j-hope failed is laughing]
[Can't believe it]
Poor j-hope
No pushing
[Yeah yeah]
No pushing from now on
[j-hope must be an angel]
No more pushing
I'll let this one pass
1, 2, 3
[Keyword: Dreamy]
Dreamy
[Jump]
[How did confident j-hope do?]
I was really dreamy
[Dreamy]
[Huge difference]
[So hilarious]
Jung Kook
[They're laughing at themselves too]
[This face has so many stories]
Jung Kook, you look like
you have a lot of stories
j-hope
Wait a minute
We can't see Jung Kook's shoulders
I jumped sideways
His shoulders are in the photo
[j-hope and Jung Kook getting compliments]
j-hope and Jung Kook's acting skills...
- Jung Kook could be an actor
- It looks like a scene from a movie
[Now the question arises]
Why don't your bangs move?
[Confident]
- I jump with ease
- Really?
- Try it
- Let's say they both failed
[Jung Kook's really good...]
No to this one
[Worried] [Both fail!]
- It looks like I'll be last
- Look at that
He looks like a peeled onion
[RM caring about his friend]
- Getting points is important
- All right
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Acting cute]
We're good at that
[j-hope & Jung Kook are almost one person]
- No distractions allowed
- No distractions
[They flew!]
I fell too soon
[Cutie]
[Expression genius Jeon Jung Kook]
This is awesome
- Your expression is unbelievable
- Wow
[So hard]
- I can't jump in time
- His expression is awesome
[Analyzing the situation like a pro]
Did I jump too soon?
[Both good acting, but failed]
We want to give you 1 point
for your acting but...
- Yeah
- The shoulders didn't make it
Those are actually my shoulders
[Other members laugh at Jung Kook's joke]
Those are my shoulders
Let's go
- Go! Let's go again
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Blank face]
- Blank face
[Actors(?) already immersed]
[So funny]
[Hush!]
We can't hear it
[Do they have springs attached?]
[j-hope and Jung Kook are good at jumping]
[Members keep laughing]
[Blank face]
- Yes to both
- Wow!
- Hey, j-hope!
- No, no
[Noisy]
j-hope! You look like a collared-lizard
[Ambiguous]
A definite yes to j-hope but...
Both of them didn't jump as high as their
shoulders but we should say yes to j-hope
[Strict]
But no to Jung Kook
[Only j-hope succeeds]
j-hope did it perfectly
[Please be quiet]
Since everyone is laughing
we can't see, I mean, hear well
- Please be quiet
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Sobbing]
[Like a choir]
Sobbing?
We're looking forward to this one
You got to cry hard
You have to really sob
[Huh?]
Too late, too late
Too fast, too fast
[Perfect]
- Yes!
[He's almost sobbing too]
This was perfect
Jung Kook doesn't look like he's sobbing
- This isn't sobbing
- They both passed
[Both passed!]
- Yes
- Isn't he sobbing?
[j-hope & Jung Kook both succeed!]
- Yes
- Yeah, go
- Let's go
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Flower pose]
[j-hope does cute things well!]
This has to be cute
[V is disturbing them]
[Will they succeed?]
Yes
[Flower pose]
Yes, yes
[Perfect]
So well done
[j-hope & Jung Kook both succeed!]
[Questions]
They jumped separately
- But they both did appear
- They're so good
[They jump separately but both make
it in the photograph]
[Boasting]
I held myself in the air
[Jimin plays along]
[j-hope goes against gravity?]
- In the air
- He defies gravity
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Heart]
Heart
- We'll look forward to this one
- Okay
[Looking forward to it]
I hope they make big hearts
[So focused]
[Jump!]
[SUGA can't figure it out]
I really don't understand the timing
[Hearts] [Perfection]
Wow, both succeeded
[Perfectly done!]
Yes, yes
[He's amazing]
Jung Kook jumped to his belly button
- Jung Kook is...
- He looks like he'll pass later
Then that won't count
- If your face doesn't make it, it's out
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Smile]
Smile
That's not hard at all
[We're good with this one]
We'll be fine
[So confident]
[Jimin thinks j-hope is so funny]
This one is easy
[Jump!]
[Upset]
I went too soon
[Amazed]
Jung Kook is really good at this
[Smile]
Well done
j-hope looks the same as the last photo
[Ctrl + C / Ctrl + V]
[It's like copy and paste]
- Wait!
- What's wrong with my hair?
[Objection]
Objection, that's not a smile
[Yeah, he is smiling rather widely]
He's practically laughing
[Argues]
Jung Kook looks like he doesn't know
what's going on, not smiling
He looks like he's clenching his jaw
[j-hope follows Jung Kook]
- No, it's a smile
- All right
[j-hope & Jung Kook both succeed!]
It's a smile, a smile
[Admiring his own jumping skills]
- I jumped so well
- You did
If your face doesn't make it in the photo
it won't count
- Should I try it?
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Rage]
[Everyone looks forward to the last word!]
- We look forward to this
- Your face can go out
[Getting ready to show rage]
Argh!
[Rage!]
[Rage]
- All right
- They're really angry
[They succeeded the last one too!]
Perfect!
We bothered each other too much
[They realize it now]
Yeah, it might end up being
one of us
[Seriously taking off his shoes]
[RM's 3rd try]
RM, are you taking off your shoes?
They're too heavy
[Meaningful comment]
Everyone, are you doing
your manito mission well?
Right
[V approaching somewhere]
Don't come
I know what you're up to
[The little one loves SUGA but
he can't be bothered]
Leave me alone
[Innocent]
[Working on their mission(?)]
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Merong]
Merong?
- Merong, I think
- Merong
[Where are you RM...]
He's gone
[Not even a strand of hair]
You're not in
[That's right...?]
Isn't that Jimin's hair?
[So funny]
Why's Jimin's hair there?
Okay
[V is crying(?) over here]
[Hey, friend]
Your timing is...
[So weird]
- I thought I made it
- The timing was way off
[Don't cry, V]
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Cute]
Acting cute?
I've never seen such timing
[V disappeared laughing so hard]
The sound of the beeps are low
[Jimin jumped behind RM]
[Too funny]
[The timing is late]
Too late
[Hehe]
Why am I so quick?
[Fail because only Jimin was captured]
[He is serious]
Am I too late?
- I'm too quick, right?
- Too quick
What should I do?
Wait, Jimin jumps better
Each of you, jump with me
one by one
- If you want to
- Next timing
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Superman]
Superman?
[Ready to jump with him]
[Jimin and Jung Kook are ready behind him]
[Even preparing matching poses]
[Everyone's timing is different]
You are too quick!
[Do re mi]
- Fail
- My shoulder is in
[Shoulder location is not clear]
It's his arm
[Unfair]
Ours was not accepted
in a similar situation
Yours was accepted
[As RM succeeded, j-hope completed
his mission automatically]
Accepted
[Quick acceptance]
- You both succeeded
- All right
Have RM jump alone
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Heart]
- A heart?
- Get the timing
[Jump!]
Well done
[Heart]
RM
Wait, that is not a heart
[SUGA secretly accomplished the mission]
Isn't this a heart?
[Slightly different, but still accepted!]
That's a heart, too
But, I'm worried that your feet will hurt
- I'll go
- Doesn't it hurt?
[RM asking how to jump without pain]
[How do you teach that?]
How am I supposed to jump?
Just jump
Okay, let's go
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword wink] [Wink expert RM?]
RM is the wink expert
Seriously
[I am serious]
[Huh?]
[Cute]
[Why the hands?]
- What was the hand thing?
- What was this?
[Cute] [Wink]
Why did you do this?
[Succeeded with a cute hand gesture!]
- Cute
- We only ordered the wink
Nice!
Let's go!
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Thumbs up]
- Thumbs up?
- Thumbs up
[Much expectation towards RM]
Make it funny
[High expectation]
I have high expectations
[Thumbs up]
[Oh]
Slightly unclear
[Thumbs up]
Accepted
Let's move on
[Like this]
He stayed in the air like this
He jumps quickly and
stays in the air long
[Keyword: Flower pose]
Flower pose
[Will he make it funny enough
to satisfy Jung Kook] Make it funny
[Using his eyes to jump with him]
I'm not sure about this
[Frustrated]
- Only his mouth is in
- He's kind of cute
- Let's move on
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Annoyed]
- Annoyed
- I'm looking forward to it
[Sharing tips]
[Already annoyed]
Stick your chin out
[Ready]
[Jung Kook looks happy thanks to RM]
[Full of annoyance]
[You're not really annoyed, are you?]
- Accepted
- He looks annoyed
[Perfect success!]
- Very annoyed
- Accepted
- 1, 2, 3!
- What is it?
[Keyword: Sobbing]
Sobbing?
It can be similar
Slightly upgraded
[Getting ready to act]
[All eyes on him]
Not sure
[Sobbing(?)]
Are you sinking?
- You're like a terminator
- Your expression was perfect
[He sobbed but failed!]
He did sob
[If only there were expression points]
I want to give him points for
his expressions
You may end up being at the bottom
[Keyword: Expressionless]
- Expressionless?
- I can see the hanbok in your future
Are you annoyed?
[I have no thoughts]
He's expressionless
[Because I simply have no thoughts]
Isn't this an annoyed face?
I think this is the expressionless face
[V's also smart, completing his mission]
He's smart, he's doing that on purpose
because he wants to wear the hanbok
[Always looking forward to RM]
Not in, not in
[Succeeded with a perfect
expressionless face!]
He's in
- Okay, okay
- This is almost an ID picture
[Going even further]
- Use this for your passport
- That's all right
[4th try! SUGA & Jin]
Now, SUGA and Jin
The odds are against me
If I end up last, I'll wear
hanbok and sunglasses
- Okay, do that if that happens
- I will
Let's go
[SUGA asking something from the members]
Please be quiet
We can't hear
[The eldest members]
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Refreshed]
- Refreshed
[I am refreshed!]
Very refreshed!
[j-hope distracting them with noise]
[What happened?]
[Puzzled]
Why aren't I there?
You jumped too early
[Jin was fooled by SUGA]
He faked it
That was amazing
[Members are amazed by SUGA's fake action]
- He's smart
- That's why he jumped early
[Sensitive]
Quiet! I can't hear
[He wants to keep the photo]
Can I get a copy of this photo?
- I love this photo
- It's refreshing. Now, quiet
[Both failed, only made members laugh]
- That's not accepted, right?
- It's not
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Goosebumps]
Goosebumps
[Busy acting and keeping the members quiet]
- Be quiet
- Fake
Quiet, I can't hear
[Members disappear
one by one as they laugh]
[What is this?]
[The eldest members making
everybody laugh]
[(Both of them) Just the tip of heads]
Be quiet!
[Clearly failed!]
Quiet, seriously
[Gasping]
I mean, we did that much before
I didn't think you couldn't hear this
- I can't hear anything
- Be quiet
- Okay, quiet
- Hush
[Too funny]
This is so funny
- Quiet
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Sulky]
[Self-hypnosis]
[We are the sulkiest]
Sulky
[Can't stand it]
So funny, really
What happened?
[Jin jumped twice but where is he?]
This is not sulky
He looks mad
[That's a mad face!]
When I'm mad, I go like this...
[V criticizes SUGA]
Your face is flat
- I'm mad
- That's not being sulky
[Jimin asks the leader to judge]
RM, come and check this
Is this being sulky?
- This is too cute
[SUGA puzzled]
This isn't sulky
[Jin wasn't in, SUGA was too cute, fail!]
If you didn't smile
that would've been accepted
- Moving on
- 1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Rabbit]
Do this
- Quiet
- Jin!
Let's be quiet
[Funny]
[How can they be this off beat?]
What are you doing?
[Rabbit]
[Jin finally succeeded!]
I got it!
[Oldest members getting mad]
I told you to be quiet!
That's right! Be quiet!
[This is too funny]
[Younger ones are scolded for no reason]
We were quiet
This group is great, seriously
We have to jump twice!
Be quiet!
[Will they be the bottom 2
as RM predicts?]
I think these two will place last
Be quiet
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Sentimental]
[Jung Kook was a good example]
Just like what I did
[Hush!]
- Quiet
- Be quiet
[Now?] [Is it now?]
[SUGA and Jin jumped after
the shutter sound again]
[And there was nobody.jpg]
This has nothing to do with distractions
[Jin frustrated as it doesn't go as he wants]
This is driving me nuts
[RM still performing his mission]
Our noise is not the problem
[What to do with those two?]
[Stop...!]
Please, for us, be quiet
[Fighting back because they were quiet]
We were very quiet
Be quiet
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Growl]
Growl
Be quiet
[I want to, but it's too funny]
[It seems they jumped well this time]
[Everything is too funny for V]
[Peekaboo] [Growl!]
[SUGA points out that his height
is the problem]
This is not me, but because of my height
[Jin succeeds!]
Jin is accepted
[We can slowly see the future]
SUGA, I can see you wearing the hanbok
SUGA, think of which one you'll wear
[Not yet]
Be quiet
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Superman]
Superman
[What?]
[Members are trying not to laugh]
[Hush!]
Be quiet
[Laughing hard]
[Jump!]
[SUGA getting mad at Jin for no reason]
[There was nobody 2.jpg]
[No one is in the frame so fail!]
Are they spies?
How can you be this bad?
[The most said words by SUGA: quiet]
- Be quiet
- Seriously!
[Members find it too funny]
He must want to wear hanbok
[SUGA failed all 7 attempts]
I haven't succeeded anything yet
[He's been crying]
Be quiet!
[Hush]
Quiet
[How can he be like this?]
He wants to wear hanbok at this point
I can't do this, it's too funny
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Batman]
Batman
[Ready with pose!]
You know?
[Jin-tman]
[Off beat as always]
SUGA got it
[Wow]
[I am the SUGA-man!]
[SUGA's first success among 8 attempts!]
Perfect!
[Super funny]
[The photo is so funny]
I now got 1 point
[The members busy laughing at the picture
to care about SUGA's success]
I finally have 1 point
Get out
[Chin hurts from laughing]
My chin hurts
[Ready to work hard]
Please give it to us
1, 2, 3!
[Keyword: Sobbing]
Will they give us a grand finale?
[Fist] [Will it satisfy everyone?]
SUGA is good at sobbing
[Jump!]
Fail!
[Very sad]
Why don't we appear?
[There was nobody 3.jpg]
[Timing seemed correct but fail!]
I thought we got it
[In doubt]
How can you be so bad?
They're really bad
The 6th and 7th place are
pretty much decided
[The last keyword]
Let's make the last one perfect
Quiet, quiet
[They have been quiet but still listen]
- Be quiet
- Don't laugh
- Don't say a word
- This is the last one, right?
[Keyword: Bye]
[Goodbye now!]
[Muted laugh]
[Quiet]
[Hehehe]
Quiet
[Jump]
They're so bad
[The members knock over from laughing]
[This is the true goodbye!]
[SUGA and Jin showed a true goodbye
and failed!]
[Too funny] [They are laughing
so hard they can't lift their heads]
[Jimin... Are you crying?]
[Title: Bye (feat SUGA, Jin)]
The photo's title is "Bye"
Please use this as the thumbnail
Game over!
Bye!
[SUGA and Jin did their best]
We did our best
- I'm crying
- I knew this team would be the best
"Bye" was the best
[Crying from laughter because he was bad]
He finds it so funny
that he was bad at this game
Let me tell you the results
of the first game
[BTS best photo zone]
[We learned how to wink from books.jpg]
[I opened my eyes and the
semester began.jpg]
[Someone told me this would be cute.jpg]
[Save me]
[Run BTS!
RM 6, SUGA 1, Jin 2]
[j-hope 7, Jimin 7,
V 5, Jung Kook 7]
[The second game]
- Run!
- BTS!
The second game, everyone
[Full of will]
What game is it?
- I'll do my best
- What is the game?
The second game is
spot the difference
- Spot the difference?
- I'm a master at this
[More sensitive because of the penalty!]
- I can't even find one
- Answer!
Those people end up wearing hanbok
[Fierce competition]
Why does this make me so nervous?
I finished
What's the last game?
[The last game where they just shout]
- Makchang!
- Wrong!
[Losing is more important than winning]
How can you get it wrong?
It's not a competition between you guys
[Fierce competition to avoid the penalty]
Is that a refrigerator?