[Run BTS]
[BTS X Manito Part 2]
[Last Episode]
[BTS X Manito Special!]
Why would you touch my neck?
How about this? 7th place
wears hanbok on the way to MAMA
[Penalty idea by Jimin]
- That's not bad
- I imagined myself wearing it
[Got some legendary pictures(?)
through the game]
[Chaos throughout the game
because of the penalty]
Look, they're my shoulders!
Wait, Jimin jumps better
Each of you, jump with me one by one
[Made each other laugh]
[Penalty receivers are becoming clearer]
Be quiet!
Game over!
Bye!
Run BTS!
[What is the second game?]
The second game, everyone
[Will to play firing up]
- What game is it?
- I'll do my best
The second game is
spot the difference
[Spot the difference?!]
- Spot the difference?
- I'm a master at this
[BTS X Manito, Second game]
[Spot the Difference]
[Looking at two pictures give by the crew
they'll have to find 7 differences]
[They will gain points according
to the order they finish!]
[If they fail to find the differences
in the 10 minutes, no points are given!]
One thing's for sure, if Jin or SUGA
place last in this game
one of them will wear the hanbok
[Beware of cheaters]
Let's not cheat
[Look at him]
- Foul! Take 1 point off!
- I didn't look
[Worked up]
[Excuses] [Hesitates]
I didn't look at it
I just stole a glance
- You saw it!
- Take 1 point off!
[Protests]
Make him start 5 seconds later
[Jin will start 10 seconds later]
Based on the majority vote
he'll start 10 seconds later
[Gives up]
- All right
- He just sighed
[Countdown]
We'll start the countdown, ready, go!
[Glances]
Please take points off of anyone who copies
[Corrects himself]
Not copies, cheats
[Bewildered]
What is this?
[10 seconds passed]
Start! Jin! Jin! Jin!
[Hurries]
Yes
How many differences are there?
[BTS is alarmed]
I can't find anything
- I can't see a single thing
- What is this?
[You can play along too]
[Spot the differences] [7 items]
[Different picture] [Original picture]
[Oh yeah]
I found one!
[Me too]
I found it! I got it!
[The members are anxious about cheating]
V, if you go back like that, it looks like
you're cheating
[They must find all 7]
You have to find all of them
[Obviously cheating]
[Pay back time]
You said I could look!
[Was this game this serious?]
What is this?
How are we supposed to find these?
[V is moving to the corner
so no one can see]
[Awkward]
I think that corner will be
a nice spot to work
[Hey]
Don't look!
[So many protests]
Don't come here! Don't come here!
[BTS is so competitive]
Everyone is so competitive...
[Determined to not show their own]
What are you doing?
He's looking! He's looking!
[Amazed]
I can't believe the staff even creates
a spot the difference game now
[Glances] [Checking]
Don't look! Come on!
- Don't look! Don't look!
- Those people end up wearing the hanbok
[Really?]
I only need 2 more
[Useful information]
- Really?
- Don't come over here
[Who are you talking to?]
- Don't look at mine! RM!
- Don't look
[Already? Are you done SUGA?]
Come on, don't cheat, for real
[Surprised] [That was nothing]
- Really?
- Submitted!
[Eyes rolling desperately
at SUGA's submission]
SUGA is really good at this
[Huh? But they say he's wrong]
- I might end up wearing the hanbok
- Wrong
[Just one]
- They say you're wrong
- I just need one more
[Which one was wrong?]
This is so well made
It's so hard to find
- I only need one more
- Everyone is struggling at the last one
[He's having a hard time too]
Jimin, want to trade answers?
[Nope]
No, I probably already
have everything you've got
[SUGA doesn't know! SUGA just doesn't!]
[CCTV]
j-hope! Jin is looking at yours!
Come on!
- How many did you find?
- I got 6
[Both have 1 left]
- What about you?
- 6? Me too
[Wow] [Done]
- How did you find 6?
- Okay! I'm done!
5 minutes left
[j-hope is 1st place]
[He tells him one and leaves] [Nervous]
I only need one more
[V submits second and then RM does]
Okay! I'm done!
[The staff look it over
and confirm j-hope is first]
I got it!
We helped each other at the end
[Manito mission] [He succeeds in exchanging
high-fives with RM 2 out of 3 times]
[Jimin submits fourth]
I'm done
[I can't...]
- Have you still not found it?
- Help me!
[V comes in 2nd place]
Nice!
[Urgent]
j-hope, I might end up
wearing the hanbok, help me
[Jin, you can do it]
Help me! I might end up wearing the hanbok
[RM is 3rd place]
- I can't find it
- Yes! 3rd place!
[RM and V's collaboration as they
exchanged answers]
Hey, bro! Trust me
[Jimin is 4th]
You should trade answers if you need it
[I saw him]
- Huh? Didn't SUGA already finish?
- He missed one
[Panting]
Here! Here!
[All right... You might fall]
[Jung Kook comes in 5th]
Why is this making me so nervous?
[Jung Kook is 5th]
Is it because of the hanbok?
[One of these 2 will end up
wearing the hanbok]
[Hm...]
Didn't he submit first?
[Here are the answers]
[On scene of the battle of two souls]
Everyone! It's a battle between
Jin and SUGA
- 2
- I think it'll be better if you
help one another. Both your scores...
[The staff gives them a hint]
We'll give you a hint
The rest of us should go forward
[1st hint!]
- We didn't touch the faces
- No faces
[2nd hint is grass?]
- And, grass
- Grass
[Staring so hard]
I didn't find the grass
[A hint in favor of Jin]
- That was a good hint for Jin
- A good one for Jin
[SUGA finishes 6th]
Let's not play this kind of game
Whether Jin makes it or not is what we
are all interested in here
[SUGA has a lot to say]
You should take points off of
people that cheated
[Then I would have zero points]
No, no
[Us?]
They said at the beginning that it
might be easier if we cheat...
[Yeah, we heard that]
Yeah, even the staff said that
[Upset]
- We said beware of cheating
- Yeah, they said beware
[SUGA pointing out all the cheating]
We should clean up the cheaters
[Really?]
Clean them up?
[Only 2 minutes left]
Where is it?
[RM is doing his mission, making a V]
- Grass
- It popped out to me
You still haven't found it?
I don't want to live in
such an unfair society...
Can you call yourself BTS?
- I really didn't cheat
- I'm BTS
- Who cheated? Who?
- No one did!
He started to look on behind me
[Perfect reenactment]
He was looking like this
[RM was cheating upfront]
[OK, got it]
[Urgent]
- 45 seconds left
- Hurry, what's the last one?
[Strict]
- I can't tell you
- Hint! Hint!
[Cheating won't help]
He can't even win with cheating!
- 30 seconds left
- Jung Kook, help me!
- I'll give you a hint when there's
3 seconds left. Over there!
- Where? Where?
3, 2, 1, time's up!
[SUGA submits for him]
You have to give it up now
[I want to know the answer]
- They grade it here
- I want to see what I missed
SUGA is so cute today
[Jin missed V's clothes]
[The staff is too much]
That was too hard
The score up to now is...
[BTS X Manito, 2nd game]
[Spot the Difference Round 1 Scores]
[RM - 5, SUGA - 2, Jin - 0]
[j-hope - 7, Jimin - 4, V - 6, Jung Kook - 3]
[What's up with him?]
Not bad
[Almost an emotional rollercoaster]
Let's move on to the next game!
- I really look forward to this being aired
- Let's give ourselves more room
[Faster than ever]
Don't come near me
[You know how I feel, right?]
Please let me look over your shoulders
[The members ask for 7 minutes]
Jin is putting his life on the line
[Giving him some advice]
If you focus, you can see it
[Ready]
- We're ready
- Ready, go!
- You didn't mess up our faces, right?
- Oh! Got one!
[It's like they're taking the CSAT]
[You can play along too]
[Spot the differences] [7 items]
[Different picture] [Original picture]
[The picture is at fault]
The picture's so big, I can't see
I'll hold it like this
[This is a variety show...
Please say something]
[It's so hard]
I can't find any this time
[Fiery eyes]
Come on, pop out to me
Does this look different to you?
[I.. I don't know]
No? Does it not?
I can't find anything
[Highest difficulty, everyone is
struggling with round 2]
It's so hard, this was well made
[Only 5 minutes left]
You have 5 minutes left
We'll give you hints...
[RM is like a BGM]
- We don't need hints
- Please give us one
No, we don't need it
I already found a lot
- Give us hints
- Please give us hints
I'll give you a hint
[1st hint is grass]
- Grass?
- What? Again?
[V rips off the photo to compare]
[Nervous]
I only need to find 2 more
[I don't get it]
The grass looks exactly the same
[1 more hint]
- Leaves
- I think you should stop giving hints
[He still can't find it]
What? What do you mean?
[I found that one already]
- I already found that one
- Shadow
[Sounds from those who found most]
He gave too many hints
That was too much!
[He's still having a hard time]
Grass, shadows?
[And he's... angry]
Was there a mistake?
I think I was given the same photos
The 3rd hint, pattern
[4th hint]
SUGA's foot
[Confused]
What about my foot?
Your foot is really pretty
[Shocked]
I can't find more than 3
What should I do?
Okay, one more left
[Jung Kook and Jimin are doing well]
This one was hard to find
Me too, me too
[Who is he talking to?]
I don't get the grass and
shadows hint, I really don't!
[The staff is giving away so many hints]
There are 2 on the floor
The sofa
[3 more minutes added to make 5]
- Give us 10
- This one is so hard...
[We can't see you either]
I can't see anything
I can't find the last one
[Do you want to trade?]
RM, do you want to
switch the sofa one for SUGA's foot?
[No]
I don't think I should trade with you
[#Edited_So_Well]
[We'll share the answer with you!]
This was edited so well
- RM! Did you find SUGA's foot?
- Yeah, did you find the sofa one?
[Of course]
I found the sofa one
[RM & V trade answers]
I found the sofa one too...
Why not me?
[Come on]
- Hey!
- We have the same scores
[Deep sigh]
[There we go]
Jin, do you want to team up with me?
[Sounds good]
- Should we?
- We have to survive
[Trading answers]
Jung Kook, did you find the sofa?
I have everything but that
[Everyone is swapping]
- What do you have?
- I've got the one on the floor...
[Lonely]
You guys are too much, all teaming up
We only have these between us
[Whispering]
[Wait]
You haven't found anything? Hey!
[Jimin is the first one done]
Hey! You! SUGA!
He didn't find anything and
then asked to team up
[Jimin is 1st place]
Finish
- How come you didn't tell me
- Sorry
- 3 minutes left
- I'm done! Here!
[j-hope & V sweetly exchanging answers]
[Let me in]
[Jung Kook is 2nd place]
[Jimin failed at making a heart together!]
- I love you
- This was a perfect game
[RM is 3rd place]
- I'm done
- He took 2 of mine for free!
[V is 4th place]
I only took one
[Bewildered]
- I can't find the last one
- Which one?
Thanks, j-hope
You helped me out a lot
- 2 minutes left
- SUGA's foot...
[The members who are finished can't help]
- You can't help if you're done
- Of course
Almost there! Almost!
[j-hope is 5th]
This one was so hard
[So interesting]
I'm going to see how SUGA is doing
[All gathered around]
You can't tell them the answers
- 1 minute left
- Are the ones I found correct?
[2nd match of the century]
- Another killer match
- On the floor, the floor, the floor
- 30 seconds left
- What's different about the floor?
[So interesting]
It's neck-and-neck
No one can tell
10 seconds!
[SUGA gets up to submit?]
SUGA?
[What will happen to SUGA?]
Time's up
You sound like you're having so much fun
Such a happy voice
[Just 1 left]
- I missed one
- How many did you find?
[Boasting]
- 4
- We'll give whoever found more, 1 point
SUGA gets 4 points
- Jin gets 2
- You all cheated
[I'm innocent!]
He found nothing and came
to me to cheat off mine
[Making up excuses] [Jin is upset]
- I found one but he already had it
- I'm upset
[Take this]
Are you upset?
[BTS X Manito, 2nd games]
[Spot the Difference]
[RM: 5+5= 10 points]
[SUGA: 2+1= 3 points, Jin: 0+0= 0 points,
j-hope 7+3= 10 points, Jimin: 4+7= 11 points]
[V: 6+4= 10 points, Jung Kook: 3+6= 9 points]
[Now everything is up to this game]
Everything is up to this last game!
What is the last game?
[The last game is 7X7 Bingo]
- The last game is bingo
- Bingo!
[BTS X Manito, Last Game 7X7 Bingo
*Theme - Food, They must act out the word]
[they want to cross off and will be awarded
points according to the order they finish]
[The member who guesses correctly
will get to act out the next word]
[If no one guesses within a minute
the chance goes to the member on the right]
[If no one finishes within the 30 minutes
the number of words crossed
out will determine the ranking]
[Beware of the wind that comes
from the mics with a wrong answer]
- Let's start
- Ready, go!
[Slurp] [Wiggle wiggle]
[No no]
[Jin is eating something]
We have to get it
- Ramyeon
- Wrong!
Answer!
[Wind attack]
- Hurry, hurry! Go!
- Answer, pickled radish
[Wind attack]
- Answer, kimchi
- Correct!
[Whining]
- How come I had to get the wind?
- Sorry
[V gets to go next]
- Hurry up, hurry up
- V, go!
[Like this]
- Answer! Ramyeon!
- Correct
[Making a square and cutting it?]
Here I go
- Answer! Doenjangjjigae
- Correct
[Now my turn]
- Where is it?
- Okay, here I go
[We didn't ask for expressions but
he's good]
Me!
[Does it need to be this serious?]
Did you call out, "Answer?"
[Have to hold the mic first]
- Do we have to?
- The one who grabs the mic first...
- Banana
- Okay
What? Banana?
[RM is doing well]
- Jimin
- Mine is easy
[V runs out as soon as he sees]
Answer! Steak
- Steak isn't on mine
- Where is it?
[10% at a bingo]
Mine is all over the place
I'm doomed
[Looking forward to him]
- V, your turn
- Here I go
[1. Open 2. Hesitate]
[3. Ouch! It's hot!]
I know!
[What is this?] [4. Peel]
- What is it?
[What's up with the face?]
Roasted sweet potato
[Will j-hope be correct?]
[Nope]
It's just sweet potato
[Wind attack]
- Wrong!
- Why'd you say the answer?
[Jimin gets to play]
Jimin is lucky
[Almost done]
- Thanks
- Jimin, get up
[Big bites] [I know]
What is that?
- Apple
- Correct
[How did he get that one?]
- Really?
- How was that an apple?
[Jung Kook is looking for SUGA urgently]
- SUGA
- Be quiet
[Jung Kook is trying his mission]
You know, right?
[Fast to catch on]
It must be his mission
[Talking aimlessly]
No, we talked about this...
We looked each other in the eye...
I trust you, I trust our friendship
[Rejects him]
There's no such thing
I'm not on your side
- Hey, we went to eat there often
- Here we go!
[Turns then eats]
Answer!
- What's that?
- Spaghetti! Pasta!
Pasta! Correct!
[So close!]
Hold on, I have to look for it
Hold on, here it is
[Me + You ??]
Here I go
[What is this?]
- What?
- Answer! Answer!
- Japchae
- Correct
- So smart
- He got it right away
[I don't have it]
Huh? I don't have it
Here it is, here I go!
[Already so noisy]
Here I go!
- What is it?
- Answer! Ogyeopsal
[Oh no]
- Hurry up, hurry up!
- Samgyeopsal
[Upset]
How come I got the wind attack?
Hey!
What?
[If you get this one, we accept]
- You understood that?
- Sweet potato
- He's so smart
- How is that sweet potato?
[V wants to hear Jin say "You're smart"]
- I'm smart, aren't I?
- Go Go!
[V's 2nd try]
- I was smart, right?
- Yeah, you were smart
[Kidding]
Be quiet
- What's that?
- Answer, pork
[Surprised] [Oops...]
[Ahh]
- Answer, gopchang
- Wrong!
- Makchang
- Wrong
[Everyone is looking closely]
Can you act it out once more?
- Answer, sundae
- Correct
[Oh no]
- Wow
- I don't have that
Let's go, what's yours?
[He's making it look tasty]
Get out of my way, come on
- Dwaejigukbap
- Wrong
[I get attacked by wind often]
Move over, move over
- Haejangguk
- Wrong!
- The hint is too weak
- I know!
[Confident]
- Rice!
- Wrong
[Nope...]
Answer! Kimchijjigae
- Rice
- Wrong
[1 minute passed, now it's Jimin's turn]
- It's bad for us if 1 minute passes
- It's Jimin
[What's this?]
Here I go
[Everyone can tell it's lemon]
- Lemon!
- Come on
[He only needs one more]
- Jung Kook! Jung Kook!
- I got bingo
[Surprised]
- Bingo?
- We can choose to not answer
[Jung Kook can't hear anything...]
Everyone, don't get this one
- Everyone, don't get this one
- Hurry up
[Masters at making him feel better]
- Come on
- We'll guess for you
[Like this] [I know!]
- Okay!
- Answer!
- Hamburger
- Nice. Bingo!
[Jimin & Jung Kook got bingo
at the same time]
We both got bingo
It's not a fight between
you two anyway
We're the ones with our lives
on the line
- That's awesome
- There's something about us
- Me?
- You should go. Jin should go
[Working hard]
- What's that?
- Can it be...
[Wrong]
- Fries
- Correct
[j-hope's bingo board is ambiguous]
Mine is all over the place
[My turn]
Look at me closely
[Put something in his ears and watching?]
You eat it with your ears?
[No]
- Earphones
- You can eat earphones?
[Why is his mouth like that?]
- Melon
- Correct
[That was it?]
- Melon?
- It's pronounced "meron"
[Melon is correct]
It's melon
- It's time for everyone's favorite snack
- Everyone's favorite?
- j-hope
- Okay
[100 points for facial expressions!]
[It's something spicy]
- Spicy?
- Answer, spicy rockfish stew
[You got this at once?]
[I must be a genius]
Are you a genius?
He was surprised after getting it right
[Sob]
- I wrote samgyeopsal twice
- V
[It looks similar to the last one...]
How come all of yours look the same?
- Why do you keep pointing at me?
- Dwaejigukbap
[So frustrating]
Wrong
[Confident]
I know!
[I just forgot...]
- What was I going to say?
- Shouldn't that count as a wrong answer?
- Jjigae!
- What jjigae?
[That's not it...]
Wrong
[Oh no]
- We don't have time!
- Gukbap
Answer! Come on!
- Just gukbap?
- Yes
[Stirring around]
Answer! Pasta
[Pasta was already mentioned]
- We already did pasta
- Wrong
[Oh no]
- Answer!
- I got you
- Carbonara
- Why are you answering?
Wrong!
[Looking at the acting once more]
Answer, oil pasta?
[Pft] [Jung Kook's hint, think simple]
You should think simple
[Out of nowhere]
Answer, beef brisket
[Dumbfounded]
This is driving me nuts
- Answer, spaghetti
- Correct
[But V didn't write it...]
- He doesn't have any of these
- I don't
- Is it you? V?
- I'll go
- This one is going to be hard
- What is it?
[Round and round]
[Bewildered]
Samgyetang
[It's not?]
[No...]
Wrong
- Bibimbap
- Wrong
[Why don't they get this?]
- Bibimguksu
- Wrong
[Wild]
- I know!
- Answer!
[We're going to state
all the noodles in the world]
[V is acting fervently]
[SUGA gets up]
What is that?
- Bibimmyeon
- Correct!
[V gets bingo!] [Look at me]
Look
[Nom]
Answer! Tteokbokki
[Glances]
- Is that right?
- Correct
[RM gets bingo]
[Last one! Sandwich]
I'm done
- This one is too easy
- Pizza
- Wrong
- You don't know this?
[SUGA looks so confident]
- That was said already
- It's so easy
[So confident]
- SUGA, this one is too easy
- Triangle shaped kimbap
[This isn't it?]
- Wrong
- You don't know this?
- Sandwich!
- Correct!
[Jin finishes bingo!]
Bingo!
[SUGA and j-hope remain]
- Here I go
- Do I guess alone?
You have to guess, but if we don't guess
each other's on purpose
[True meaning: let's give it our best]
30 minutes just go by like that
Let's try to hurry up, all right?
[Pulls] [It's like a bow]
Bow!
[Acting]
I really don't get this one
[He's acting so well]
[My score to you is 100]
His acting is pretty good
[SUGA is working even harder]
He's ripping it
[So many questions]
Why is he eating it like that?
[Let me just try]
- Kimchijjigae?
- Correct
[SUGA finishes his bingo!]
Bingo!
[Such sweet angels...]
- We'll guess for you
- There's still time
[I know]
I know!
[Already?]
Raw fish
- Burdock
- No
[I'm not afraid of the wind]
[No one can act as well as him]
[All watching a mime show]
- Agwijjim
- Father?
- Let's go
- One more?
- Okay! Miyeokguk
- Yes! Bingo
[BTS X Manito game results]
[Photo zone + Spot the Difference
+ Bingo Results]
[1st place Jimin: 7+11+7=25]
[2nd place Jung Kook: 7+9+7=23]
[3rd place RM: 6+10+4=20]
[3rd place V: 5+10+5=20]
[5th place j-hope: 7+10+1=18]
[6th place SUGA: 1+3+2=6]
[7th place Jin: 2+0+3=5]
[Jin and SUGA get the penalty!]
[Frustrated] [So excited]
The total score is...
[1st place Jimin]
Wow, I can't believe it
It's my first time placing first
as BTS
[So excited]
It's my first time
Jimin! And there's also a special prize
- What is it?
- The member in 6th place
- will have to wear the CHIMMY character
- You have to wear mine, then?
[Likes that idea]
That's awesome
- 2nd place is Jung Kook
- Yeah!
Joint 3rd place is V and RM
My bro!
5th place is j-hope
[I don't want to look up]
- 6th place, SUGA
- Yeah!
[Is that such good news?]
- Hanbok!
- 7th place, Jin
[So close]
How close was it? 1 point
♪ It'll be all right ♪
The hanbok is so pretty
- You have to wear hanbok to MAMA
- You'll make it in the news
- "Jin Wears Hanbok to MAMA?"
- You'll look like a boyfriend
It was a rough fight
[Finally time to show the missions]
Let's take turns guessing
Starting with RM
[Me?]
I really don't know
[Is RM's manito Jin?]
Jin? I really don't know
Who is it?
[Wrong]
- Wrong
- It isn't him?
[SUGA guesses V!]
- SUGA?
- V
[SUGA guessed wrong too]
No? Why not?
- It wasn't him
- Wow
[Counting his chickens first]
- Is it me?
- I think it's V or Jin
[Not sure]
I think it's Jin or V...
I don't think any of us will
guess correctly
I think it's V!
[Wrong]
It's Jin
[You only got it now?]
What about V?
[V guessed Jung Kook]
I guess Jung Kook
[Yeah..]
- Wrong
- No one is getting it
[Jimin thought it was SUGA or V]
I thought it was either SUGA or V
- Why am I so popular?
- V was going around to everyone
[Wink]
[Jimin selects SUGA!]
I think it's SUGA
[Wrong]
[Hesitant]
- Jung Kook, let's go!
- I know who it is...
[Tell us]
- You're worried you won't get the prize?
- Just guess
[It's you...]
Me?
[Talking with his eyes]
- He was like that to everyone
- Come on and tell us
[Jung Kook thinks...]
- Tell us
- V
[Wrong!]
It wasn't him? Really?
[Will Jin say V, too?]
- Say V, too
- Will Jin be correct?
Jung Kook
[No one guessed correctly]
Everyone was wrong?
I was Jimin's manito
[Surprised]
- Really?
- My mission was so easy
[Mission was to make a V behind Jimin]
It was to make a V behind him
[RM succeeded easily]
[So many times...]
[Mission clear!]
[So jealous]
That's so easy
[Upset]
Come on, that was too easy
[Everyone is jealous of his easy mission]
- So I did it like 7 times
- He picked well
[Saddened] [Upset] [Smiles]
You all picked it yourselves...
[Everything was fate]
- Then you should have picked it!
- The staff like RM
[SUGA's manito was V]
I had V
It was to make a heart next to V
[Mission clear!]
[Upset]
- That was easy too
- The director must like SUGA
[Really?]
I think so
[Mission was to high five with his manito]
My mission was to high five
Is that why you kept doing it to me?
[Bingo]
My manito was RM
[Once, twice, three times]
[Everyone's mission was so easy]
Yours were all easy
- You do that all the time
- We do it all the time
[It was so easy to do]
He always high-fives people
- I thought everyone had
difficult missions like me
- Me too! Mine was hard
But we couldn't make it so obvious
[He had a plan in doing his mission]
But I had to be secretive about mine
I tried to trick everyone
[V's manito was Jin!]
My manito was Jin
[Mission]
I had to hear, "You're smart" from him
- Jin, I was smart, right?
- Yes, you were smart
[V's mission was hard but he did it well]
- That was really hard
- Wow
[Haha]
V is good at this kind of thing
[Jimin doesn't sound confident]
My manito was Jung Kook
[Had to make a heart with Jung Kook]
I gave up because we had to
do a heart together
That was hard
[Didn't you do it earlier?]
You did it earlier
[With V...]
He did it with me
[Oh]
Oh no! You should have called him out!
[It hurts so much...]
You should have been smarter about it
Just do it now
[Heart]
[Jimin put a lot of thought into it]
Was that why you asked me?
I told him that people made
hearts like this
[Not sure]
I'm not sure if it was
caught on camera or not
I did it though
[Was it filmed...?]
We did it, but the directors were
holding a meeting at the time
[It made it on camera]
- People make hearts like this
- Really?
[Bewildered]
[A handshake out of happiness]
[Jung Kook's manito was SUGA]
My manito was SUGA
[Mission was to lock fingers together]
- What was your mission?
- To lock hands
[Jung Kook is bold and tries his mission]
- You know me, right?
- You must be my manito
You were too obvious
But SUGA didn't get it
[Reflects on himself]
I'm a fool, I don't know anything
[Jin's manito was j-hope]
- My manito was j-hope
- And your mission?
- I think it must have been really hard
- It was
[To hear "Stop it" from j-hope]
To hear "Stop it" from j-hope
I don't usually say that kind of thing
[That was Jin's big picture?]
That's why I kept cheating earlier
I think he said it
[Jin failed]
Don't look
Only one person won't get a gift
[Jin, who will wear hanbok]
Jin, who will wear hanbok
- It hurts my heart
- He has to wear hanbok
and won't get anything
[I feel so bad for him]
It makes me so sad
[Time for gifts]
RM will get j-hope's gift
[Gift prepared by j-hope]
- That's mine, right?
- Yes, is it underwear?
- It's underwear
- SUGA will get Jung Kook's
SUGA, you can guess what it is
by the size, right?
[What is it?]
- It's a diffuser
- Diffuser
[I see]
Jin's gift will go to j-hope
[What is it?]
- Lucky j-hope
- Jin!
[What is it? He can't contain himself]
Wow!
[Cheers]
What is that? Is that a fridge?
[Of course]
- Do you think I'll like it?
- Yes
[What is it? The staff bursts out
laughing at SUGA's gift]
V will get SUGA's
[V will like SUGA's gift]
- What is this? A book?
- You'll love it
[What is it?]
- Isn't it our album?
- No
- It's RM's
- The best gift
[What is it?] [Acting like he doesn't know]
- SUGA...
- What?
[Jimin -> Jung Kook]
This is Jimin's
It's heavy, what is it?
[The staff decide to give Jin
something too]
[Yes]
- We all think he should get one
- Thank you
[Time to open]
Let's go one by one
[Excited] [Jin opens V's gift]
- Jin first
- I got something nice
[Everyone is amazed at V's gift]
- Wow!
A cactus!
[Looking closely]
- Cacti are cool
- So pretty
[Nice for decorating]
They're good for decoration
[I want it]
It's so unique
None of us have plants in our rooms
But I wanted to get a cactus
[And that someone is me?]
and I wanted someone to grow it with me
[V wanted to share his cactus]
Let's grow them together!
[Perfect]
- I'm going to get one too
- This is a nice gift
So nice
[Jung Kook opens Jimin's gift]
- What is this?
- Underclothes?
It's much prettier than you think
[So curious]
- I know what this is!
- Show us! Show it to us
[Stammers]
The cat lights up after you plug it in
[So cool! A cat lamp!]
A lamp!
I like this
I've never seen a lamp this big
[Since I'm a calico cat]
I'm a calico cat, everyone
He's promoting himself
It's worse than this
[Jimin got RM's gift]
- Jimin
- I got RM's
[Confident]
My gift is really practical
[What is RM's practical gift?]
- Thank you
- I'm going to get one for me
- Heat-tech underclothes
- They're underclothes
I tried all kinds of underclothes
[RM selected his gift carefully]
but those are the warmest
[Awesome]
- Thanks, I'll really wear them
- RM
[What did he get from j-hope?]
- Mine is from j-hope
- What is it?
- A mini vault?
[RM destroys things often]
Don't break it
- My gift is a vault
- That's a good gift
[Hold on]
- I was going to get one
- Isn't it a strange size?
[It's so small you can carry it]
You can just carry it whole
But it's unique
[A gift from Jung Kook]
- What is this?
- It's a diffuser
[Jung Kook's cool gift]
It's a diffuser
It's tree-shaped
[Everyone got a nice gift]
We all got nice gifts for each other
[He's getting so talkative]
Show them what it is
I want to explain mine
[We shouldn't be laughing but...]
- It's... Oh...
- Really?
[SUGA's gift is the most expensive]
It's really expensive
[Take pride!]
You can't get it anywhere
SUGA fans
[See you online]
I'll post this on the online market
Just 1000 won!
[I have to buy that!]
[SUGA's present is his stands]
It's made in Japan
[Not 1, but 4!]
There are four of them!
It's not 4000 won
[4 for 1000 won]
All 4 for just 1000 won
[Including shipping charges]
- Including shipping?
- I'll pay for shipping
[4 mini SUGA figures for 1000 won!]
That's minus 1500 won!
[Free shipping]
[If you want world star SUGA]
You can't buy it anywhere
[Call right now] [Almost sold out]
[Nice offer]
I'll really post it
[The last gift]
Let's go, j-hope!
[It's so big, everyone is excited]
- I'm really curious
- Can I hold it?
[So many guesses]
- It's really heavy
- Is it a sand bag?
It's a bearbrick box
[What is Jin's gift?]
It's really amazing
[So amazed]
- Wow...
- Rice puffs...
[Rice puffs]
30,000 won worth of rice puffs
[Claps] [Kind of practical]
You can eat this for 5 years
- Awesome
- No, there's something else
[V is jealous]
- There's something more?
- At least you can eat that
[My present]
j-hope, what do you think? Do you like it?
[j-hope really likes it]
- I like it
- Where are you going to keep this?
In j-hope's room
That's all we have prepared
for today's Run BTS
[We're happy if you are]
Let's give everyone a round of applause
- I'm looking forward to this episode
- Me too
Do you all like your gifts?
[The members like their gifts]
Yes, I really do, I'm really thankful
[Collecting his gifts] [Look at him]
We had a lot of fun playing games and...
[Working out]
I'm going to use them to work out
[Seriously]
- It looks amazing
- Thank you for these
[Nice comments for each other]
- The games were fun, and everybody got gifts
- That's great
I should put some in here
[Manito special was fun!]
We had a lot of fun for the manito special
and it was meaningful for us too
[Yes]
Run BTS!
[The penalties remain!]
- With hanbok and CHIMMY
- I'm so relieved
[While the two members are upset]
- I'm really looking forward to it
- Will continue
[Run BTS! See you next time!]
- Run!
- BTS!
Thank you everyone! Bye!
Run BTS will continue
I'm glad that I got to wear it
since I'm a fashion leader
[Jin's hanbok fitting session]
[Jimin is helping?]
Please prepare a Korean traditional hat too
[Mic drop with the Korean traditional look]
[Dance]
[So happy]
I'll see you when we leave
Thank you
[Day of departing for MAMA]
[j-hope is telling them about Jin]
Good morning
He looks nice
I was so surprised in the morning
[Respect]
He's really amazing
[Are you here?]
[Kim Seokjin (27)/ V LIVE victim]
Hello, everyone
I'm BTS's Jin, a victim of V LIVE
[Speaking gibberish]
My clothes are too fitting
[I won't say too much...]
Jin, I feel for you
[Jimin is proud of Jin who will show off
the country's hanbok]
Jin is wearing our proud hanbok
I'm glad that he'll be able to
show off our traditional clothes
[Jimin is proud of his looks too]
Since he's so handsome
he looks so good in it
I thought he was wearing hanbok
[V came to see Jin]
I came to see you
You look amazing
You pop out even more than I do
Are you doing a penalty too?
[ARMY]
We'll have lots of fun
and stay healthy!
Bye!
Kim Seokjin!
[Wow! He's amazing]
He's so awesome
- Look forward to it!
- Coming soon!
[Jin came in last at BTS X Manito special]
[As a penalty, he showed up to the
airport in hanbok]
[But he looked so handsome in it]
[that ARMY have fallen for him once more]