[Run BTS - Kimchi Battle]
Run BTS!
[Looking at Jin]
I smell something
[Sniff]
- Yes, really...
- What's this smell?
Where are we?
It's the heart of Korea
[What are these ingredients for?!]
- There are napa cabbages
- You can tell right away, right?
I think we're going to make kimchi
Is that right?
[Today's Run BTS! ]
[BTS makes kimchi
as the gimjang season is here!]
[Divided into three teams]
[They make kimchi from different
regions (Gyeonggi, Gyeongsang, Jeolla)]
[Which team will make the best kimchi?]
- Wow
- Making different kimchi by region
Why don't you promote your hometown?
What kind of kimchi is popular in Geochang?
We make kimchi with oysters
Oh!
- Oyster kimchi!
- Yes
- What about Gyeongsang Province?
- My mother's kimchi is the most famous
- Can I ask my mother for help?
- Yes, you can
- For 60 seconds, nice
- 60 seconds
We call it jimchi in Chungcheong Province
- Jimchi?
- Why?
[Trying out Chungcheong by Gyeonggi man]
- Should I make jimchi today
- Jimchi
That sounds like some noir film
Cabbage kimchi in Gyeonggi Province
- Cabbage kimchi
- That's good
[Gyeongsang - kkakdugi, suyuk]
- Kkakdugi in Gyeongsang Province
- Kkakdugi
Altari
Or chonggak kimchi
- But...
- Perilla leaf kimchi in Jeolla
- and burdock kimchi
- What? I've never heard of it
- Is there such a thing?
- I know perilla leaf kimchi
But what is burdock kimchi?
They make kimchi with burdock?
They make kimchi with this
[Burdock]
Isn't this a danso?
[Witty j-hope]
I was in a danso club
[Time to team up]
- Let's choose our partners
- Please
- Does anyone want to change?
- Let's just go for it
[Sneak]
- Should we open it one by one or together?
- Let's do it together
[Changing their papers]
What? No, I won't change
Not a chance
[The younger members, crazy as usual]
I don't have anything
Don't take mine, I need one
Let's open it
1, 2, 3
[Checking out the region]
Perilla leaf kimchi, burdock kimchi
The three Kims
Come on out
[Cabbage kimchi team: RM, Jin, and V]
Hello, we're 3 Kims
[Kkakdugi, suyuk: j-hope, Jung Kook]
Gyeongsang Province
[Perilla leaf, burdock kimchi: SUGA, Jimin]
Perilla leaf and burdock
Never heard of burdock kimchi
[Jeolla and Gyeongsang chemistry]
When Jeolla and Gyeongsang work together,
- what kind of kimchi will come into...
- Kkakdugi
[Kkakdugi team, each saying what they want]
We should make suyuk as well
[Jin can tell how it's going to be]
Looks like I have to make kimchi by myself
[Kim: Jin, Chi: RM and V]
He's Kim, and we're Chi
[Listening]
We'll keep the kimchi you make today
to make some kimchi dish later
My kimchi fried rice is awesome
[Proud of Jin]
Jin is a great cook
I've made kimchi for five years
when I was in elementary school
Sure
[What is it?]
- Burdock kimchi is...
- I know, I've never heard of it
All we have to do is listen to Jin
[Jin's tips on making cabbage kimchi]
It's simple
First, get the cabbages salted
It takes a day, so we go home
[The staff is prepared for this]
- See you tomorrow
- The cabbages are salted
We invited a Korean food expert
who will help you
[Applause!]
Wow, hello
[Bow] [Park Jungsook]
- Hello
[1998-2001 Cook master of Miryang City]
I have a license in Korean cuisine
[Currently runs a restaurant]
I'm honored to join the global stars
[Wow]
- We're flattered
- Thank you
[Let's cut to the chase]
What should we do now?
You'll be given the recipe, and if you
have questions, you can ask her
All right
Why don't we shout "Run BTS"?
[Voice breaking?]
- Run BTS!
- Let's make kimchi, let's go!
[Making kimchi START!]
- Now, make kimchi
- Here we go
[Under the leadership of RM?]
One should be in charge of radish
[Deep sigh] [V... are you doing surgery?]
I'll take care of water parsley
- I'll cut water parsley into 3 cm long
- All right
This is 3 cm long
[The length is so obviously different]
- This long?
- That's 10 cm
This is 20 cm
[Dumbfounded]
It should be 3 cm long
Why do you bring up 20 cm?
[Innocent]
- This is exactly 20 cm
- Will you split that into seven?
[SUGA is enlightened]
They make plastic gloves extra long
Amazing
[Huh...?]
We should make suyuk and pork together
[Serious]
Should I boil water?
[Everyone is all over the place]
Not yet
Suyuk doesn't take long, this does
- Boil water and make suyuk first
- I know, that's what I thought
[j-hope tells him off, but
Jung Kook works quietly]
I've lived three more years than you
[Jimin uses the 60-sec mother chance]
I'm using the 60-second chance
[V is putting on surgical gloves]
- My mom set the Rolly Rolly song
- That's nice
- Mom
- Yeah
I'm filming something, Mom
- I have to make perilla leaf kimchi
- Okay
[Working hard]
- Perilla leaves are salted
- They're salted?
[Concentrated]
I think so
[Doing their own things]
Hello?
Perilla leaves are supposed to be salted
[The teacher teaches an easy way to SUGA]
That will make things messy
[Say something, guys...]
Do it in one stroke
Push it harder
At one stroke
There you go
[j-hope is preparing water for suyuk]
- How should I make a cut?
- Neatly
Neatly?
[j-hope and Jung Kook's great chemistry]
- Repeat after me "If possible"
- "If possible"
[The teacher's demonstration]
Like this
And put the whole thing in
[Super serious]
- Right now?
- Yes
♪ Mom, My mother ♪
[j-hope is worried about SUGA]
SUGA, are you doing okay over there?
[Shrug]
I'm quite a good cook, for real
[V is watching the members cook]
Can you cook, V?
You should cut like this
That's easier
[I've never cooked, but I've seen a lot]
How would you cut like that?
[The kkakdugi team divided their roles]
Peeling the radish is so much work
[SUGA and Jung Kook say
their work is the hardest]
I think this is the hardest work
Hey, a radish is big enough to peel
But burdock is too thin
- I'm done, now I should cut it into cubes
- Cut it into a heart shape
You put so much effort
Your kimchi will turn out really great
I'll do my best
[Jimin's 60-second mom chance is over]
Okay, Mom, I got it
[Jung Kook is cutting carefully]
Cut it
It should have been the other way around
Like this
What are you doing, V?
Mince salted shrimp
[If you won't cook, sing a song]
Why don't you sing a song?
[I'll take song requests]
Any song requests? I can sing anything
- Song requests?
- Yes
"Save Me"
[Save Me]
♪ Give me your hands, save me, save me ♪
[Keeps singing even while changing places]
♪ I need your love before I fall, fall ♪
What are you doing?
Is that some background music?
[A guy who got excited while making kimchi]
Yeah, there you go!
[Dangerous]
Stop dancing
I might cut myself
Yes, that's possible
[SUGA shows a talent in gimjang?]
I think I'm pretty skilled
- Should I put everything?
- You guys put a lot of effort into this
I think you should put everything in
[SUGA's accent]
Gimjang requires efforts
[Angel j-hope cares about the staff]
For our staff members
Isn't a grater for grinding?
It can make julienne strips?
[Jin was cutting with a knife]
It's the 20th century
The 21st century
[Amazed]
[Surprised]
[Jin is enlightened]
It's like a new world
[What is it?]
When you use this...
[SUGA is surprised Jin didn't know]
What age are you living in?
[Oh]
Awesome
[Jung Kook is chopping with
his veins popped out]
You're doing really great
- What's the saddest vegetable?
- Burdock
[How funny]
Then what is the happiest vegetable
in the world?
- How would I know that?
- Cabbage
[V has a knack for decoration]
I'll decorate it
[Glance]
Okay, you do that
Find lots of plates
This should do the trick
I need plates!
[V has an eye for plating]
This is perfect
Are you still peeling?
[Feeling guilty]
Hey! Peeling is important
[Jimin is puzzled]
- I wasn't talking to you
- Really?
I think all I can do is decoration
[Working hard]
[V is working on decoration at the back]
Let's make and acrostic poem with kimchi
Kim
Kim Seokjin, Kim Namjoon,
and Kim Taehyung
- Chi
- Are cheeky
[Dumbfounded]
How come there's only such a word for Chi?
[Acrostic poem with carrot]
Let's try again with carrot
Car
- You go ahead, car
- You
- Rot
- have a strong will
[j-hope is discussing with Jung Kook]
- Am I doing it right?
- As for the thickness
[Listen carefully]
You know kkakdugi we usually eat
Think about that and cut it
The width doesn't really matter
[Working hard]
Whether it's in heart shape or not
[The decoration is done in the meantime]
I engraved BTS
[BTS decoration by V]
- Cool, isn't that B.S?
- B, T, no
Nice
Let's make kimchi with this
[Jin encourages him, giving missions]
That's neat
One each for Jin, V, and RM
- That's going to be a little hard
- What I'm doing is hard too
This is a special radish, guys
If you get this, you're the lucky one
[Focusing on making kimchi]
Who am I talking to?
- To ARMY
- Who am I talking to?
[j-hope is talking with ARMY]
I put my heart and soul into this radish
[j-hope's heart toward the fans]
[V is teaching RM...?]
RM, if you don't cut this,
leaving just this...
No can do
That will make kimchi bitter
[Thick face, teaching him again
as if nothing happened]
That will make it bitter
The leaves should be removed
[Busy]
Hey, isn't this too big?
[A radish as big as a fist]
Did you have kkakdugi this big?
[Is that a cubed radish?]
That looks like a soap
[Amazed]
This is so...
I wonder how my mom did all this
[Realizing the parents' hard work and love]
My shoulders are sore
[j-hope is creating art with the radish]
Everyone, I put my heart into
this second piece of radish
[Jung Kook's frustration pent up inside]
Come on, I cut this much,
and he cut only this much
[j-hope is stammering]
You can take it if you want
[RM is confused]
[The cabbage kimchi looks confused]
Right here
[Doesn't know where to put the vegetable]
- Right here
- Just put it there?
Yes, right here
[3 cm-long water parsley]
He thinks this is 3 cm
[So silly]
[Brazen]
I was going to cut it, Jin
Here's the third piece of radish
[Jung Kook is stressed out because of him]
All right
[j-hope calms him down]
- I cut this much
- Okay, I'll get serious now
[Passing the radish to Jung Kook]
- We have so much work to do
- All right
You just passed this to me
[Each team has a frustrated member]
- Cut it right!
- There's a mandoline
[Jimin used the knife
as he didn't know there's a mandoline]
- I can just use this?
- Yeah
Jin did just the same thing
[Carrots are julienned real quick]
Wow
The world has come a long way, everyone
[#Be careful_ promoting a mandoline]
Use this utensil so you won't cut your hand
[Scared] [Jin is scared by the scissors]
Don't hold the scissors toward me, RM
[RM is scared of himself]
- I'm scared of RM
- I'm scared of myself
- Scallions
Chop these scallions
Here!
- Scallions! Scallions!
- Where did that come from?
You're so full of beans today
What's j-hope's favorite
character in "One Piece"?
Chopper!
[It's like a teen series]
Good, I'm feeling encouraged!
[Grabbing a handful]
V!
[Freak out]
- Stop
- Those scallions
[V's touch causes a commotion]
- That's too many scallions
- Stop, stop
How long has it been?
30 minutes?
All I'd been doing for 30 minutes
was cutting carrots? It's depressing
[Kim brothers are watching the eldest Kim]
I feel like...
[This feels strange, but not bad]
It feels a little...
How do you tell something is
slightly blanched?
[I can teach you!]
To blanch means to
dip it and take it out quickly
[SUGA is bothered by "slightly"]
I know that
But "slightly" is ambiguous
Slightly? It means to parboil real quick
and remove it
[Solomon?]
Like shabu shabu
[j-hope's full of energy]
What can I do for you? This?
You're good
[Mixing the kimchi paste into the cabbage]
Pour the whole thing
Should I start from the inside
or the outside?
- Teacher!
- Yes?
Could you teach us
how to spread the paste?
[A very rare scene of V teaching cooking]
You should spread it on every leaf
[Following what he's seen as a kid]
Then it gets easier
Simple and quick
I've seen this a lot
♪ Bam bam, spread it ♪
This can be a good exercise
[1, 2, 1, 2] [Making a fuss]
- It's so heavy
- My eyes are burning
[My eyes are burning]
[Focusing on their own task]
[j-hope was chopping
the radish on the floor]
Making kimchi is so much work
Our kimchi paste was already made
Otherwise, that's a lot of work too
[So tired]
Oh, my
[Jimin sniffs something out of curiosity]
What kind of sauce is that? Anchovy sauce?
Argh!
[Try this, SUGA]
[Always share something nice]
It's not bad
[Jimin lets the other members smell it]
You're strong
[Smell it, j-hope]
[So calm]
Impressive
[The teacher is demonstrating]
- She'll show us
- This is too big
- Oh
- We should fold it in half?
[Oh, I see]
Fold it in half
[She shows how to make kimchi!]
[They were doing it wrong]
- We should redo this
- Yes, let's do that
- And take one leaf
- All right
[Like an owner at a traditional market]
Wrap it around and taste it right away
[Nom]
[Is it good?]
- How is it?
- It's incredible
[Pleased]
Does it taste good?
[Awesome!] [So good]
It's incredible
What do I do with this? It's ruined
[King of destruction]
I'm sorry, I destroyed one
[Jimin wants SUGA's approval]
What do you think? Did I do a good job?
Is that carrot kimchi?
No, I will spread this paste
on the perilla leaves
[Satisfied]
It looks pretty
Open your mouth
I washed my hands, ma'am
[Jimin came to ask the teacher to check]
Could you taste these carrots?
- I washed my hands
- It's a little off
- It's a little off?
- I know
The red pepper powder
taste is missing, right?
[Firm]
- No, the fish sauce is missing
- Taste this
This kimchi tastes incredible
Let me have a bite!
[Sweet Jin cares about the staff]
Our director should taste this
Where is he...
[Confused]
[Handsome Jin even when feeding the staff]
It would go really well with suyuk
[No, no]
- It's a little salty, right?
- Because it should be served with rice
[Huh?]
The food is a little salty
in Gyeongsang Province
[V, you're making Gyeonggi kimchi]
This is Gyeonggi Province
V, when you said Gyeongsang Province,
the teacher was like,
"That's Gyeonggi Province style"
[The teacher drops something...]
- Oh no!
- Something is dropped!
- What did she drop...
- The sticky rice paste!
1, 2, 3
[Wow]
We have a pancake
- Pass me some water, please
- My gloves got a hole
- Can I get another pair?
- How can you get a hole in the gloves?
I cut the finger part with the knife
I'm sorry
[He didn't know it had a hole]
It got all over my finger
Let's think about the efforts of those
who made kimchi for us
- Let's do that
- My mom and my grandmother
[Gimjang lets them reflect on their family]
- And grandpa
- ♪ Mommy ♪
[Jimin looks confident]
I'm done
I think this is good enough
[Model student Jimin always asks questions]
- Every two or three leaves
- Spread the paste here
- And place it again
- There you go, put more leaves
[Huh!]
[Jin got the kimchi paste on his cheek]
[Flustered]
- It's me?
- You look good, Jin
[He lets it slide]
- Beauty mark?
- Yes
[Jin continues mixing the paste
with the beauty mark on his face]
[The kkakdugi team's suyuk]
It's awesome
Don't we need to poke it
with a chopstick?
You should
- Should I?
- Yes
- What happens? Would it flop around?
- I'll poke your heart!
[Amazed]
j-hope is a pro entertainer
I really respect you
I think you'll make
a great home-shopping host
[Run BTS Home Shopping] [Today only]
[j-hope's soul into the radish!]
I put my heart
[The 4th piece of heart radish]
into this 4th piece of radish
[Along with j-hope's natural paste!]
[Call us] [Limited offer! Almost sold out!]
[If you want to buy the radish which j-hope
put his heart into, call 070-1994-0218]
[SUGA tastes for seasoning]
Is this sugar?
[Pouring sugar]
[Flustered]
Based on my experience,
I think I need to put lots of sugar
[Would it taste good?]
That will make it taste good
You're doing it so neatly
[Jimin's neat perilla leaf kimchi]
[Kimchi making makes them]
How do moms do all this?
[appreciate their parents' hard work]
Let's listen to "MAMA" together
- My head, shoulders, knees, feet, back
- I'm done
[SUGA finished his burdock kimchi]
- My first and second vertebra are sore
- I'm done
[SUGA's burdock kimchi looks good]
Wow
Good job
Look
When the container is almost full,
[Hidden talent V is teaching them]
cover the top with unseasoned leaves
[Can't believe it]
V is teaching?
- Now follow me
- If possible
[The other members are amused]
- He said to follow him
- Until when will you do that?
When it's done, we should mark it like this
Did you open a restaurant?
It was really hard
It looks like art
Give it a name, V
Wild camomile
Oh, that's romantic
[Feeling happy by the compliments]
[SUGA is kicking back]
It's amazing
Are you done?
[Jimin is almost done]
It's good
You want to try?
[A rocker here]
[Whining]
- V, taste my perilla leaf kimchi
- No, thanks
[95z argument begins again]
- It's good, I just tasted it
- No!
[It's good]
Is it edible?
Let me have a bite
[Pouting]
Seriously
How can you react like that?
[Awesome]
- It seems like they're running a business
- Let's sell this
[Strong accent]
It's just 2000 won
Oh my, there are so many people
[They look like they're running a business]
- We can name it Youth Kimchi
- I need sugar
- Sugar!
- Come in, SUGA!
In you go, SUGA!
[Sweet already...!]
I told you it's good! Yeah!
Let me cut it
[Shrug]
[Seems like he's sold kimchi for a decade]
Oh, are you here to film me?
I'm honored
[Spread]
It's quite good
Would you like to taste it?
[Jimin works hard, SUGA roams around]
It's really good
You can't believe me
[My precious kkakdugi] [Quick]
- j-hope!
- Hey, hey! 3-second rule!
We should eat this
You applied the 3-second rule
to kkakdugi?
[Global stars BTS]
- Indeed
- We're BTS
BTS is really something
since we're going worldwide
Jung Kook's arms...
[Mixing the radish,
Jung Kook's eye-catching arms]
[The cabbage kimchi team
now makes geotjeori]
Geotjeori
[The teacher cuts scallions with scissors]
Cut scallions
[That's an easy trick]
- Mix it together?
- Wow
- Oh!
- Together! Right
[It's my type of thing]
Wow! This is good
- It's good, I tasted it
- Jung Kook!
[We're filming]
Stop showing your back
[Jung Kook listens to SUGA]
It looks good
You've been in this
industry for over four years
It looks good
[Jin takes care of the staff]
This is how you should eat kimchi
[Curious]
- You don't look good
- Why? Is it too salty?
[Jin is copying the facial expression]
After tasting it...
I think it's a little too salty
[Helping Jimin]
This should speed things up
What are you doing? You should spread it
Not like this
[Spreading perilla leaves]
This is why I didn't do it this way
It was a hard day today
He put just three leaves and
said, "It was a hard day"
[V feeds the teacher]
[j-hope is still looking for
his heart radish]
My heart radishes are gone
That's crushed already
[Here it is]
It's here!
I'm done
[Jimin's perilla leaf kimchi]
[Jimin shares tips on how to eat it]
Wrap it around rice and have a mouthful
[Proud]
[Looks good, right?]
It's getting more water,
feeling like it's mixing well
[Working hard]
It's so rewarding
[Confused]
How do I open this?
- What is this thing?
- I can't open it
[Complaint 1]
Why is this stuck?
[Complaint 2]
Why did you glue this glove?
[Turns out there's something wrong
with those gloves]
[Crazy skill]
- Jung Kook, you're almost like...
- A machine
[Jung Kook's amazing kimchi-making skills]
[Question]
Teacher, why is this glove stuck together?
[Frustrated]
I'm stuck here!
[I can't open this glove]
I'm doing this all by myself!
[It's not fair] [You picked your own team]
Why are they on my team?
[So tired]
It's done
[Blank]
That should do it
- Okay, let's rinse them with cold water
- Should I put them here?
No, we should do more
[Jung Kook stepped on the rice paste]
- My feet!
- Jung Kook stepped on it
He stepped on the teacher's jeon
- Show us your acting, V
- Yeah, do it, V
- What should I do?
- You broke up, and you're tearing up
You're tearing up
not because you're sad about the breakup
- You're crying because kimchi is spicy
- There you go
[Amazing cook]
[Kim Seokjin, playing the father]
[Attractive dimples]
[Kim Namjoon, playing the oldest son]
[Impossible not to love this guy]
[Kim Taehyung, playing the youngest son]
[Action!]
1, 2, 3, cue!
[Run BTS mini series]
[Cabbage Kimchi Family's Gimjang]
[RM and Jin and V, TAKE 1]
- My son, isn't this kimchi good?
- It's good
[Flustered]
My little son...
[My eyes are burning]
[Sobbing]
Why are you sniffing, son?
[Weeping]
[It's hilarious]
[Crying]
Be careful
[Not sure what it was, but - THE END -]
You did great
Kimchi is really spicy
[Kkakdugi kimchi]
Ma'am, it's dead
It's wilted
[Making a fuss to act improv]
- Are you sure it's dead?
- Is it not breathing?
It's not breathing?
- It's dead
- Did the heart stop?
[The bigger radish is still stiff]
The smaller ones are soft
It's no good when it's too hard
[Sit back and order what to do]
You should work on it, Jung Kook
[SUGA is having fun teasing Jung Kook]
[So fun!]
The sons are making kimchi
[Seems like the parents and sons]
We're mom and dad
[Working hard]
Looks like it's still stiff
It's taking long
It can't fit this in
- I told you already! It can't fit
- Seriously
- Then what do we do now?
- Press it down
[Pressing]
No, I can't press the air out of it
[Press hard]
Jin!
You're supposed to do this
[Good job]
I yelled because you're doing great
[V complimented Jin by yelling]
He yelled because he's doing great
Jung Kook, let's take some out
[Come on, SUGA]
SUGA is giving a hand
Don't show your back!
[Defending himself]
There's a camera from this angle
You're blocking Jung Kook's arms
[Right]
Yeah, his arms are the key here
[SUGA gives in]
[Jung Kook's arms are the key] [Yeah]
I'm nothing
[EatJin teaches how to
sprinkle sesame seeds]
You should sprinkle on the hand first
[I want to do that]
- Why?
- You don't want to pour a whole bunch
[V grabbed it with his glove on]
You weren't supposed to grab it
[Oh... the sauce is all over it]
You weren't supposed to grab the bottle
[I got it]
You're the second RM
How long is it going to take
to make geotjeori?
- It's taking forever
- How do we decorate now?
[Jin looks at RM's plating]
[Show us... Let's laugh together]
Our concept is putting everything
on this plate
- Okay?
- Yes
[Teasing]
You're the one to blame
[The plate looks too small]
- There's an empty plate
- It's okay, let's do this
My back hurts!
[The kkakdugi team is draining water]
Stay still
Let's drain water
[They look cute to SUGA]
[Kimchi tower]
Let's invite all the neighbors
and throw a party
[V's plating is done]
My decoration is finished
[Here? There?]
Which camera is filming me?
[Showing it to the camera
with his cute smile]
Mix it! Mix it! Jung Kook!
Mix!
[Jung Kook's arms are in operation!]
He's like a machine
[Looking sweetly at Jung Kook]
[Jung Kook's arms are like a machine]
It's almost like a robot
[RM is struggling to close the lid]
It's strange
Why isn't it closing?
[Nervous]
It's just you're not doing it right
[Punch]
Don't punch!
[Jin is nervous]
I got this
- I got it
- Really?
If you're not working,
slice the suyuk, please
[Well-cooked to the inside]
Wow, suyuk!
[Requests]
Please slice it into thick pieces
Do you know why it's yellow?
Because we added turmeric powder
[Yellow meat due to turmeric powder]
To get rid of the gamey smell
[Question]
Why didn't you use all this?
[Making an excuse]
- You should use them all
- I just followed the recipe
Just do it
We used all of ours too
[V found gonggi stones]
Why are gonggi stones here?
[Dropping gonggi stones]
Hang on
The perilla leaf team is
trying to get rid of the evidence
[Jimin, there's too much left]
Seriously!
Jimin came over to me and said,
"What do I do with all this?"
[What just happened]
There's a lot leftover here
Don't you think you have to use all that?
[Acting]
Huh? Where's the paste?
[Acting like he's sad]
The paste is gone
I can't serve this to our members!
It's unhygienic
If the teacher approves
that your kimchi is good,
- If she approves?
- Then we'll clean it up
Teacher, please come over here
[j-hope and Jung Kook work really hard]
Our kimchi should be really good
[Working hard]
Hard work never goes in vain
Cooking is all about hard work
[Nervous]
[How's perilla leaf kimchi?]
[She approves]
Please give a thumbs up
[Smile with his eyes]
I'll clean up really well
[How's SUGA's burdock kimchi?]
It's good
[Confident]
I made 1 kg, according to the recipe
[Jung Kook tastes the kkakdugi he made]
[Excited]
How do you like it?
[His mouth moves like a robot]
It's too fresh, of course
You should let it sit to ferment
I really like the paste
[Looking at the teacher]
- It should be good if it's fermented
- I believe so
[Hope's heart radish]
Heart! There's the heart radish
Let's put it in the container now
[Kkakdugi team rocks]
Great job, you two
[The kkakdugi looks beautiful]
- Look at the color
- It's perfect
[We should take a picture!]
I should take a picture
I'm totally satisfied
Shouldn't it be stored in the
kimchi refrigerator? Pop, pop, pop, pop
[Kimchi and suyuk
the members made sincerely]
[Juicy suyuk and kkakdugi]
[Three Kim Brothers' cabbage kimchi]
[Perilla leaf kimchi with craftsmanship]
[Uncommon but delicious burdock kimchi]
[BTS done with their gimjang]
We did it!
[Proud]
We put our blood, sweat, and tears into it
- I realized how hard it is to make kimchi
- I agree
My mother has never bought kimchi so far
[Kimchi pixie]
I thought I should buy some for her
I've made kimchi with my mom
for like five years when I was a kid
It was different from back then
[Speechless]
Back then...
[It's awesome]
Kkakdugi turned out awesome
[Lots of compliments]
Jung Kook mixed it really well
It looks like kimchi
in a seolleongtang restaurant
[Proud]
Let it sit for a week
[All the kimchi dishes look great]
- Geotjeori is good
- It's really great
Suyuk is also good
Hang on, guys!
[RM, Jin, and V's geotjeori]
This one
[and cabbage kimchi filled two containers]
and this one is made by one team
- These are made by one team
- No
[j-hope and Jung Kook, 2 containers of
kkakdugi and suyuk]
We made suyuk too
[SUGA and Jimin's smaller amount of kimchi]
And these are made by one team
- You should taste it, you'll love it
- It's a little small
[SUGA and Jimin explain]
It's supposed to be that small
[Hmm... I see...]
It's not a competition
but since you guys made it
- Yes
- let's choose which one tastes best
Sure
[The teacher will evaluate the kimchi]
- The teacher will decide
- Teacher!
She watched the whole process
- If she eats all this...
- She needs a lot of water
[SUGA and Jin are worried]
I think she'll need to drink a lot of water
Let's step back for her
[j-hope is adding comments for the teacher]
We made the suyuk, ma'am
[She tastes geotjeori made by RM, Jin, V]
Starting with geotjeori
Geotjeori tastes good
[Nod]
I think she likes it
[Moving on to kkakdugi!]
- Kkakdugi
- Try smaller pieces
[Obsessed with heart pieces]
Is there a heart radish?
[Thinking hard]
She's not nodding this time
[Killer smile]
[It should be good once it's fermented]
- Kkakdugi should be fermented
- We should let it sit
It was my first time making
and tasting burdock kimchi
[Worried]
I'm not sure if it tastes right
[All eyes are on her]
- It's good
- The sesame seed taste?
[Next is perilla leaf kimchi!]
Time to taste perilla leaf kimchi
[Shrug]
Who made it?
- You did a great job
- Oh
[Strong reaction] [Thank you]
- Oh, that's...
- She's so kind-hearted
Which one would you choose
as the best kimchi?
You guys did a great job
as global stars
[Awesome]
Your speech is excellent
You put so much effort into it,
so it's hard to pick one
[Selection criteria]
But the kimchi that you
worked hard on the most
[The members seem nervous]
[She chose kkakdugi] [It's us! Yipee!]
Kkakdugi!
I chose it based on your efforts
[Jin is tries the kkakdugi]
[Kkakdugi made him crack up]
[Curious]
What does that mean? I need an interpreter
[EatJin's review]
It tastes like radish
dipped in the kimchi paste
Let me taste kkakdugi
[The leader's advice]
Don't open your mouth too big
Let's give it up for the teacher
[Thank you, teacher]
Thank you
[Thank you]
[Getting aggressive in front of food]
Let's dig in
We made them, after all
[It's good]
To be honest, I've been tasting it
Suyuk is cooked beautifully
[Mouthful]
It's good
[Nom nom]
Jin made this geotjeori
almost all by yourself, right?
[Shaking his head]
[Jin... You look like an alpaca]
[Mumbling]
No, we did our best too
[I worked hard too!]
[First time trying burdock kimchi]
- I like burdock kimchi
- I wanted to try
It all tastes like kimchi
made by professionals
Let's do some special episode of Run BTS at
a gukbap restaurant with kkakdugi
No, I object to the gukbap restaurant idea
- No
- Then we have to make gukbap
[Serious] [You know how things go]
They can make us get a pig
Too bad we can't taste the kkakdugi now
If you're watching this overseas,
you might think,
"Kimchi requires so much work"
[Proud of it]
- It's Korea's signature dish
- Right
[Moving to the side]
It takes some time for a man to be mature
The same goes for kimchi
[Leader RM's amazing speech]
- Nice
- We worked hard to make this kimchi
I hope you can taste it with your eyes
Run BTS continues
Bye!
- Run BTS, gimjang episode
- We should make a dish with this
[Please look forward to the dishes they'll
make with the kimchi they made today]
[Run BTS
- Kimchi Battle -]