[Run BTS - Kimchi Battle]
Run BTS!
[Familiar place]
- We've been here once, right?
- Right
This is where V's epic work
"Squirrel trapped in the garden" was made
[Funny already]
- Jung Kook...
- I only remember flipping it
Bingo sweet potatoes
[Right, that one]
[Why the cooking studio again?]
What are we here for with kimchi?
Today's Run BTS topic is
cooking using the kimchi
you made yourself last time
[Today's Run BTS!]
[]
[Make a dish with the kimchi
they made last time]
[SUGA and Jimin each picks the team
between cabbage kimchi vs. kkakdugi]
[Each team makes two dishes]
[Based on the production staff's votes,
the losing team should clean up!]
SUGA and Jimin will pick the team
through a draw
Give me anything
Your fates will be...!
I want to pick the kkakdugi team
Then you will pick the other team
[Bingo]
Jimin wanted to pick the kkakdugi team
and he did
[The dance line happens to be
on the same team]
The dance line!
[Going crazy]
We are the vocal line
[Somber]
[And he takes it]
[RM's better off as a rapper]
That didn't work
Team Cabbage Kimchi should make
- kimchi japchae
- Kimchi japchae?
and tonkatsu kimchi hot pot
- Tonkatsu kimchi hot pot
- Sounds really yummy
I have never heard of that dish
- But they have that
- I know that
[I don't know]
There's a dish called
tonkatsu kimchi hot pot
Team Kkakdugi should make
[The first dish]
- kkakdugi fried rice
- That's what I was thinking
[His gut instinct was right]
This is why I came on this team
[Second dish]
And kkakdugi pork jjigae
Kkakdugi pork jjigae?
I've never heard of that
I'm learning a lot of new dishes
[Time to taste the kimchi they made!]
Why don't you taste the kimchi
[The staff couldn't ripen kimchi enough]
before you start cooking?
Let's try
[How would it taste?]
It's still very fresh
[Nom nom]
I tasted it.
I think it'll be good once it's fermented
[Jung Kook... This is it!]
Try smaller pieces
Bigger ones didn't ripen
- What do you think?
- It still needs to be fermented
But perfect with rice
I'm satisfied
Burdock kimchi is quite fermented
I like burdock kimchi
I love this fresh kkakdugi so much
It'd be perfect with seolleongtang
[Gulp]
I want to eat sundae gukbap
[Jimin is eating well]
Kimchi
- Is it fermented?
- How is it?
He's quiet
[Crack up]
I don't think he likes it
[Jimin carefully talks]
It has that overpowering taste
- You put that, didn't you?
- What?
- What's it other than garlic?
- Ginger?
- Really?
- You should try
It turns out it's ginger kimchi
[Yum]
It almost got on your nose
I'm sorry
[Doubtful]
Do you think you can cook with it?
Everyone is speechless after tasting it
[EatJin's review]
The problem with the kimchi is
it's too fresh
[It'd taste good if it ferments more]
It needs to be fermented
[Objective]
The ingredients aren't blended together
- We will have to cook anyway
- Right
I'd like to apologize to the judges first
That will be your lunch
[Come on]
Don't do this to us
[Motivated!]
Let's make it really tasty
[So excited]
I skipped my breakfast for this
[V]
- Good job
- That means
your lunch is on the line
- No!
- Work hard
All right!
[Okay, got it]
Okay
Shall we begin?
We will make a dish
with the kimchi we made
Kimchi Battle
2018, the epic battle begins
Kkakdugi vs. Napa cabbage kimchi
- The war begins
- Let's go!
BTS!
[The kimchi BTS worked hard on]
[The ingredients for kimchi dishes
are all set]
Run BTS!
- We have all the ingredients ready
- Let's get started
Safety first, safety second
Taste third
Let's start cooking
with our own ingredients
- Let's go!
- Is there a time limit?
Is there a time limit?
Should we ring the bell? Ding!
We'll give you an hour
- One hour?
- One hour
[SUGA asks for scissors]
V, please get me a pair of scissors
Scissors
Cut the green onions diagonally
[Looking for scissors]
Chop the onion into cubes, okay?
I don't know how to cut diagonally
- To cut diagonally
- Diagonally
- Excuse me
Slanted
Sideways
[I ended up laughing at j-hope's joke]
Maybe I shouldn't have laughed
That was funny
[Delivering the scissors he found]
Get the cutting board ready
[Focused]
[Looking for the sound of gas stove...]
- Oh, chef Jin
- I'm awesome
- Don't you need to ring the bell?
- I nailed it
[Jung Kook quietly cuts sausages]
[That's new]
[Line up technique]
[Jin, home cooking master
and V, his favorite student]
Meat seasoning 101
Gan-seol-pa-ma-cham-kkae-hu
[Respect!]
Soy sauce, sugar, green onions,
garlic, sesame seeds...
[Cooking 101! Gan-seol-pa-ma-cham-kkae-hu]
- Cool
- Gan-seol-pa-ma
Sesame seeds, pepper
Cham-kkae-hu
- Cham-kkae-hu?
- Yes
[Chef SUGA cuts them off]
We need to put in more frying mix
You should make the deep fry batter
[Me?!]
Deep fry batter
[Team Cabbage Kimchi divides up the work]
- With eggs and flour
- Deep fry batter?
You can do it
I should drain it?
[No! That's not how you do it! (urgent)]
[Not sure]
[Don't forget... You should eat it...]
So how can I cut diagonally?
[Like this]
Cut it in this direction
[Help me...]
Do you know how to make deep fry batter?
[Passing the buck]
Search that on the Internet
[He's smart]
Internet can teach you everything
[Put the whole thing in!]
Cut up all of the meat
- I'll put in all of this
- We'll eat it anyway
- If it's too much for the pot...
- No, no
[Divided opinions over pork]
- Isn't it too much?
- Trust Chef Hope
I think it's way too much pork
Cut it down!
[Just trust me!]
[Figuring out how to make deep fry batter]
How to make deep fry batter
- What is this, Jin?
- I think that's frying mix
[j-hope looks like a pro]
Check if it's heated up
Oh no, I almost poured oligosaccharide
Pour oligosaccharide?
[Arguing]
- Why did you give me that?
- Sorry
What kind of deep fry is it?
[V has to make the tonkatsu batter]
- Tonkatsu
Is this the right size for sausage?
[He's pretty good]
- For fried rice? I think that's good
- Oh, no
[Keep asking]
Isn't this too big?
No?
Flour, eggs, breadcrumbs
[Sesame seeds party]
[Oh... I gained nutty taste
but lost the dish...]
[Another problem]
I made a mistake
I should have added oil first
You told me to trust you
[Jin got in trouble]
I ruined it
[Calm down...]
What? You ruined it already?
[I can take them out]
You shouldn't have ruined it already
How much sesame seeds did you put in?
[Jin is sad!]
It got poured in!
Are you making beef tartare, Jin?
[Making it up by putting more kkakdugi]
In they go!
I'm choosing smaller pieces
Mix sugar, sesame oil, and sesame seeds
[Anxious]
Jin, do you think I can mix this?
Can I mix anything at all?
Minced garlic
Get me minced garlic
And you, cut diagonally
Get minced garlic ready
Where is it?
[Help me]
I should chop green onions
[Jung Kook is speaking
in an accent, out of panic]
I should make green onion oil
I don't understand
Shall we make it at home?
If you cook
[No problem]
I will cook for you
If it's good today
[Master cook's class on how to beat eggs]
I'll teach you how to beat eggs
[1. Tap an egg making a nice sound]
Good, crack it with this nice sound
[2. Smoothly drop it into the bowl]
And like this!
[The eggshell got into the bowl...
Class dismissed!]
[Exchanging opinions]
Isn't this 5 cm?
That's roughly 10 cm, Jin
[RM and Jin are arguing]
It's not nearly 10 cm
It's 5
- Isn't this 10 cm?
- This is 1 cm
[Glance]
[Admit]
- You're right
- I know
[This duo is going to be fun to watch...]
[Slurp]
[The soup is amazing] [Wide-eyed]
Hey! It's good
It's incredible
[We should sell it, Jimin]
We should sell it
Let's sell it
[Speechless because of the delicious taste]
[This is amazing!]
Should we open a restaurant?
- j-hope
- Kkakdugi
[I was meant to be on this team]
There's a reason why I came on this team
[I had a dream]
I dreamt about kkakdugi last night
[I dreamt of kkakdugi, it was good]
- Last night?
- We should use kkakdugi
This onion is peeled, right?
[Quietly grabs the onion]
[Jin teaches how to slice an onion]
Slice it like this
[Got it!]
Like that?
[SUGA teaches how to
coat it with the batter]
You see? Like this
[Working hard] [In charge of deep-frying]
You can coat it again and make it thick
We might eat it all up
before we finish making
[Addictive taste]
It's really good
What do we do?
[Savor the flavor]
[This is amazing]
[j-hope informs them of
the success of kkakdugi pork jjigae]
Don't worry about lunch, guys
- Are you done?
- Lunch is ready
Jung Kook, our kkakdugi is really good
By the way, j-hope
- What?
- I have to make the sauce
[Go, Jimin!]
- Help him with the sauce
- What?
[I got this!]
I just have to put things in now
Help him with the sauce
[Jimin's briefing]
- This is sugar
- Okay
This is anchovy
You can use this spoon
[Jimin is worried about j-hope]
- Put the whole thing in
- I shouldn't
[He cut the kimchi in advance]
I chopped it up already
[Moved] [How thoughtful]
Should I cut more of this?
Cut it and add it at the end
That should do it
[Don't you smell something cool?]
- I'll work on the sauce now
- Jimin
I got this, you know?
[SUGA tastes the hot pot]
[Savoring the taste]
[Huh?]
Huh?
[Flustered]
It tastes like Japanese food
How?
[Soy sauce + ginger = Japanese taste?]
I added soy sauce and ginger
and it tastes like Japan
[Doubt]
For real? The Japanese seasoning?
[j-hope comes over]
- It's Japanese style
- Let me try
I put a lot of sugar and ginger,
and it tastes like Japanese food
[No way...]
- Try it
- Japanese soup
[I know this taste]
Right? Right?
It's true
It's the taste of Japan
[It tastes like Japanese food?]
- Yes, it's Japanese
- Japan, the taste of Japan
- The taste of Japan.
- Tokyo!
[SUGA's magical broth]
- It's Shibuya
[How interesting]
It's Tokyo
[SUGA and V try to make coating thicker]
Coat it again
Dip it in the egg mixture
- Dip into the egg again
- Like this?
Yes
Dip into the mixture
Where's dark soy sauce?
- Jin soy sauce
- Jin is here
[Reject]
- I don't need Jin
- You don't need Jin? I'm hurt
[Interesting]
What's that cutting technique, RM?
- This? RM's technique
- Hey!
[What?]
I didn't tell you to dice it
[Disaster]
[Thumbs up]
That is RM's cutting technique
I still have half an onion
[Oh my]
I will cut this half well
Leave that and slice it again
[V made the coat thicker]
- This is thicker
- Make one more, please
Hey, it's so puffed up
You told me to make it thicker
[SUGA is flustered by the thickness]
- This one's the thick one?
- Yes, thick
[Sorry]
- This is thin
- Let's use the thin one
[Setting aside]
Let's grill it later
I'm saying this every time I cook
I pay my deep respects
to all the chefs out there
Those who work in the restaurant industry,
I really appreciate it
[SUGA is about to deep-fry tonkatsu]
- Deep-fry tonkatsu?
- Yes
Is SUGA the master of tonkatsu?
- Sukatsu, Sukatsu
- V loves tonkatsu
- Jimin likes tonkatsu, right?
- I love it, please make it well
I'll put the whole thing in
[V is choosing a plate]
[Pondering, V is carefully checking plates]
[Seems like he's on the
"Authentic Masterpiece" show]
[Don't need to sing this well]
[Kkakdugi fried rice
along with sweet voice]
Try this, RM
Is it cooked?
[What...?]
I haven't even tried it yet
It's rubber!
[The portion is getting bigger]
I'm making a lot
Wow
That's tonkatsu
[Curious]
Was that raw pork?
It was a little seasoned
[V hasn't chosen plates]
- Should I use this dish?
- Looks good
Is it a little off?
- This one is more Japan-like
- I know, right?
Should we name our dish "Gonichiwa"?
I like that
Gonichiwa
[Jin is rinsing noodles in cold water]
- RM
- Yes
Help!
I'll drain it, please hold the noodles
Argh!
- It's not hot, I poured cold water
- Hot!
[It's hot!]
Is it hot? Use a spoon and chopsticks
Chop chop!
It's heavy and hot
Hang on
Out of the way! Out of the way!
[It was really hot, huh?] [Embarrassed]
Hot!
Tonkatsu is looking great
- I'll make more later
- Can you make more tonkatsu for me?
[I made a lot]
- We got more here
- I'll make more after this
- I think we lost because of tonkatsu
- Why?
[Smacking lips]
- Tonkatsu looks so good
- No
Isn't it just because you like tonkatsu?
[Can't help but love this]
[Worried]
The only variable is the kimchi
I'm not sure how it would change the taste
[RM urgently looks for soy sauce]
Soy sauce! Soy sauce!
Soy sauce is over there
[Where?]
[Right here]
[#Silent scream] [(Staff)That's fish sauce]
[Shocked]
Fish sauce! Fish sauce!
Where's soy sauce?
[Freaking out thinking he used fish sauce]
Did I put fish sauce instead of soy sauce?
[Sniff]
- It's fish sauce
- Soy sauce
Was it soy sauce?
[RM is surprised by a large amount]
Didn't you put too much?
[Can't hear you] [#Soy sauce makes it work]
Mix it
Mix it, mix it
This plating for japchae would be
too challenging, right?
[Flustered]
That's not japchae
It's something else
- It's Vietnamese spring rolls
- Vietnamese spring rolls
[Bluffing]
You know this, SUGA?
[Coaching]
Your salt should touch here
[So happy]
I'll make a dish with the leftover sausage
[Stir]
[Odeng is Jin's sugar glider]
Doesn't it sound like Odeng's barking?
Exactly!
[Interesting]
Isn't it like Odeng's barking sound?
[Nom]
Did you taste it? Is it good?
How is it?
I put too much pepper
[Worried]
Too much pepper can ruin the dish
- I put too much pepper
- Huh? Pick it out!
[No one knows how to pick out pepper...]
But how?
[Tonkatsu kimchi hot pot
looks great already]
SUGA
[I love tonkatsu]
That looks so good
- Oh my, what do I do?
- Is it not cooked yet?
- I mean, it'll be unbelievable
- Our kkakdugi stew will be amazing
[Hmm...]
[Something is missing...]
[I know the answer
Salt!]
[Making egg garnish]
There's too much oil
[Oh no, my egg garnish]
It's ruined perfectly
Where's the microwave?
[V is looking for the microwave
to cook instant rice]
[Looks around]
This is not a microwave, is it?
V is trying to heat up
the instant rice in the oven
- That should work
- He said it's okay to use the oven
[Confidently going to the oven]
- I told you
- Heat it up in the oven
[Still not sure]
- It's all right, right?
- I don't know, give it a go
[Glance]
The writers look worried
[Precious V shouldn't get hurt]
No?
It does taste like Japanese food
Man!
[You should just enjoy it!]
[Team Kkakdugi gathered around
the fried rice]
I think it's okay
[Mouthful]
- The pepper is overpowering, though
- We should balance it out with cheese
- Isn't it good?
- It's good
- The kkakdugi is still fresh
- We shouldn't put too much cheese
[How will the fried rice turn out?]
It'd be better without cheese
It might be better without cheese
[Crispy tonkatsu]
Hear the sound
The sound is amazing
[Still struggling with egg garnish]
[Deep sigh]
[Jin throws away the ruined part]
It's not egg garnish
More like a fried egg
28 minutes to go
[Confident]
- So much time left
- We have much time left
[RM tastes the egg garnish]
Are you done, RM?
We just need 10 more minutes
- It's good
- What did you eat?
[Egg garnish]
A fried egg
- It looks delicious
- Should we cut it differently?
[All these guys think about is ARMY]
- ARMY
- Should I try that?
[j-hope is carving a heart]
Wouldn't it be strange after it's cooked?
[Looks delicious]
The knife cuts are spreading apart
Let me check how you're doing
Can I have a bite, Jung Kook?
[Close friends who share their food]
[Mmm] [Awesome]
[Great job]
[A satisfied smile?]
[The heart sausage is beautifully cooked]
[Showing off]
Look at this, Jin
Heart!
[Big smile]
Can I eat that?
[Showing off his heart sausage]
Heart
[Heart on sausage]
My father told me I should
keep my hands busy when making fried rice
I should keep my hands busy?
[Like this]
I should keep stirring
[Unbelievable salted squid fried rice]
My dad's fried rice is so...
I loved his salted squid fried rice
[The heart sausage goes to V]
You're the winner
[Yay! Excited]
It's almost half meat, half noodles
[50:50]
The meat and noodles
are the same in portion
[Time to check Jimin's dish]
- Jimin
- Yes
- Let me check how you're doing
- Yup
[Hehe] [Hang on]
Hey, by the way,
[Meaning: I want ketchup]
- doesn't tonkatsu go along with ketchup?
- Yes
That would work
[How would the tonkatsu with ketchup
taste like?] [Good!]
As we've cooked before
we feel more comfortable
- It's good.
- I know, right?
[Even thinking about making another dish]
Should I make the same sauce
and stir-fry the pork?
[Excited]
Sounds delicious
[SUGA starts making another dish as well!]
I'm done already
I'll make another one
[He finished his side dish]
That's really cool, j-hope
[Juicy]
This team is making spectacular dishes
I'm good at cooking
[V is excited after having bacon]
I've always been good at doing the dishes
You might lose this time, RM
[Stealing the spotlight]
It's all right, RM
We're going to win
[j-hope urgently works out a strategy]
Let's make extra dishes
[Already working on it]
- To stand out
- Already working on it
[Satisfied]
You're doing great
[SUGA making a skewer for kimchi hot pot]
It's good
[Things are going smoothly with japchae?]
It's working out as planned
[Not really...]
[Ridiculous]
How did you stir-fry this?
You did just this, right?
[Right on]
[A big smile out of embarrassment]
[Tell us] [We don't know either]
I don't know what I'm making
How many minutes to go?
[11 minutes to go]
11 minutes! I should boil it
[Blow]
Should we cool it down? It might be too hot
It will cool down in 11 minutes anyway
[Kimchi japchae is smoking hot]
I should mix it
[Be careful]
Let me do it!
- It's really hot
- I got this
[So hot...!]
[Taking turns]
[Why does this remind us of Pat and Mat?]
[Use chopsticks, please]
It's way too hot
10 minutes to go
[Mysterious]
I really don't know what this dish is
[Mysterious dish]
Stir-fried kkakdugi pork
It tastes better than it looks
- Really?
- It goes well with rice
[Tasting japchae with numb fingers]
It's good
[This flavor is?!]
You like it?
- It's like my mom's japchae
- Yeah
[Sudden reality check]
I think we're making too many dishes today
There's a basic plating technique
to present noodle dishes
[Just remember this! Grab!]
- What should we do?
- Grab the noodles
Twirl it
I failed
[After twists and turns,
kimchi japchae is finished]
Kimchi gives a nice kick
I guess that's the
beauty of kimchi japchae
Yeah
This is epic
We should do MIC Drop
[That's a spatula]
I'll hold the spatula instead of a mic
[Careful]
Is there a microwave?
Here?
[Amazed]
I kind of feel guilty about heating up
only one bowl of instant rice
with this
[Kkakdugi fried rice and
cheese kkakdugi fried rice are done]
Nice, two versions
That's cool
Now... hurry up
[Jin is plating with finesse]
Japchae perfects everything
[Impressive visual]
Hey, RM
- Did your hot pot turn out good?
- I can sell this, for real
[He is also singing his own praise]
[Even the plating of kkakdugi
pork jjigae is perfect]
[It seems like he's making a work of art]
[Working hard]
You have 5 minutes to go
I'm done.
SUGA! It's done
[Cracking up]
Jimin! Jimin!
[Look at this]
That's unique
[Unique]
- This is quite new
- It looks like flowers, bacon flowers
[The judge will evaluate only the main]
Guys, it's the main dish that's important
We should make our main dish stand out
It's pointless to make nice extra dishes
[Jung Kook is still cooking]
For various flavors
Something is a little off
[Have no idea]
We can't add anything, though
Let's search the japchae photos
We don't need to place the
egg garnish on top, I guess
- I think our cooking skills have improved
- I know
[Nom nom] [Awesome]
- What is he doing?
The authentic Japanese dish
I focused on cooking seriously today
[Respect]
For real
It should be amazing
[What does SUGA's serious dish look like?]
Awesome!
[Kimchi hot pot looks like
an authentic Japanese dish]
The japchae is absolutely beautiful
- Why did you put it there?
- To make them fresh
[A wild man's table]
To make it look fresh
[Unique plating]
That's the worst plating ever
What did you make? Japchae?
- Yes
- Nicely done
[The members are amazed by kimchi japchae]
Great job
It looks yummy
- We can enjoy all this soon
- Hey!
[Showing off]
SUGA made this, and RM and Jin made this
And I made it
[He has every reason to be proud]
Tonkatsu hot pot looks great
[All done!]
We're done
[The harmony of jjigae and fried rice
(feat. sausage)]
[The harmony of japchae and
tonkatsu kimchi hot pot]
Our managers are foodies
- Right
- They know all the good restaurants
[Let's introduce the judges, our managers]
They are in charge of our group
Our two managers
Please feel free to eat up
You should remember that it's a hot pot
It's not kimchi jjigae
[Appealing even before swallowing]
The key to our dish is the soup
The fried rice might be salty
He's so our manager
He always wears that BTS staff jacket
- He's known as a cold guy
- Cold?
I asked him if I could sleep one minute
and he said absolutely not
[Of course] [That's right]
He's right
He will evaluate it fairly
That's a Japanese hot pot dish
[Nodding?]
- You're so into that dish
- It's a Japanese hot pot dish
[Appealing] [Manager, my love]
- Let's see!
[Team Cabbage Kimchi vs. Team Kkakdugi]
It's Team Cabbage Kimchi
versus Team Kkakdugi
I'm curious whether they will make
the same choice
I saw it
They chose the same dish
Did they choose the same dish?
[No]
- No?
- He said no
- Why would you make a moss?
- No?
[Where's the moss?]
- Make a fuss
- You mean, make a fuss
[That was funny]
"Make a moss"
[Summary]
It's the combination of
"my gosh" and "fuss"
[Audio director and camera director's turn]
- Audio director
- Our audio director
He has great senses
- His five senses are amazing
- Right
[Static sound, can you hear me?]
I love you, director
Can you hear me? Love you
[No need for words]
[Good]
He nodded
[Nod]
[Applause]
[Jumping to a conclusion]
Thank you, sir
[Acting cute]
Our Solomon!
He's the top commander
[Having high hopes for the director]
- He directed "Bon Voyage" as well
- Right
He tasted it and tilted his head
[That's quite ambiguous]
It means, "How can it taste this good"?
- He's having another bite of hot pot
- One more time
See? Japchae from Korea, hot pot from
Japan, and bacon from Italy
It's three nations in one place
[Hang on]
- Does bacon originate from Italy?
- I don't know
- Isn't it America?
- Let's say it is
[Time to announce the result]
What's the result?
[Excited]
- 4 to 1
- 4 to 1?
Team Cabbage Kimchi won
We did it!
[Whatever]
We lost again
- Is it sweet?
- I really like it
[The winner of Kimchi Battle]
It's the hot pot
[So excited]
- It became sweet
- It's simmered for too long
It tastes like the restaurant
in Yeonnam-dong
[That's so specific]
- Yeonnam-dong
- There's a hot pot place
I lost again
[Strong will]
Let's have a cook-off again
[So busy eating it]
I'll do it properly
It's simmered too long
[Regretful]
What should we have added?
Should we have added Cheongyang peppers?
Deep, not deep
In my opinion,
all the directors voted for this team
except one manager
Isn't that too cruel?
[Eating up]
- We should wrap it up
- Let's finish up
[Take your time...]
Stop eating
We should wrap it up
We made kimchi ourselves and had a cook-off
- How was it?
- What I really want to say is
[It's good]
our dish is really good
[It's so good]
We should cook it at home
Our cooking skills are improving
What should we do now?
[Well... Yeah...]
We do everything so well
- Try this, it's not evaluated yet
- Right
[Almost forgot] [Skinny figurine?]
- We should try that
- It's so skinny
Isn't this a figurine?
[Eat up]
It's food
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Suddenly, rock paper scissors?]
The losing team should eat it
[Speaking quickly]
You three can each have one
[Eating an onion?]
Should the loser have a bite of this?
[Suddenly]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Spectators]
- Rock, paper, scissors!
- The one who brings up always lose
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Poor Jimin]
- Everyone
- See? He lost
[The one who made the onion figurine]
You said it, so you lost
I'll try
- Please wrap it up as I eat this
- Let's go!
[Munch!]
The cooking shows by BTS will continue!
- Run!
- BTS!
[Flooded with requests]
Shout out "Run BTS" after eating that
Run BTS!
[Here you go]
Whistle
[Satisfied]
- Good job
[Carrying out the penalty]
[Team Kkakdugi cleans up]
We should collect the food
I will hurry up
Someone should start doing the dishes
Who wants to do it?
[Rock, paper, scissors?]
- Who will do the dishes?
- Who brought it up?
Him? Me?
- You brought it up?
- Yes
- I think you will lose
- Rock, paper, scissors!
- No way
- No way, for real?
[Here it comes] [Paper]
- This is destiny
- Rock, paper, scissors!
[Rock]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Unbelievable]
- Is it real?
- It's amazing
Let me begin
Let's clean this up first
You're cleaning up really nice, Jimin
I clean things very well,
but I'm not good at organizing my clothes
[The beauty of a guy with confidence]
I like cleaning, except that
It's not that bad compared to last time
So many dishes were stacked up last time
[Muttering]
I can't check the temperature
I should rinse with hot water
[Team Kkakdugi works hard to clean up]
[Done with their penalty!
(We lost, but we enjoyed eating)]
[Run BTS - Kimchi Battle]