[Run BTS!]
[The return of BTS Marble!]
- Run!
- BTS!
You may not believe it
but we're currently in Hong Kong
Tsim Sha Tsui?
This is Tsim Sha Tsui, right?
Everyone, that's not important
There's a rumor that after
I wore hanbok
- Run BTS's reputation has gone up
- Really?
[Respect] [So proud]
- Jin!
- I gave the idea
and I was very proud of it
- You cook well, have broad shoulders
- I do
- You're good looking and good at dancing
- Good looking
[Never heard of it]
What?
[Let's move on]
What are we doing today?
Today's Run BTS is
an upgraded version of
BTS Marble from the MT episode
[Today's Run BTS]
[BTS Marble is back]
[The fun BTS Marble is back!]
[It's been upgraded with more games]
[Members will play a warm-up
game first to decide the order]
[After playing BTS marble for an hour
the two members with the least coins]
[will receive the penalty
Who will the two members be?]
As a warm-up game
to decide the order...
[Nervous] [How intense will the game be?]
We need a warm up?
- Halli Galli
I was a Hall-Master
[What's that?]
[Jin looks so confident]
You should all give up being first
Is it easier if you're
closer to the bell?
[So cool] [It's a piece of cake]
Halli Galli? It's easy
Please decide on the penalty first
Read a designated book then
write a report
[Explosive reactions]
That's nice
[Love it]
- More than 15 lines!
- What a good idea!
[True]
- You fall asleep reading books
- That's why it's a penalty
[What about this?]
- But it helps
- Climbing a mountain!
[Mountain?] [Hate that]
I don't like that
[As long as it's not me!]
- In winter?
- Let's write it down
Watching a scary movie with
headphones on, it's scary
[Useless penalty for Jung Kook]
- That's...
- I'm good with scary movies
- He's immune to it
- Then Jung Kook will climb a mountain
[Ardent applause]
- No, no, for Jung Kook
- Make him write a book report
Make him write a book report
[Strong denial]
No, no
That's nice
I've won the month's reading king
before
[He used to read books...]
It was an award given to
the student who read the most books
during the month
[The penalty wheel got
completed like this!]
[Today's Run BTS] [Halli Galli]
[Cards showing fruits in groups of 1 to 5]
[are equally divided across players
All players hold their deck face down]
[Players reveal their card
face up in front of them]
[The moment a player sees five of
one kind of fruit, they must hit the bell]
[and can take the played cards
If they're wrong]
[they must give one card
to each player]
[The one with the most cards
at the end wins!]
[The winner will decide the order
for BTS Marble!]
[Warm-up game]
[Halli Galli start!]
Are we going to have a practice
round or not?
[Practice round to get used to rules]
We should because I've never
played before
Are there people who don't
know the rules yet?
[Yes... These three...]
- I don't know it well
- I understood it all
[Hall-Master Jin's Halli Galli class]
Hold your cards like this
[Focused]
One hand reveals the cards
and the other hits the bell
- The winner of this game will
decide the order for BTS Marble
- Okay
[Jimin starts!]
- Let's go counter-clockwise
- That surprised me
[j-hope's fake!]
[Little lamb who fell for it]
Give us a card
[Surprised]
Why do you take my cards?
[That's the rule]
Everyone takes one
[He's broke]
Let's move on
[Sad...]
I only have two cards left
Please!
[11 plums and 6 strawberries]
- Why? There were 5!
- Nope
[Firm]
You're out
[Sad]
[Jin shared his deck with Jung Kook]
- Play one more round
- Try one more time
Go, Jung Kook!
I'm out of cards again
I didn't understand the rules
but I do now!
[All right]
I see
[And... Another stone statue]
- No
Give me yours, everyone
Every time we play a game
V has no clue what's going on
[Haha, you got me]
- That's right
- Here we go
[Reeling them in like a
professional fisherman]
You're really fast
[Fast as lightening]
What? Did we have 5?
There were 5
[He also only understood now]
Oh, so this is how you play it
[Urgent]
Have you all understood the rules
of the game now?
[Everyone looks at V]
Huh? This is too difficult
Let's shuffle the cards
and play again
[Practice game is over!]
Let's see if Jung Kook can win
[This is now the real game!]
As long as I avoid last place
- Let's go, V
- Let's go
[Members are sensitive with the real game]
- Consistently
- Oh, j-hope!
- j-hope!
Feeling great
Here I go
[Master of fake moves]
What? Me?
[When j-hope revealed his card
the strawberries became 5]
He's super fast!
[Amazed]
- How is he so fast?
- How is he so good at this game?
[These newbies]
Which fruit became 5?
[I still don't get it...]
Strawberry
Wow
- He's so fast!
- Great
[Was his major Halli Galli?]
Did he study Halli Galli
at Konkuk University?
He's so good
Can you donate a card to me?
[Forced noblesse oblige]
Right, donate a card to all of us
- Why?
- Hurry up
Put a card out and hit the bell
[What's he saying?]
Donate it
A Halli Galli major doesn't
make such mistakes
Hand!
[Jin made "that kind" of mistake]
[Good]
Yay!
- Let's hurry up
- Here we go
I've never touched the bell
[Hesitating] [Ding-dong!]
Oh, oh...
[Kicks of anger]
[Hilarious]
He's so cute
You're cute
[Cute Jung Kook is out again]
- Hilarious
- Hurry up
[Feeling empty]
- Is it me?
- You can't put your card like that
- How come I ran out of cards so fast?
- It's over
[That's because you're not
good at this game...]
I don't have any cards either
- No
[Oh... Oh?]
- There are five greens
- What?
[Wow!]
[Declaring bankruptcy one by one]
I only have one left
I'm out of cards
[Hall-Master is on fire]
Now it feels like Halli Galli
[Sweeping]
So fast
[Can't keep up with Jin's speed]
- As expected of a Halli Galli major!
- Great
[It was close! So close!]
- He's really good at this
- Jimin has only one card
I'll put everything on this round
Let's go! Oh?
[No... I bet everything on this...]
RM is left
- Good!
- Here we go
[RM vs Jin, 1-on-1 match!]
- 1-on-1?
- Here we go
[Everyone is watching
holding their breath...]
[Ding-dong!]
Oh no!
[So proud] [Amazed]
He's so great
Are you also a Halli Galli major
at Cyber University?
No, he double majors in it
Double major!
[High deck]
A lot has piled up
[Who will win at the end?]
Here they go
Argh!
Good!
[Great!]
- A double major can't win over a major
- Great!
I was pretty good in the past
- You know, this is a warm-up game, right?
- I know
Let's count their cards
The one with a higher deck will win
Okay, we'll give you 10 seconds
[Merciless]
10, 9, 8...
[So cool!]
Okay, you won
- Hey, now you can...
- I lost but I fought well!
You can decide the order
[The order to play BTS Marble
is at Jin's hands]
I'll decide the order
[Kissing up]
You looked so cool
[Members start talking to Jin]
Hey, I took your pictures
I'll show them to you right away
[Ambitious]
Please make me second
I'll announce the order now
[Of course]
First is Jin
[2nd player...] [Please tell me it's me]
The 2nd will be...
- The one who competed with...
- RM, who competed with me
- Thank you
- The 3rd one, the poor
[Silent pressure]
Jeon Jung Kook
There are so many poor guys
- We ran out of cards together
- I never even got to touch the bell
I competed with you as well
[Rock paper scissors when it's ambiguous]
Please play rock paper scissors
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
[Jung Kook wins!]
- This is important
- Rock paper scissors!
The 3rd player, Jeon Jung Kook
[Pit-a-pat]
The 4th player
- Play rock paper scissors again
- Really...
[j-hope wins!]
- Rock paper scissors
The 4th player is j-hope
- The 5th!
- Rock paper scissors
[Hey, I won...]
You two play rock paper scissors
The 5th player is SUGA
[Complaining]
The 6th and 7th players have
to go through properties owned by others
- Do you want to be the 7th player?
- What?
[I'm sad to hear that!]
I want to go 6th
Then please show me a personal talent
or act cute
[I won the rock paper scissors]
But I...
[Acting cute]
[I can't let him win]
Jimin rarely does that
[Cringe-worthy]
Hey! I'll just go 7th!
Stop it!
[Embarrassed after acting cute]
The 6th player
[Cute V]
V
[Boo]
Let's wrap this up
Let's sit according to the order
[Changing their seats
according to the order]
[Complaining]
Do you have a grudge against me?
[Complaining to the winner?]
- The 7th player... V
- No!
[V and Jimin get switched]
- The 6th player is Park Jimin!
- Okay! Let's switch seats!
[The result of going against power]
Hold on I didn't mean...
[Today's Run BTS!]
[Result of the Halli Galli game]
[BTS Marble order decided by Jin
[Jin > RM > Jung Kook > j-hope
> SUGA > Jimin > V]
[Today's Run BTS!]
[BTS Marble]
[The game will run for one hour
Complete the missions to buy land!]
[If a player lands on land bought
by another member, they have to
complete a mission to pass!]
[If they fail, they have to pay a fee]
[Ex: RM bought Danger for 4 coins]
[If Jung Kook lands on Danger and fails
he pays 4 coins to RM]
[When buying land, they'll have to pay
-1 coin compared to what's written
on the board]
[You must pay the coin amount
written on the board to pass]
[Ex: V succeeded the Stigma passion
and paid 2 coins for the 3 coin land
to buy it]
[Players will start with 50 coins
and when they get through the board once]
[they will be given 5 coins]
[The final result will be the total
of coins each player has]
[as well as the land they bought]
[Last place can only spin
the penalty wheel once]
[6th place will be able to
spin it twice and the other members
will receive snacks]
[BTS Marble START!]
- Let's play!
- Let's go!
[Hey]
Please begin
[A golden key from the start]
- 6!
- Golden key
It's not good to pick this
in the beginning
It actually doesn't matter now
Return your most expensive land
- It's not effective
- Right, invalid
[Jin's fruitless golden key]
I'll return it
[RM's turn]
"Begin!"
[Showing off moves]
[Moving so fast]
He's aiming to be the best dancer
Are you going to buy it?
[Of course]
Of course I will
[Has to complete a mission to buy it]
There's a mission
- Cham Cham Cham game
Beat the crew 3 times to succeed
- There's a mission?
- I have to pass it 3 times?
- Yes
[Trying right away!]
Okay
Cham Cham Cham
[RM succeeded the mission!]
[He bought "Begin"]
[He bought the land]
- We shouldn't be applauding
- Right
[Jung Kook's turn]
- Hahaha
- 6!
- Double
- Golden key
[A golden key from the start
for him as well!]
What is it?
Exempt from paying coins when
failing a mission
[Oh]
Throw it again
[Double: When two dices show the
same number, a player can throw again]
6!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
"Stigma"
Four letter quiz
You will hear the first 2 letters
of a 4-letter word
If you can guess the last 2, you succeed
That sounds hard
I won't buy it
Try it, you should try it
[Gullible]
- It could be easy
- I'll try
- He's trying
- Try
- National...
- Team members!
[Jung Kook buys "Stigma"]
- I told you it's easy
- Let's go
Boop!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
[Hehe]
Love Yourself
My favorite
Donate 3 coins to the village
[Straight face]
[SUGA's turn]
- Here we go
- All right
[Disappointed]
I didn't do anything and had to
donate 3 coins
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
- "No More Dream"
No, it's a free pass
[Oh... Is it?]
[Free Pass: A player can't buy the land
and there's no mission]
He said "No More Dream" so naturally!
[Jimin's turn]
[Landed on LOVE YOURSELF!]
Love Yourself!
[Smiling thinking about donation]
Donation?
[Happiness from donation hidden in places]
Love Yourself is hidden here and there
There are many Love Yourself spots
[V is playing while others are talking]
- Social welfare fund
- 4
"Spring Day"
[Human jukeboxes sing
the chorus automatically!]
What's the mission?
Korean alphabet game
- Say 3 words in 5 seconds
that consist of the alphabets given
- We've played this before
This is hard
[Trying right away!]
Ready, go!
[Given consonants: O and S]
Greeting, personality, excellence...
[Success!]
If you want to buy the land
give us coins
[Bought "Spring Day"]
- 1 coin?
- It's worth 2 coins
Since it's worth 2 coins, you take
1 coin off when you buy
[After playing a round, back to Jin]
- It came back to Jin
- Good, let's go
- Let's play fast
- Let's go
[Moving forward!]
9! 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
- Fire!
- Here we go!
[Give 3 nonsense answers to the question]
Nonsense party. Give nonsense answers
to the question
[Failure if it makes sense!]
Let's go right away
- 2 times 2 is?
- Worldwide handsome
- What's Jin's nickname?
- V is a fool!
[Oh? It makes sense]
- It makes sense
[Dumbfounded]
My nickname is "V is a fool?"
Think about names
There are random names out there
[Suppressing anger]
So what would be considered an answer?
Ho-ro-la-ya-ah-bba-tta!
What time is it?
Something like this
No
[It's not fair]
This is out of the scope
- I think Jin's right
- Right, it's out of the scope
[Jin is given a second chance]
- The 2nd one
- All right
- You need to answer one more question
- Okay
- What's the color of an apple?
- Paper cups are delicious
- A paper cup is delicious?
- Do you think it's delicious?
- Have you ever tried it?
- I don't know
[Struggled to buy "Fire"]
Good!
[Fast play]
- Me? I'll go right away
- Good for you
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
"Blanket Kick"
[I want to play...]
My turn never seems to come
- What's the mission?
- Korean alphabet game
[Let's go]
I'll play right away
Are distractions allowed?
[Staff allowed distractions]
[Alphabets given are G and P]
- G and P
- Watch!
[Brain no longer works]
[Hilarious]
[Great]
That was an amazing attack!
I tried to practice
[High level of difficulty]
but I couldn't think of anything
- Jung Kook's turn
- G and P are difficult
[Gets doubles whenever he throws]
Double
[Jung Kook also landed on "Blanket Kick"]
Doesn't that mean he has to play
the alphabet game?
Korean alphabet game
Let's get it!
1, 2, 3
[Give consonants: S and K]
- Stop
- Apple
Hard work, scam
[He succeeded despite the distractions]
Success!
[Bought "Blanket Kick"]
I'm awesome
[One more chance because of double]
- How come my turn comes so slowly?
- Let's play quickly
1, 2, 3
[LOVE YOURSELF donation]
- Love Yourself
- I'll donate
Where am I?
- There
- Okay
[Self BGM]
Boom!
Lucky seven!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
[Congratulations! You entered an island]
- Deserted island
- Lucky seven means deserted island
That hurts my heart
- j-hope is...
- 10
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Avoided the island]
- I avoided it, yes!
- What is that?
Four-letter quiz, start
- Bullet-proof
- Vest
That was too easy for SUGA
Can you believe I haven't
bought a single piece of land yet?
[Disappointed]
I want to buy one
[Dices look disappointed too]
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
["No More Dream" mission:
Nonsense party]
I'm not good at this
[Game he isn't confident in]
Let's go
- What's this color?
- You have a beautiful mole
- What can you see with your eyes closed?
- Your nose looks so pretty
- The question was what you can
see when closing your eyes
- What you can see with eyes closed
[SUGA's radar started working]
And producer's nose is pretty today
[That makes sense]
Oh, it makes sense
[Performing a short role play]
What can you see with your eyes closed?
I can see your beautiful nose
Okay, I'll admit this
[I want to buy a piece of land]
I want to buy one
Buying real estate isn't easy
[He makes it even more difficult...]
I'll go now
[Moved 6 spaces to reach "Baepsae"]
- 6
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 to "Baepsae"
[Flip a water bottle to succeed]
- Bottle flip?
- Bottle flip!
[A total of three chances]
- How do you do this?
- Let's go
- 1st try
- Now?
- Here we go
- Will he succeed at once?
- Close
- He did a great job
2nd try
He'll fail
[Wow]
[2nd attempt!]
[Success!]
[Like a movie scene]
It was like a movie
When j-hope said, "He'll fail,"
and then you threw it up and bam!
You usually succeed if someone
says such things
[V bought "Baepsae"]
V has bought two pieces of land
[Rushing due to the time limit]
- Now, Jin's turn
- Go
It's 6
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
[7 coins! Chance to get "Run"]
"Run"! 7 coins!
- Great!
- 7 coins
Nonsense party
[Oh, again?]
- Again?
- Here we go
- Where are we?
- I'm hungry
- Why are you so hungry?
- You're handsome!
- Who's handsome?
- Red
[Oh?]
Handsome? Red!
[I have no power to fight back...]
Who's usually good looking? Red!
[Hehe]
Your ears are also red
You're good looking right now too!
[Logic] [Who's the most handsome character]
Look at the power rangers or so
Think about the color
of the most handsome character?
- It's red
- Why do I keep getting this game?!
[Right]
This is a reach
[Let's move on]
- I'll go
- We have to hurry, there's not much time
- 11
- Why do I move so much?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11
[Making a fuss]
[Mission for "Fire"]
Nonsense party
- Here we go. What's your name?
- You make me begin
- What's the song title you're singing?
- I don't know where to go
- 2 times 2 is?
- What?
[Smiling]
Wrong answer!
[Perplexed]
Hold on, the question was...
[Creative]
It was a Japanese word
- Iie
- No
Okay, how much do I have to give?
[Cool guy RM paid 5 coins to Jin]
[Jung Kook's turn!]
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
- Taking a break might be better
[So excited he started babbling]
There's something here
[Jung Kook landed in "Awake"
owned by Jin]
Nonsense party again
- What's the color of an apple?
- There's a paddle there
[Greasy]
Look at me
[Trying to pull a trick]
He's trying to avoid it
- 2 times 2 is?
- What time is it now?
[Oh...]
What time is it now?
[Jimin laughing on the floor often]
[Happened to me too]
If you can't think of something to say
it's a fail
[Critical, Failed a 7-coin mission]
- How many coins?
- He's a new master of this game
7 coins, it was expensive
You have a golden key from before
[Jung Kook's golden key to exempt
him from paying]
Right!
Okay, let's move on
[Passing the person stuck on the island]
- I'm having a hard time
- The deserted island...
[SUGA landed on "N.O"]
- 1, 2, 3, 4 "N.O"
- What's the game?
- Announcer game
- What's that?
Say a tongue-twister sentence
without making a mistake in 10 seconds
[If you have time, you can try time]
It's like Peter Piper picked
Go!
I wish to wish the wish
you wish to wish
But if you wish to wish
the witch wishes
I won't wish the wish
you wish to wish
[Objection]
- Hey! Wrong!
- Wishes!
[Can't speak]
Wish and wishes
You should've said it in the middle
Why are you saying it afterward?
You passed 10 seconds anyway
[Oh, really...?]
[He failed!]
Here we go
Throw your dice
[Disappointed SUGA]
- Jimin's turn
- Let's hurry up
[Jimin's turn!]
- 10
- Oh... Deserted island
- Congratulations
[Jimin and j-hope]
- Jimin and j-hope
- Deserted island, turn up!
- 10
[Come on, fall on my land!]
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
- SUGA
[Player has to change where the accent is]
- "Danger"
- Absolute pitch game
[2 chances available!]
Please pick one
Almost there
- Crossing our paths...
- Ready, go
Crossing our paths is like a math formula
[Oh, smooth]
[Making a fuss]
Crossing our paths is like a math formula
[He's... Good at this?]
Crossing our paths is like a math formula!
[Perfect!]
Okay, that was perfect
Let's go
[Move forward 7 spaces!]
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
["DNA" mission, Cham Cham Cham]
- "DNA"
- Cham Cham Cham
[Only 30 minutes are left! Hurry up!]
- Left, right and middle, 3 times
- Okay
Cham Cham Cham!
[Failed in an instant]
This is so hard
Really hard
It's hard!
- 9! Jung Kook
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
"2! 3!"
[Make a sentence with the 5 words given]
Make a sentence?
- Will you go?
- Yes, this sounds difficult
Ready, go
[Box, V, watch, double eyelid, taxi]
I opened a box
and V came and said
there was a watch
[So?]
[Giving up]
Ah, this is a fail
Why? You can continue
with other words
So, his double eyelids opened up
[This isn't nonsense party]
I took that box and caught a taxi
[Difficult]
Hang on, what would be considered
a success?
It just has to make sense
[Double-master! Whenever he throws
he ends up with a double!]
Double!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
When a player passes this, give him 5 coins
[Monthly payment - 5 coins are given
when a player finishes a lap]
It's the monthly wage
- Please give it to me
- Yes, I'll give you 5 coins
[Jung Kook excited after receiving it]
Next
- 8!
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Big payment after getting paid]
- Donation
- Donation angel
- This is...
- BTS's donation king, Jeon Jung Kook!
[In a rush]
j-hope, spin it, hurry up
[Finally out of the island]
- Finally, my turn!
- Throw it well
[Variety show genius]
It'd be hilarious if you got out
and then landed on Jin's land
And if you get 7 right away, then?
- 4, "Mama"
- Hey, Mama!
[This is my song]
- I need to get this!
- It's a game for j-hope
[So desperate]
- j-hope!
- I want to buy this
- Make a sentence
- 1, 2, go!
[Mom, wallet, yellow, j-hope, icicle]
I went to my mom's place
and stole her wallet
And I bought a yellow neck-tie
j-hope wore it and felt
joy while touching icicles
[He's good]
I think that makes sense
[j-hope's first purchase!]
That was the best sentence so far
- That makes sense
- My heart is racing, feel it
Hearts are meant to race
[Calm down]
- If you don't, you'll die
- Does everybody owe property?
[Yes, you're the only one]
Yes, only you don't have one
[j-hope bought "Mama"]
I'm so nervous
My hands are trembling
Next turn SUGA, please
Yay!
- 5
- 1, 2, 3, 4
[SUGA landed on Jin's land "Awake"]
[I love it]
What's the game?
[Today's a nonsense party special]
- Nonsense party
1, 2, 3, go!
- Where are you from?
- I need a cup of water
- What do you want to drink?
- Let me look at the clock
[Throwing bait] [Bites it]
- What time is it?
- Well, what time is it?
[Hilarious]
[Hard to breathe]
7 coins! 7 coins, please
Thank you
[Give me the coins]
Aren't I being too funny?
- My sense of humor is amazing
- It was hilarious
- 5
- 1, 2, 3, 4
[2 players landed on Jin's property]
"Fire"! Jin, you're so lucky
[Jin's lucky day]
- It's his lucky day
- Right, today
["Fire" mission: Nonsense party]
Let's go
Ready, go!
- What's your favorite color?
- June 13, 2013
- What day is that?
- Maybe I should dance to Baepsae
- 2 times 2 is?
- Let's go! Everyone!
- Oh, isn't it 10?
- 10! 2 times 2 is 10!
I can't admit this
[That's not fair]
How come you can't admit this?
I just stretched my arms
He didn't say it right away
He bought time
[If a player takes time, he's out]
You need to answer right away
Oh, so you have to give Jin money?
Jin is winning the game
- He's got lots of property
- What's more important is...
[Who gets the last place matters]
First place doesn't matter since
we're picking 6th and 7th
[Unexpected benefit]
I did nothing but you're spending coins
- Being on the island might be better
- That's what I'm saying!
[Last turn... Jin's turn again]
Buying property isn't everything
- 7
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
[No benefit]
- Free pass
- I have to visit the starting point
[Sad] [Can't hear]
That's how I can earn coins...
[Passing the starting point!
RM arrived in "MIC Drop"]
- 1, 2, 3, "MIC Drop"
[Monthly wage]
Please give me 5 coins
[In a rush]
- Let's hurry up, there's only 20 minutes
- Flipping bottles
Bottle flip?
[Feeling pressure of the time limit]
Please start it right now
Okay
I'm going to be cool and succeed
[Success!]
That was so cool!
That was really cool!
[Doubtful]
- Why is he so good all of a sudden?
- Right?
- Big trouble for me
- I'll donate
[Threw the dice quietly and donated]
[I envy you]
Your character is so unique today
[You'll succeed!]
- Donation king!
- Unique character!
[j-hope got a double!]
- Double, 6
- I'm here
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
[Please]
If you receive all the donations
it would be amazing
[Golden key]
Pay the property tax, pay coins
for the number of property you own
- How many do you own?
- One
Give one then
[Calm down]
Why are you so excited?
[Excited]
- Why are you excited?
- It's fun
[A legendary scene]
I still remember the bottle flip
- I didn't know RM could do that
- 10
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
[Getting two golden keys]
Wow!
[Golden key]
Congratulations
Gain a property that you want
[Awesome]
- Amazing!
- Wow, awesome, I'm sweating
He can gain anything, right?
[Bought ARMY]
Amazing
- What a jackpot!
- Right, hurry up
I need to hurry up
[Those who are likely to be
at the last place feel stressed]
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
- "MIC Drop"
[MIC Drop mission: Bottle flip]
- Bottle flip
Wow, that was great for me
[Not really]
It was close
Let's succeed!
Let's make history!
[Entertainment master failed!]
Entertainment master, let's go!]
[SUGA gives 2 coins to RM]
- 2 coins
[Jimin finally got out of the island]
- 8
- 8?
- 8 Jimin, 8
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
[Jimin finally stepped on land]
It's nice!
You have to succeed the mission
to buy it
[Too early to get excited]
It's too early to be so happy
[Make a mission sentence]
- "2! 3!" What's the mission?
- Making a sentence
I'm really going to buy this one
[Hat, sweet potato, Jimin, dentist's
office, parking]
I wore a hat and ate a sweet potato
when Jimin got a toothache
and visited the dentist's office
He came back down and there
were too many cars parked
[What?]
- The parking lot was full
- Right
Do you own a car? You don't
- What? What does that matter?
- You don't need to park a car
[Jimin's dad]
I think it makes sense
- It makes sense
- Okay! Pass!
[Jimin finally bought "2! 3!"]
Did I get "2! 3!"? Thank you!
- Wow, everyone! Thanks to...
- Please give 7 coins, we don't have time
- Okay
- Next, V!
[Please]
Please 4 or 9! 4 or 9!
It's "Lie"
[Disappointed... I wanted 4 or 9...]
[It's okay]
What's the mission?
[Cheer up]
- "Lie?" "Lie"...
- That thing
[Lie's mission: Make a sentence]
- Make a sentence with 5 words
- Make a sentence
The last game
The last game of BTS Marble!
[Look who's talking]
The last place... V is in danger
[Hey, we're all in danger]
It's a neck-and-neck match
Calculate it
I donated too much
[Donation angel Jung Kook's
heart-warming moments of donation]
I'll donate
Donate! I'll donate
[Let's go for the last game!]
Ready, go!
[Paper, character, Jin,
bag, fragrant candle]
I took a look at a sheet of paper
and found a cartoon character
I took a closer look at it
and thought it was Jin
Oh! I don't know!
♪ It's alright, now count
1, 2, 3 and forget ♪
[Future MC]
All right, the game has come to an end
Hey! Why don't we each pick
a golden key
[Perfect teamwork]
- And try our luck for the donation?
- Yes
[Good!]
- What do you all think?
- I don't want the penalty
- Let's pick 7 golden keys and the person
who picks donation takes it all
- There's a donation card
[Chance to turn everything around!]
- Since the donation exists
- I think it's an amazing chance
[Production team chose
7 random golden keys]
We picked golden keys
Are you all participating?
[RM joins]
- Of course
- Me too
[V and Jung Kook]
Me too!
[Jimin] [I hate it]
- I will
- People with nothing to lose are scary
[Already the winner]
- It doesn't matter for me
- I'm the middle class
- Please spread them
- Should I just hand them out?
[Members are sensitive]
We're all sensitive right now
Please just give us the cards
It doesn't matter for me
[Distributing the golden key cards]
- Let's reveal them at once
- Let's do it one by one
[Revealing the cards one by one]
Let's do it one by one
I don't care what I got
Then, show yours first
Here we go
1, 2, 3, go!
[Golden key]
Congrats
Gain the property that you want
[Envious]
You can't beat a lucky person
[Bought RUN with the golden key]
- I'll buy "Run"
- Jin is so lucky
[Feeling nervous]
Then... Hold on
[Golden key: Great job! 5 coins]
- 5 coins
- What?
[You earn as much as you give]
What's going on?
[Pit a pat]
Oh my...
[Golden key: Won a lucky draw! 10 coins]
10 coins
See, the ones who don't participate
end up suffering
[Glance]
[Ah... My life...]
What is it?
[Golden key]
Return your most expensive property
- Is this just returning?
- Yes
[Peeping]
My most expensive one is that one
[Oh my my!]
[V's turn to reveal his card]
Next
[Golden key! Get donations
from LOVE YOURSELF]
Hang on! That will flip things around
[Drum sounds of joy]
Yeah, it changes everything
[Rags-to-riches story]
You changed your life around
Look at me, what fault do I have?
- If this is returning my most
expensive property...
- Together!
- What's your most expensive property?
- 4 coins
- Mine is worth 8 coins
- 1, 2, 3!
[Golden key, go to the starting point
5 coins of monthly pay will be given]
Go to the starting point
[Golden key: Return your most
expensive property]
Look, look at this
[j-hope got 5 coins]
Hold on!
Hang on, I think I'm 6th
Let's count our coins
[The top of the members' heads
as they are busy counting]
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
[Today's Run BTS!]
[BTS Marble Results]
[Winner- Jin, Fire(5 coins), Run(7 coins),
Awake(7 coins), 65 coins: Total 84]
[2nd place - j-hope, Lie(4 coins), MAMA
(5 coins), ARMY(8 coins), 47 coins: Total 64]
[2nd place - Jung Kook, Stigma(3 coins),
Blanket Kick(4 coins), 57 coins: Total 64]
[3rd place - Jimin
2! 3!(8 coins), 51 coins: total 59]
[3rd place - V, Spring Day(2 coins),
I Need U(3 coins), Baepsae(3 coins),
Danger(4 coins), 47 coins: Total 59]
[4th place - SUGA
Dope(4 coins), 41 coins: Total 45]
[5th place - RM
MIC Drop(2 coins), 40 coins: Total 42]
[Today's Run BTS!]
[BTS Marble Results]
[SUGA and RM will spin the penalty wheel!]
SUGA gets two chances to spin]
[RM gets only one chance]
- Were there any unexpected results?
- No
[As you know, the winner is Jin]
- As you know, the winner is...
- Jin
How many in total?
[With 84 coins, an overwhelming victory]
A total of 84 coins
2nd place, Jung Kook with 64 coins
He tied with j-hope
The 3rd place is... Jimin
who got "2! 3!" and 59 coins in total
[Pit a pat]
V is...
tied for 3rd place!
- If you didn't get the 18 coins...
- You were at rock bottom!
[Gritting his teeth]
I'd be at a higher rank
if we didn't play that last game!
By playing that game, V and
SUGA's ranks got switched
SUGA, 45 coins, 4th place
[RM is last]
RM, the 5th place with 42 coins
[Tok tok! Moni and Gani]
Moni, Gani, let's go
[Let's spin the penalty wheel!]
What penalty will we have today?
Please give it a spin!
[Gasp]
- Oh no!
- He spun it fast!
[Mountain climbing]
Wow! Mountain climbing!
[The penalty that he mentioned]
[Dragging others]
Hey! Let's go together! Hand in hand!
Moni and Gani together
You know, I haven't had
a penalty in a while
- Let's go!
- Mountain climbing... Wow
SUGA, Gani! SUGA, Gani!
[Watching a scary movie
with headphones on]
A scary movie!
[Taking a risk of mountain climbing]
- Will he spin one more time?
- Will you?
[Will he?]
If you spin one more time
you can't change the result
[SUGA's choice is...]
[Simple]
- I'll spin again
- Really?
- Really? You need to accept it
- I hate scary movies that much
[2nd try]
- Please give it a spin!
- Mountain climbing! Let's go together!
- SUGA...
- Mountain climbing!
[The penalty that he said, Write
a book report of more than 10 lines]
Book report!
[His dream of climbing together is crushed]
That was so close
Mountain climbing was on the left
[Proving he's a lucky guy]
I escaped well
[Snack from Hong Kong's famous
restaurant is served for the rest!]
We've prepared...
[Sadness and happiness together]
[Disappointed]
We can't have it?
We'll eat the meal over there
They can stay here
[Bags of food coming in]
Wow, there are a lot
[Nom nom] [He's eating well]
[Tasty]
We've tried this place before
We bought a lot so share
it among yourselves
Don't pretend to be generous!
I'll go outside and get some
with my own money!
- Did you lose your appetite?
- I'm worried about mountain climbing
[Already seated next to them]
- Have some
- This is good
- What is it?
[Yum yum]
Tasty!
You're dropping crumbs everywhere!
[A bunch of crumbs here too]
[MC Min is back]
Anyways, Run BTS will continue
Are you going home now?
[Of course]
Yes
[Bye!]
- Because I need to read a book
- Are there mountains in Hong Kong?
[Please look forward to
RM's mountain hike!]
[This is the final concert of
The Wings Tour]
[Production team came to
give SUGA a book for the book report]
What is this?
[I don't know what to say]
- For Run BTS...
- It's a children's book!
[Not sure]
I think I've read this before when
I was younger
Anyways... When is the deadline?
There's a form inside
- Until the next Run BTS shoot
- Okay
- ♪ My bag is full of trophies ♪
- It reminds me of the past
[Interruption by the youngest's voice]
I got it
- Good luck with your concert
- Thank you
[Good luck on the book report as well...]