[NewJeans are all in one place
for the digital cover of NME]
[First up is HANNI!]
[Listening to what she'll be doing]
That sounds like so much fun!
Oh, this is so exciting
[HANNI sits in front of the drums]
[Getting ready]
[Boom!]
[Bang!]
[Really getting into it]
[Time to start!]
[HANNI is looking at all the props]
[Let's monitor the photos]
Oh? Okay!
[Confused HANNI]
[LOL]
Bye
See you later
[Encore]
[The result of HANNI's photo shoot!]
Hello
It's NewJeans' DANIELLE
Sudden self-introduction
Oh! HANNI just finished up
[HANNI is here]
Today
I have a funky, rock star look going on
Let's go see what's going on!
[Let's go watch MINJI's photo shoot, go!]
[Ta-da♥]
[HANNI and HAERIN are also watching MINJI]
Kitty
Our kitty is here
[Hi]
[Look at MINJI!]
[Suddenly very focused]
KIM MINJI
[So cool!]
[The next concept is to
play the electronic keyboard]
[Pretending to play]
[Wow]
Right now, MINJI
MINJI? Yes
[LOL]
MINJI is playing the piano!
She's playing the electronic keyboard
She looks like such a natural at it!
[Professional KIM MINJI]
[Live updates of what's going on]
She's leaning on the keyboard like this
She's thinking!
MINJI is thinking about things!
[Thinking]
MINJI looks so pretty right now!
But you can't see it just yet!
[Teasing Bunnies]
MINJI's playing the piano in her photos
and she looks like she's good at it
but she's really not in real life
[So funny, LOL]
Diss
[Queen of dissing]
[Let's say that only MINJI
knows her true piano skills]
Oh! MINJI
[Awesome]
You can't see it yet!
But MINJI looks so pretty right now!
Shhh
[Top secret just for them]
-You want to know, right? Right?
-Look, look
[These two are having fun teasing Bunnies]
Bye
[Sudden end]
[MINJI's photo that DANIELLE
& HAERIN were in awe of!]
[Done!]
[Passing the baton to DANIELLE!]
[MINJI, you were awesome!]
I feel like a rock star!
Wow...
[Listening to what her concept will be]
That sounds fun, yes!
[Warming up before the shoot]
Wow, look at this mic!
[Immediately concentrating]
[Wink♥]
Wow, I have to hold it up with one hand!
[Wobble]
Wait, this is too heavy
Is it?
[Changing guitars]
[Lift]
[New guitar doesn't shake
in DANIELLE's hand★]
The guitar looks so cool
[Succeeds in getting photos with
the guitar she had her eye on]
I like it
[Energetic concept goes
perfectly with DANIELLE]
[Having fun till the very last cut♪]
[Monitoring her photos]
A total rock star
[DANIELLE's photo!]
Hello
Today, we're rock stars
A lobster?
The lobster you eat!
The lobster you eat
[Hi]
It's my first time with hair this dark!
I had lighter brown hair before
It's my first time taking photos
with hair this dark, so I'm excited
[Shows off her cute ring]
[Our queen of photo shoots, HYEIN]
[Concentrating]
[Serious when monitoring photos]
[Spots the camera]
[Shows off her ring one more time]
[Time for HAERIN's
individual photo shoot!]
[Flick]
[Flick 2]
[Flick 3]
[Continuously flicking her hair back]
[Gets an apple]
I think this is a speaker
I really like this!
[Unique prop catches HAERIN's eye]
And
I have this ring on today
Isn't it so pretty?
[Gumdrop ring]
[Today's must-have accessory
is the gumdrop ring]
I like this too!
[Has her eye on a lot of things]
[Nom]
[Today, HAERIN is the apple lover]
[Getting ready to take photos with drums]
[Could you throw
the drum sticks in the air?]
[Warming up her wrists beforehand]
[Gets into the shoot right away]
[Nervous]
[Photo shoot wraps up
after throwing the drumsticks!]
[HAERIN's photo!]
Hello!
Today, we're taking photos
for NME magazine!
And one more thing!
We all dyed our hair dark today!
It's a really dark color, right?
But as the days pass
it will look more natural
I'm curious to see that
Humans are really good at adapting
Despite having lighter hair
up till this morning
I've already gotten used to
this hair in just a few hours!
[Looking perfect as always]
Pardon?
Let's go!
[Let's go take group photos!]
[Hi]
Today
we're going for a rock style!
[This concept is the best]
Kind of like this
[Group]
[photo shoot]
[Move closer!]
[Showing off her gumdrop ring]
[Nom]
[No!] [Nom]
[Poke]
[Mischief mode activated]
[Going in a second time]
[HYEIN didn't do anything]
[Timid teasing +1]
[More teasing]
[Roar]
You could never play with these nails!
Right?!
[Acting like the world's greatest pianist]
[This time, she's a guitarist]
[I]
[can't play guitar]
[I can't]
[play the guitar!]
[But it's okay]
[DANIELLE is full of energy
even when cameras aren't rolling]
[Spots her]
[Me too]
[Hula dancing]
[Laughter]
What are you doing?
Doesn't the smokey eye makeup suit her?
Everything looks good on DANIELLE!
[Dance dance]
[Bringing the energy up for the shoot!]
[Photo shoot wraps up]
Wow, great job!
-Thank you
-Thank you!
[So excited]
Great job!
[Bye]
[Successfully wraps up the photo shoot!]
Everyone's a rock star
[Please give the NME
photo shoot lots of love!]
Rock stars
Great job!